<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<source>
  <publisher>Myticas Consulting Job Site</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://myticas.com/</publisherurl>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior System Engineer (32529) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 10, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ V5WF29YSDQ ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 32529 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>The Senior System Engineer will contribute to our clients program in conducting advance performance assessment studies for system configurations as needed to provide solution for complex customer needs. Using his / her expertise in satellite communications, orbital configuration and large communication networks, the candidate will define solutions with enough details to enable implementation across their system. </p> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Develop new solutions to commercial needs using their system, including among others solutions for low latency high capacity services, hosted satellite (space relay) services, mobile services, and other new configurations to support opportunities. <li>Support sales activities by evaluating complex use cases using internal and commercially available simulation tools. <li>Evaluate system performance boundaries by incorporating realistic user traffic profiles and terminal mix. <li>Help prepare and manage feature development roadmap in collaboration with commercial and engineering teams by evaluating value-add. <li>Develop technical documentation and reports. <li>Prepare and deliver high quality technical presentations supporting the delivery of solutions. </ul> <p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong></p> <ul> <li>B. Sc. in Electrical, Computer or System Engineering and a minimum of 5 years of relevant experience in satellite communications or other large communication systems. <li>Experience in system simulations and service performance assessments. <li>Programming experience in Matlab and / or Python. <li>Knowledge of radio communication systems and/or satellite communication is desirable (experience with link budgets is an asset). </ul> <p><strong>Specialized Knowledge, Skills and Abilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Creative problem-solver with thorough attention to detail. <li>Highly collaborative team-player who can quickly earn the confidence of co-workers and teammates. <li>Excellent oral and written communication skills. <li>Experience with STK for orbital analyses is an asset. <li>Fluent in English, written and oral. <li>Computers running Windows and Linux </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Direct Hire ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Onsite ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Local to Michigan -Cloud Architect, Hybrid (SOM-144546) (32642) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 21, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ EEA85SYZUN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 32642 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas' direct client, based in Lansing, MI, is seeking a <strong>Cloud Architect</strong> to work on a hybrid schedule in Lansing, MI (on-site 2 days per week).</p> <p><strong>Please Note:</strong></p> <ul> <li><strong>Position Location:</strong> Lansing, MI. The resource will follow a hybrid schedule and <strong>must</strong> be on-site from day one, two days a week (typically Tuesdays and Wednesdays). <li><strong>Local candidates are strongly preferred</strong>, but non-local candidates may apply if willing to relocate at their own expense and adhere to the hybrid schedule without delays. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Top Required Skills & Years of Experience:</strong></h3> <ul> <li><strong>Experience:</strong> 5+ years in the field. <li>Strong expertise in .NET, HTML, XML, SQL, SOAP, REST, PowerShell, IaC, Microsoft Azure, and Function Apps. <li>Hands-on experience writing and implementing Infrastructure as Code (IaC). <li>Comprehensive knowledge of Microsoft Azure, web-based systems, and client-server-based architecture. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Preferred Skills:</strong></h3> <ul> <li>Ability to conduct interviews and build effective relationships with system users. <li>Proficient in Microsoft Visio and Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint). <li>Experience in analyzing, designing, programming, testing, implementing, and supporting web-based applications on the Microsoft/Windows platform (e.g., ASP.NET framework 4.8 or higher, .NET 6 or higher). </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Job Summary:</strong></h3> <p>The <strong>Cloud Application Architect</strong> will serve as a technical expert for the Michigan Center for Educational Performance and Information (CEPI). This role involves designing and orchestrating the placement and interaction of application components to meet business requirements while balancing factors such as sustainability, cost control, standardization, security, compliance, and strategic alignment.</p> <p>This position will focus on IT system modernization initiatives within the CEPI portfolio and ensure seamless integration of the CEPI Cloud infrastructure with COTS packages, SaaS, Web Services, and other federal, state, and local government applications and services (both internal and external to the State).</p> <p>The Cloud Architect will provide technical expertise and leadership to the application development team, promoting usability, security, mobility, maintainability, and reusability. This role requires minimal supervision and involves significant collaboration with program managers and technology oversight groups. The architect will work as part of a team of architects/designers, supported by additional staff.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></h3> <ul> <li>Lead the development and application of technical architecture strategies. <li>Analyze technical and business problems and recommend solutions to improve processes and enable productivity. <li>Collaborate with other architects and developers to select and adapt cloud architecture frameworks and tools to project needs. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Skills/Experience:</strong></h3> <ul> <li>In-depth knowledge of complex cloud application development environments and practices. <li>Ability to gather and analyze facts, define problems, and recommend solutions. <li>Thorough understanding of cloud application development architecture, frameworks, and tools. <li>Advanced knowledge of business requirements, network-based application orchestration, database management, and application development. <li>Expertise in advanced cloud application development and integration techniques. <li>Strong proficiency in .NET, HTML, XML, SQL, SOAP, REST, PowerShell, IaC, Microsoft Azure, and Function Apps. <li>Knowledge of secure coding and authorization concepts, relational database principles, web services, and microservices architecture. <li>Experience with distributed tracing and observability. <li>Proficient in creating and maintaining distributed applications using microservices. <li>Excellent technical documentation and presentation skills. <li>Strong problem-solving and troubleshooting abilities in high-stress environments. <li>Self-motivated, capable of managing tasks independently with minimal supervision. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Additional Qualifications:</strong></h3> <ul> <li>Knowledge/training in object-oriented analysis, design, and programming. <li>Familiarity with cloud application and database development methods. <li>Ability to prepare detailed instructions and documentation. <li>Capacity to establish and maintain effective relationships with clients and support teams. </ul> <p>This role requires a candidate who can work efficiently under pressure, handle complex assignments, and deliver optimum solutions in a timely manner. The ideal candidate will be proactive, technically skilled, and collaborative, ensuring successful delivery of cloud architecture projects.</p> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Lansing ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ MI ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ SAP FICO Functional Lead - Oil & Gas (32637) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 18, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ TZFS5OMLPT ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 32637 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is seeking an experienced <strong>SAP FICO Functional Lead</strong> for a long-term contract opportunity supporting a high-profile SAP S/4HANA transformation project within the oil and gas sector.</p> <p>This leadership role will play a key part in driving finance-related workstreams, providing expert guidance on core SAP FI/CO modules, and aligning solution delivery to the needs of an asset-intensive organization.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead the design, configuration, and deployment of SAP FI/CO modules (GL, AP, AR, AA, CO-OM, PCA, etc.)</p> <li> <p>Collaborate closely with finance and business stakeholders to gather requirements and define functional specs</p> <li> <p>Drive integration with upstream and downstream modules and legacy systems</p> <li> <p>Ensure alignment with industry best practices and EY methodology for SAP implementations</p> <li> <p>Support UAT, cutover planning, data migration, and go-live activities</p> <li> <p>Lead or mentor junior consultants and ensure effective knowledge transfer</p> </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>10+ years of SAP FICO experience with at least 2 full-cycle implementations</p> <li> <p>Proven functional leadership experience on large-scale SAP projects</p> <li> <p>Strong background in asset-intensive industries (oil and gas preferred)</p> <li> <p>Hands-on experience with S/4HANA Finance (nice to have but not required)</p> <li> <p>Excellent communication and stakeholder engagement skills</p> <li> <p>Ability to work onsite in Vancouver for the majority of the engagement</p> </ul> <p><strong>Contract Details:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Duration: Initial 12 months with potential extension</p> <li> <p>Work Location: Vancouver, BC (Calgary-based candidates may be considered with travel flexibility)</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Vancouver ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ BC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[  DevOps Technical Analyst (32638) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 18, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ J7R9KOSNRN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 32638 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is seeking a self-motivated <strong>Technical Analyst</strong> to support a long-term engagement with our non for profit client. This is a two-year contract opportunity ideal for a DevOps-savvy analyst with a strong foundation in system analysis and cloud/infrastructure operations. The ideal candidate will thrive in a collaborative environment, have a passion for automation and modern DevOps practices, and be eager to take ownership in a hands-on technical role.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Manage, maintain, and enhance cloud and on-premise environments</p> <li> <p>Implement and optimize CI/CD pipelines</p> <li> <p>Conduct system and integration analysis to ensure high performance and availability</p> <li> <p>Collaborate with development and infrastructure teams to support environment configuration and deployment</p> <li> <p>Leverage monitoring tools to identify and resolve technical issues proactively</p> <li> <p>Mentor junior team members and contribute to best practices documentation</p> </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <p><strong>Education:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or a related field</p> <li> <p>Certifications such as AWS, ITIL, or similar are an asset</p> </ul> <p><strong>Experience:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5+ years in system analysis, environment management, or software engineering</p> <li> <p>Experience with cloud platforms and managing hybrid infrastructure</p> <li> <p>Hands-on with DevOps tools and CI/CD processes</p> </ul> <p><strong>Technical Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Proficient in APIs, RESTful services, and system integration</p> <li> <p>Skilled in containerization (Docker, Kubernetes)</p> <li> <p>Experience with version control tools (Git)</p> <li> <p>Scripting capabilities (Python, Bash)</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with monitoring and automation frameworks</p> </ul> <p><strong>Soft Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Excellent analytical and communication skills</p> <li> <p>Leadership qualities and ability to mentor others</p> <li> <p>Self-starter mindset with strong organizational abilities</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Cloud Operations Engineer (32574) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 25, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ FPVMEV8Z3K ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 32574 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Cloud Operations Engineer<br> <strong>Location:</strong> Vancouver, BC</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Qualifications Required</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Computer Science, Information Technology, Cybersecurity, or a related field. Equivalent professional experience will also be considered.</p> <li> <p>A minimum of 7 years of experience in Azure cloud operations, with a strong focus on security and vulnerability management.</p> <li> <p>Proven experience in managing and securing large-scale Azure environments in production settings.</p> <li> <p>Hands-on experience with vulnerability scanning, remediation, and compliance within enterprise cloud infrastructures.</p> <li> <p>Extensive experience in security incident response and threat mitigation in Azure environments.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Technical Skills</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Azure Expertise</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Deep understanding of core Azure services, including:</p> <ul> <li> <p>Azure Security Center</p> <li> <p>Microsoft Defender for Cloud</p> <li> <p>Azure Key Vault</p> <li> <p>Azure Policy</p> <li> <p>Azure Sentinel (SIEM)</p> <li> <p>Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)</p> </ul> </ul> <p><strong>Security and Vulnerability Tools</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Proficient in using tools such as Qualys, Tenable Nessus, or Rapid7 for vulnerability scanning and management.</p> <li> <p>Experience with native Azure security tools for threat detection and remediation.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Infrastructure Hardening</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Strong knowledge of best practices for securing Azure resources such as virtual machines, storage accounts, Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), and network components.</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with zero-trust architecture principles and their implementation in Azure.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Automation and Scripting</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Advanced scripting skills using PowerShell, Azure CLI, Python, or other automation tools.</p> <li> <p>Experience in integrating security checks and controls within CI/CD pipelines.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Certifications (Preferred or Mandatory)</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Azure Cloud Certifications</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Microsoft Certified: Azure Administrator Associate (AZ-104)</p> <li> <p>Microsoft Certified: Azure Security Engineer Associate (AZ-500)</p> <li> <p>Microsoft Certified: Cybersecurity Architect Expert (SC-100)</p> </ul> <p><strong>Security Certifications</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP)</p> <li> <p>Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH)</p> <li> <p>CompTIA Security+</p> <li> <p>GIAC certifications (e.g., GCIH, GSEC, GCED)</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Other Requirements</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Familiarity with regulatory and compliance standards such as ISO 27001, SOC 2, GDPR, and HIPAA.</p> <li> <p>Experience conducting or supporting cloud security audits.</p> <li> <p>Demonstrated ability to stay up to date with emerging cloud and cybersecurity technologies and trends.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Vancouver  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ British Columbia ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dominic Scaletta ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior ASIC Design & Product Integration Engineer (32623) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ NQIG6GN0KA ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32623]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Our client is seeking a Senior ASIC Design and Product Integration Engineer to join their team working on cutting-edge ASIC technology. </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Main Responsibilities:</span>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Translate high-level system requirements into detailed IC specifications.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Drive ASIC design validation, performance evaluation, and reliability testing.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Serve as the technical liaison between ASIC designers and hardware integration teams.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Manage the delivery of prototype silicon for validation and analysis.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Perform statistical data analysis on large datasets to assess and enhance IC performance.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Troubleshoot silicon issues and drive resolution collaboratively with design teams.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Support manufacturing ramp-up with yield, capability, and supply planning assessments.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Develop technical documentation and application notes for IC integration support.Hands-on experience in analog ASIC product or application engineering, across multiple product development cycles.</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Required Skills and Qualifications:</span>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Strong understanding of analog circuit behavior and device physics, with a proven track record in failure analysis and performance optimization.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Proficiency in statistical data analysis and large dataset handling.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Excellent communication and presentation skills, with the ability to engage cross-functional teams.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Programming and process development experience is a strong asset.</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Bachelor’s degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, or Physics.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">MS with 4+ years, or PhD with 2+ years of relevant experience in analog ASIC product or application engineering.</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Location:</span>
    </strong><br> <span style="">Hybrid, United States.</span>
    </span></span>
    <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ High-Speed Analog ASIC Engineer (32624) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ D8V1LE1LBH ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32624]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Our client is seeking a talented High-Speed Analog Engineer to join their innovative team building next-generation >100Gbaud integrated circuits for high-performance data center and communication products.</span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Responsibilities:</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Lead the design, layout, and bring-up of ultra-high-speed analog ICs.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Contribute to all phases of IC development, including validation and characterization.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Collaborate with verification, CAD, product, and test engineering teams to execute design verification test (DVT) plans.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Support product performance evaluation and refinement in the lab environment.</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Required Skills and Experience:</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Experience designing high-speed analog ICs using SiGe BiCMOS or CMOS technologies.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Solid understanding of transmission lines and high-frequency passive structures.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Strong grasp of device physics and its impact on analog performance.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Hands-on experience with RF wafer probing and lab evaluation of high-speed ICs.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Familiarity with VerilogA and scripting (Skill, Python, shell) is an asset.</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Effective communicator and strong team player.</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Qualifications:</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">BS in Electrical Engineering or related field with 5+ years of relevant experience</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">MS with 3+ years of experience</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">PhD in a related field (experience level flexible)</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Location:</span>
    </strong><br> <span style="">Hybrid – United States</span>
    </span></span>
    <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Principal ASIC Verification Engineer  (32625) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ DR89VQ8A8D ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32625]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Our client is seeking a<strong> Principal</strong> <strong>ASIC Verification Engineer</strong> to join a high-performing team developing leading-edge technology for next-generation optical networks and data centers.<br> <br> <strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Drive the development of verification infrastructure using SystemVerilog and UVM.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Create protocol/traffic generators, checkers, and testbenches aligned with functional and standards-based requirements.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Define and implement test plans at the block and sub-chip levels for advanced digital ASICs.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Develop and execute self-checking test environments to ensure thorough validation.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Collaborate with cross-functional teams in a geographically distributed environment.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Optionally lead small teams or verification efforts for key deliverables.</span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Bachelor’s degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, or a related field (Master’s preferred).</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">10+ years of experience in ASIC verification with hands-on expertise in UVM and SystemVerilog.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Solid knowledge of assertions, functional and code coverage, and formal verification tools.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Proficiency in scripting languages such as Python.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Strong problem-solving skills and a collaborative mindset.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Experience with DSP and/or FEC is a plus.</span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Location:</strong>
    <br> Hybrid – Canada</span>
    <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Lead Mixed - Signal IC Design Engineer - High -Speed Circuits (32627) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ KPC8YUFM0M ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32627]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Our client is seeking a <strong>Lead Mixed-Signal IC Design Engineer- High-Speed Circuits </strong>to join a cutting-edge team building advanced analog and mixed-signal IP for next-generation communications and data center systems.</span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Design, implement, and simulate high-speed analog blocks such as ADCs, DACs, and PLLs.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Optimize floorplans, supervise layout teams, and provide layout guidance (including hands-on layout work when needed).</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Evaluate and select circuit topologies to meet stringent performance goals in terms of power, area, linearity, and bandwidth.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Develop test plans and collaborate with product and test engineering teams for validation and characterization.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Follow established design flows and contribute to process improvements.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Model analog circuits using Verilog-A/AMS for system-level simulations.</span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Key Qualifications:</strong>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Strong experience with CAD tools: Cadence Virtuoso, Spectre, Incisive, Calibre, EMX, Totem EM/IR.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Proven track record designing and bringing to production high-speed analog/mixed-signal IPs in deep submicron CMOS (e.g., high-speed ADCs, DACs, low-jitter PLLs).</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">In-depth understanding of analog circuit methodologies, layout effects, and device physics.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Experience with behavioral modeling (Verilog-A/AMS).</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Ability to work collaboratively with distributed design teams.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Strong problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and effective communication.</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Experience with Matlab and/or optical communication theory is a plus.</span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Education & Experience:</strong>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">M.S. in Electrical Engineering with 12+ years of experience, or</span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;">Ph.D. in Electrical Engineering with 8+ years of experience.</span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><strong>Location:</strong>
    <br> Hybrid – United States</span>
    <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Lead Custom Analog Layout Engineeer (32628) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ BP1HB6XNOE ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32628]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Our client is seeking a <strong>Lead Custom Analog Layout Engineer</strong> to support the development of high-performance analog and mixed-signal ICs for next-generation communication and data center systems. In this hybrid U.S.-based role, you&apos;ll collaborate closely with circuit designers to ensure optimal layout quality, performance, and delivery timelines.</span>
    </span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Partner with circuit designers to optimize block- and chip-level floorplans.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Perform daily layout editing, verification (DRC/LVS), and quality checks using industry-standard tools.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Apply best practices and efficient layout methodologies to streamline design cycles.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Contribute to chip-level integration, including P&R and top-level planning.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Key Qualifications:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Extensive experience using layout tools such as Cadence Virtuoso and/or Laker.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Proficiency in DRC/LVS/ERC verification flows (e.g., Calibre, PVS, IC Validator).</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Solid understanding of layout challenges including IR drop, EM, RC delay, crosstalk, self-heating, and analog matching techniques.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Hands-on experience designing layouts for precision analog blocks like SD-ADC, SAR-ADC, bandgaps, and regulators.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Familiarity with analog design methodologies and layout constraints.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Experience with RC extraction and EM/IR analysis is a plus.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Strong communication skills and ability to work effectively with cross-functional, distributed teams.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Education & Experience:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field or equivalent experience.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">10+ years of experience in analog/mixed-signal layout design.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Location:</strong>
    <br> Hybrid – United States</span>
    </span><br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Principal Engineer - High Speed Analog IC Research &Development (32629) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 0VYGW3V0WK ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32629]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Our client is seeking a Principal Engineer - High Speed IC Research & Development. This role offers the opportunity to contribute to the development of high-performance analog ICs that enable next-generation communication networks. </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">Responsibilities:</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Design, lay out, and bring up ultra high-speed analog ICs</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Drive the development and validation of custom ICs for high-capacity networking systems</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Collaborate with verification, CAD, product, and test engineering teams to define and execute DVT and characterization plans</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Evaluate and optimize circuit performance using RF probing and lab tools</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Qualifications:</span>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Proven experience designing high-speed analog ICs using SiGe BiCMOS or CMOS</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Solid grasp of transmission lines, passive high-frequency structures, and device physics</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Hands-on skills with RF lab equipment and analog IC evaluation</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Familiarity with VerilogA and CAD scripting languages (Skill, Python, Shell) is a plus</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Strong communication and teamwork abilities</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Bachelor’s degree with 5+ years of relevant experience</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Master’s degree with 3+ years</span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">PhD candidates welcomed</span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Location:</span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Hybrid, United States</span>
    </span></span>
    <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Mixed -Signal ASIC Design Engineer (32626) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ YGBB3KM4TS ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32626]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Our client is seeking a <strong>Senior Mixed-Signal ASIC Design Engineer</strong> to join a dynamic team working on next-generation integrated circuits for high-performance communication and data center applications.</span>
    </span><br> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Responsibilities:</span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Design and simulate high-resolution data converters (DACs/ADCs) and low-power analog circuits such as bandgap references, opamps, and output buffers.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Develop layout floorplans, supervise layout activities, and provide clear guidance to layout engineers (hands-on layout work may be required).</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Create analog test plans and collaborate with product/test engineering teams for characterization and validation.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Follow established design methodologies and release processes to ensure product quality and consistency.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Model circuit behavior using Verilog-A/AMS for design verification.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Key Qualifications:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Strong expertise with analog/mixed-signal design tools (Cadence Virtuoso, Spectre, Layout XL, Mentor AFS, Calibre).</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Proven experience in taking data converters from design to production.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">In-depth understanding of CMOS and high-voltage (BCD) design, layout effects, and ESD protection.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Skilled in circuit analysis, device physics, and analog design methodology.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Excellent communication skills and ability to work effectively in cross-functional, distributed teams.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="">Capable of mentoring junior engineers and independently resolving complex design challenges.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Education & Experience:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Staff Design Engineer</strong>: M.S. in Electrical Engineering with 8+ years of experience or Ph.D. with 8+ years.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin-right: 0.0in;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Principal Design Engineer</strong>: M.S. with 12+ years or Ph.D. with 12+ years of experience.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style=""><strong>Location:</strong>
    <br> Hybrid – United States</span>
    </span><br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Sunnyvale ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Power BI Architect (32633) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 17, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ HYWO3DGG0Q ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32633]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div style=""><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Myticas direct client is seeking </span>Power BI Architect at </span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Waukegan, IL (<strong>Hybrid, </strong>
    </span><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);"><strong>3 days in the office</strong>, 3 days of choice Monday – Thursday. Onsite Hybrid schedule is mandatory, cannot be altered)</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </div> <div style=""><br> <span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Duration:</span>
    </span></strong>
    <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;"> 6+ month contract</span>
    </span><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"> (</span>
    <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">potential to extend)</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </div> <div style=""><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span>
    </span><br> <u><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">TOP 5 SKILLS:</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span></u>
    </span></span>
    </span></div> <div style=""> </div> <ol> <li style=""><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);font-family: Aptos;font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience with design and architecture</span> <li style=""><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);font-family: Aptos;font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience with data modelling</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style=""><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience with Performance Optimization.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style=""><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience as a BI Architect or similar role, with 5-7 years’ experience in Power BI.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style=""><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Strong expertise in full Microsoft BI Suite, data modeling, DAX, and Power Query.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> </ol> <div style=""> <ol style="margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-top: 0.0cm;"> </ol> <span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">JOB SUMMARY:</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">We are seeking a highly skilled Power BI Architect to join our dynamic team. As a Power BI Architect, you will be responsible for designing and implementing effective BI solutions that transform data into actionable insights. You will lead the strategic development of our Power BI platform, ensuring scalability, reliability, and optimal performance.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">Key Responsibilities:</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <ul style="margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-top: 0.0cm;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Design and Architecture: Develop and design the architecture of the Power BI platform, Power Automate, and Power Apps, ensuring alignment with business requirements and best practices.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Data Modeling: Create efficient and scalable dimensional data models that facilitate data analysis and reporting.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Dashboard Development: Lead the development of dynamic and interactive dashboards that provide valuable insights to stakeholders.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Integration: Collaborate with IT and data engineering teams to integrate Power BI with various data sources and systems.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Performance Optimization: Identify and implement strategies to optimize the performance of Power BI reports and dashboards.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Security: Ensure data security and compliance with organizational policies and industry standards.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Strategy and Planning: Advise on BI strategy and roadmaps, aligning business needs with technology advancements.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Training and Support: Provide training and support to end-users and junior team members, promoting effective use of Power BI tools.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Documentation: Maintain comprehensive documentation of architectural designs, configurations, and project specifications.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">Qualifications:</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <ul style="margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-top: 0.0cm;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Bachelor’s degree in computer science, Information Systems, or a related field.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Proven experience as a BI Architect or similar role, with 5-7 years’ experience in Power BI.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Strong expertise in full Microsoft BI Suite, data modeling, DAX, and Power Query.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience with SQL, Python, Jupyter Notebooks, and integrating Power BI with various data sources.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Excellent analytical, problem-solving, and communication skills.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Ability to lead projects and work collaboratively in a team environment.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">Preferred Qualifications:</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <ul style="margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-top: 0.0cm;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Experience with Azure data services and cloud technologies.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(36,36,36);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Familiarity with other BI tools and platforms.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(33,33,33);background: white;"><span style="font-size: 16.0px;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(36,36,36);">Power BI certification is a plus.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> </ul> </div> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Chicago ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ IL ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Programmer Analyst-Databricks (32636) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 17, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 1W9TFRVJSM ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32636]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Programmer Analyst-Databricks</strong>
    <br> <strong>Location:</strong> Lansing, MI 48933 (Hybrid Role with 2 days onsite from day one)<br> <strong>Client:</strong> Myticas&apos; Direct Client<br> <strong>Work Schedule:</strong> Hybrid (On-site two days per week – Tuesday and Wednesday)<br> <strong>Candidate Requirements:</strong> Candidates MUST be local (within 90 minutes of Lansing). Will need to be onsite starting day 1 for hybrid work schedule of 2 days a week in office. No remote-only option.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Top Skills & Years of Experience:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>6+ years of Development Environment Support for Databricks <li>5+ years of JIRA <li>2+ years of Confluence </ul> <br> <strong>Job Summary:</strong>
    <br> Programmer Analyst 3 as an advanced information technology programmer/analyst and technical resource in the Eligibility Area. <ul> <li>This advanced position provides development environment support, production support, batch jobs support, evaluates possible solutions, develops alternative solutions, recommends technical modifications, and designs, develops, and maintains applications across multiple platforms and experience/understanding of agile processes. <li>This position will be using Databricks/JIRA/Confluence technologies for Eligibility projects and upgrade technologies as needed. <li>This position is also responsible for the development and maintenance of portions of other related processes in the Client Support area that support the Department of Health & Human Services. This may include reports associated with those processes. <li>This role also includes development of documentation in all areas under their own responsibility, navigation, data storage, data retrieval, data validation, data manipulation, printing, and other processes. <li>This position will help in the support of Eligibility projects related to Databricks/JIRA/DevSecOps/Confluence. <li>Relies on experience, judgment and accomplish goals, independently performs a variety of complicated tasks, may lead, a wide degree of creativity and latitude is expected. </ul> <br> <strong>Required Skills/Experience:</strong> <ul> <li>8-11 + years of experience in the field or in a related area. <li>Development Environment Support <li>Databricks <li>JIRA/DevSecOps/Confluence <li>PL/SQL <li>Business Objects/Crystal Reports <li>Oracle Database <li>Bitbucket/Azure DevOps GIT <li>Batch Jobs <li>.Net 4.8 with C# <li>JAVA <li>Development Tools and Upgrade Technologies as needed </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Lansing ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ MI ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Design Verification Specialist (32630) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ W9GXOTXRDC ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32630]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Our client is seeking<strong> </strong>a highly experienced ASIC Verification Engineer to help develop and verify complex digital ASICs in a collaborative, geographically diverse environment.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Key Responsibilities</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Lead the development of verification infrastructure for advanced ASIC designs</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Create System Verilog/UVM-based protocol and traffic generators/checkers</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Develop and execute test plans based on functional and standards requirements</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Define, develop, and run self-checking tests for complex digital ASICs</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Required Qualifications</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Bachelor’s degree in computer science or electrical engineering (master’s preferred)</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">8+ years of experience in ASIC verification</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Proven experience in developing and implementing test plans at block or sub-chip levels</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Proficiency in System Verilog and scripting languages such as Python</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Deep understanding of UVM methodology</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Experience with assertions, functional coverage, code coverage, and formal verification tools</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Strong communication skills and ability to work effectively in a distributed team</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Preferred Skills</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    </span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: rgb(250,250,250);"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="">Knowledge of DSP and/or FEC technologies</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior SAP EWM consultant (32622) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ UKZF6FLIHR ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32622]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is actively seeking a senior <strong>SAP EWM Consultant</strong> to support a long-term transformation engagement for a major utility and energy client. This is a <strong>hybrid role</strong> requiring <strong>50–70% travel to Winnipeg</strong>. Candidates may be based anywhere in Canada but must be flexible with travel as needed.</p> <p>The consultant will play a <strong>key functional leadership role</strong> within the SAP EWM workstream and collaborate closely with stakeholders to design and implement warehouse and logistics solutions using SAP S/4HANA.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead and deliver SAP Extended Warehouse Management (EWM) implementations</p> <li> <p>Configure warehouse structures (e.g., storage types, sections, activity areas)</p> <li> <p>Manage picking and putaway strategies, process/layout-oriented storage control</p> <li> <p>Integrate EWM with related SAP modules (TM, PP, MM, SD)</p> <li> <p>Execute blueprinting, document business requirements, and lead testing cycles</p> <li> <p>Provide expert client-facing communication and presentations</p> <li> <p>Mentor junior consultants and support stakeholder alignment across teams</p> </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5–8+ years of SAP EWM experience with at least 2 full lifecycle implementations</p> <li> <p>Strong hands-on configuration experience with SAP EWM</p> <li> <p>Experience integrating with SAP TM, PP, MM, and SD modules</p> <li> <p>Prior experience leading teams on SAP S/4HANA projects</p> <li> <p>Strong communication and presentation skills</p> <li> <p>Experience delivering solutions in the utility, energy, or related industries is a plus</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with SAP TM is an asset</p> </ul> <p><strong>Additional Information:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Travel to Winnipeg required (50–70%)</p> <li> <p>Candidates must be located in Canada</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Winnipeg ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ MB ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Business Systems Analyst with QA (32632) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ MO1TMTII4I ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32632]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">Myticas direct client is seeking Business Systems Analyst with QA experience at </span>
    </span></span>
    </span><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Waukegan, IL <strong>(Hybrid-3 days onsite)</strong>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Duration: </span>
    </span></strong>
    <strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">5 months</span>
    </span></strong>
    <strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;"> (with a possibility of extension)</span>
    </span></strong>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Description</span>
    </span></span>
    </strong></span>
    </span></span>
    <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">The BSA/QA will play a critical role in bridging the gap between business needs and technology solutions. This individual will work closely with the project team and stakeholders to understand their business requirements and do document them in User Stories to then be developed. The BSA/QA will create test cases for user stories and will execute these tests and clearly documenting results and creating defects where needed.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Key Responsibilities:</span>
    </span></span>
    </strong></span>
    </span></span> <ul> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Collaborate with business stakeholders to gather and document detailed business requirements and functional specifications.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Analyze existing business processes, identify areas for improvement, and evaluate potential solutions to increase efficiency and effectiveness.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Assist in the design and implementation of software solutions that meet the business needs and integrate with existing systems where necessary.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Develop test plans and coordinate testing efforts to ensure that solutions meet business requirements and provide a high level of quality.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Create and maintain comprehensive documentation including process flows, business rules, and user guides.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Work closely with project managers and other team members to ensure timely delivery of project milestones and resolution of any issues that may arise.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Serve as a liaison between the IT department and business units by communicating project status, changes, and potential impacts to stakeholders.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Perform manual testing of software applications to ensure they meet user requirements.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Extensive experience on different types of testing that includes Functional testing, System Integration testing, Regression testing and UAT.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Experience in Agile/Scrum Environments on multiple Projects.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Experience in developing test plans, strategies, and test Scenarios.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Create, execute, and maintain test cases and test scripts. Collaborate with the development team to address and resolve identified issues in a timely manner.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Expertise in using JIRA for writing the Test Cases and tracking the Defects.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Excellent Communication skills-Verbal and written.</span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span>
    </span></span> </ul> <br> <br> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Chicago ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ IL ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ EDW Informatica ETL Developer (32541) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 79D9PNH2S4 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32541]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>EDW Informatica ETL Developer </strong>
    </p> <p><strong>Job Title: </strong>Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) Informatica ETL Developer</p> <p><strong>Duration: </strong>12 months with possible multi-year extension/s</p> <p><strong>Job Summary: </strong>
    </p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is are seeking a highly experienced Informatica Extract Transform Load (ETL) Developer for a large, direct client in Springfield, IL. This opportunity will be an assent to the Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) team.</p> <p>This role is responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining robust ETL processes using Informatica PowerCenter and Teradata. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of data integration, performance tuning, and data warehousing best practices, with a focus on supporting healthcare-related data systems.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities: </strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Design and implement ETL solutions using Informatica PowerCenter to extract, transform, and load data from various agency sources. <li>Automate data staging processes and optimize ETL job scheduling for performance and efficiency. <li>Administer and support ETL environments, including development and production systems. <li>Perform repository backups, recovery operations, and system maintenance. <li>Develop mappings, mapplets, sessions, and workflows using a wide range of Informatica transformations. <li>Monitor and troubleshoot ETL jobs across development, testing, and production environments. <li>Write and optimize complex SQL queries and Unix Shell scripts for data marts and interfaces in Teradata. <li>Collaborate with stakeholders to define requirements, document technical solutions, and support project planning. <li>Participate in unit, integration, and system testing. <li>Provide technical support, mentoring, and guidance to team members. <li>Communicate project status and deliverables to leadership and clients. <li>Continuously learn and apply new technologies to enhance system performance and capabilities. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>7+ years of experience with Informatica PowerCenter and ETL development. <li>5+ years of experience writing complex SQL and performance tuning. <li>5+ years of experience with Teradata (v17+), including Fastload, TPT, and Multiload utilities. <li>5+ years of Informatica PowerCenter administration experience. <li>2+ years of Unix Shell (Bash/Korn) scripting experience. <li>Strong communication, collaboration, and mentoring skills. <li>Bachelor’s or advanced degree in IT, Computer Science, Mathematics, or a related field. <li>Strong organizational and time management skills. 2025 Page 1 of 2 Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) ETL/Informatica Developer </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications: </strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Residing in or near Springfield, IL. <li>5+ years of data warehouse development experience. <li>5+ years of data modeling experience using ERWIN or similar tools. <li>2+ years of experience with Azure Data Factory and Snowflake. <li>Experience with scripting languages such as Python, R, or JavaScript (React). <li>Familiarity with Informatica Data Quality (IDQ), Address Doctor, and Metadata Manager. <li>Experience with Medicaid, Medicare, or healthcare data systems. <li>Experience working in Agile environments. <li>Knowledge of BI and data integration technologies across relational and multidimensional systems. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ hematics ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Oregon ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michelle Corino ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst (32542) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ EXYBNJ6IXR ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32542]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst</strong>
    </p> <p><strong>Duration: </strong>12 months with possible multi-year extension/s</p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is are seeking a highly experienced <strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst </strong>for a large, direct client in Springfield, IL. </p> <p><strong>Primary Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Gathering and analyzing technical information from various sources to be included in the documentation. <li>Planning, writing, and maintaining detailed technical, operational, and process documentation. <li>Leading, developing, and maintaining a library of technical and business documentation source code and reports. <li>Analyze Medicaid program including claims, eligibility, and provider data supporting data warehouse downstream reporting and analytics. <li>Developing and supporting technical training materials. <li>Modifying existing technical documentation for business needs. <li>Participating in and leading technical and business requirements sessions. <li>Meeting with the project team regularly to consolidate project status and reporting. <li>Engaging with the customer as needed to provide updates on technical documentation and project work. <li>Working with the development and QA team to assure each document has been thoroughly reviewed and support process improvements and operational efficiency. <li>Mentoring/Coaching other project team members on effective writing skills and strategies for consistency. <li>Performing additional duties that are typically associated with this position, as assigned. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>5+ years of healthcare business analysis experience supporting business initiatives through data analysis, writing business requirements and user acceptance testing of various systems. <li>5+ years of experience serving as a technical analyst in healthcare (payor). <li>3+ years of experience working specifically with Medicaid programs, MMIS/MES or related systems. <li>3+ years of experience in knowledge management creating, organizing, sharing, and optimizing knowledge within an enterprise organization using tools such as Microsoft 365, AI-enabled search, MS SharePoint/Teams, and JIRA. <li>Proven ability to lead communication (written and verbal) at the customer leadership level. <li>Knowledge of health insurance, HMO, and managed care principles including Medicaid and Medicare regulation. <li>Ability to interpret federal and state Medicaid policy and translate it into business and technical requirements. <li>Effective organizational, analytical, time management, problem-solving, and multi-tasking skills, and habits; ability to complete assignments under tight deadlines with little/no direct supervision. <li>Bachelor’s degree in business, information systems, Public Health, or a related field </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Master’s Degree in related field is preferred. <li>5+ years of experience as a technical analyst in payor healthcare. <li>3+ years of experience writing SQL using large-scale database management tools. <li>3+ years of experience working with State Medicaid and CHIP agencies including federal reporting (CMS 64/21, TMSIS, PERM). Enterprise Data Warehouse - Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst <li>Knowledge of data integration, software enhancements/planning and agile methodologies <li>Experience with using Azure DevOps, SharePoint, MS Project, Visio </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ a supporting data warehouse downstream reporting and analytics.
	Developing and supporting technical training materials.
	Modifying existing technical documentation for business needs.
	Participating in and leading technical and business requirements sessions.
	Meeting with the project team regularly to consolidate project status and reporting.
	Engaging with the customer as needed to provide updates on technical documentation and project work.
	Working with the development and QA team to assure each document has been thoroughly reviewed and support process improvements and operational efficiency.
	Mentoring/Coaching other project team members on effective writing skills and strategies for consistency.
	Performing additional duties that are typically associated with this position ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ as ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dan Sifer ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Technical Support and Customer Service Associate (32581) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 30, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ RDML32E0DT ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32581]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <strong>Technical Support and Customer Service Associate </strong>
    <strong>- REMOTE<br> <br> Contract: 12 months with possible CTH</strong>
    <br> <strong>Schedule: 3rd shift - 12 am to 9 am, Tuesday thru Saturday<br> Work Type: Fully Remote</strong>
    <br> <br> Myticas is actively seeking a <strong>Technical Support and </strong>
    <strong>Customer Service Associate </strong>for a direct client to join their <strong>Personal Support Center (PSC)</strong> team. This role is perfect for someone with a passion for helping others, a knack for troubleshooting, and the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, tech-forward environment.<br> <br> As a PSC Associate, you’ll be the first point of contact for users via phone, email, and chat—working to resolve technical issues, answer questions, and ensure a seamless customer experience. You'll be supported by extensive training, a detailed knowledge base, and a collaborative team ready to help you grow.<br> <br> <strong>What You’ll Do:</strong> <ul> <li>Provide Tier 1 technical support for software, hardware, and connectivity issues <li>Assist with password resets, software installations, VPN setups, and general troubleshooting <li>Escalate complex issues to senior team members when needed <li>Maintain clear, professional communication across all customer interactions <li>Simultaneously manage support requests via phone, email, and chat <li>Accurately log cases using tools like ServiceNow and Zendesk </ul> <strong>What We’re Looking For:</strong> <ul> <li>Strong customer service and communication skills <li>Comfort working in a flexible, 24/7/365 support environment <li>Ability to adapt to new tools, systems, and processes quickly <li>Team player who’s open to ongoing feedback, learning, and development </ul> <strong>Why Join Us:</strong> <ul> <li>Hands-on training and mentoring <li>Access to a robust internal knowledge base <li>Opportunities to collaborate with tech experts and leadership <li>A supportive team environment where growth is encouraged </ul> If you're ready to jump into a dynamic support role where no two days are the same, apply now or reach out to learn more. We’re excited to meet you! ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[  ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michelle Corino ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ IT Plant Manager (32619) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ LAMJZY7KCN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32619]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>IT Plant Manager</strong>
    <br> <strong>Direct hire</strong>
    <br> <strong>Onsite - Orion, MI</strong>
    <br> <br> Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is seeking an <strong>IT Plant Manager</strong> for a large client in Orion, MI. This role is crucial in managing all IT-related activities at the local plant, with key responsibilities encompassing infrastructure, manufacturing software, and business operations. Local candidates are strongly preferred.<br> <br> <strong> Responsibilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Manage daily IT activity at plant level including employee related issues. <li>Assist in budget (cap-ex/allocation) for plant and corporate level. <li>Maintain budget for plant related IT expenses. <li>Provide direct supervision for IT Plant Support Specialist assigned to respective plant. <li>Manages the third-party maintenance for network, hardware, software, and telecommunications services. <li>Participate in budget planning, implementation, and monitoring for purchase and maintenance of hardware and software for the plant <li>Prepare plans for applications, physical infrastructure and the acquisition of the necessary resources to support these items and assure responsiveness of the plans relating to corporate objectives. <li>Manage the installation of hardware and software by others. <li>Manage provisioning of end user workstations/laptops based on corporate standards. <li>Reasonable accommodation may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions. </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>A minimum of six years of experience in an IT Manager role. <li>Bachelor's degree in Information Technology, Computer Science or a related field <li>Six (6) years of experience creating strategic plans <li>A minimum of four (4) years of experience working with cross-functional teams <li>Four (4) years of experience managing a budget <li>A minimum of 4 years of project management experience <li>A minimum of three (3) years of experience training and developing direct reports <li>Six (6) years of organization and planning experience <li>A minimum of six years of experience with the following technical skills: <li>SQL Server database software <li>Microsoft operating systems and Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Access) <li>VMWare <li>PC <li>RF <li>Printing <li>Server <li>Network Storage systems <li>Knowledge of networking <li>Backup technologies to support troubleshooting efforts <li>Industry based IT tools <li>Must be able to regularly lift and/or move up to 30 pounds. </ul> <p><br> <strong>Preferred skills/Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>IT automotive systems <li>ERP such as Plex <li>MES <li>Plant floor applications and networks preferred. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Orion ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Michigan ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michelle Corino ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Hybrid Work-French Legal Invoice Analyst/Initial Reviewer (W-2101) (32444) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ Y6F2WHMRH8 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32444]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Location:</strong> Hybrid Contract Position | Minneapolis, MN<br /> <strong>NOTE: W2 Candidates Only!</strong>
    </p> <p>Myticas's direct client, based in Minneapolis, MN, is seeking a <strong>Legal Invoice Analyst/Initial Reviewer</strong> for a hybrid contract position.</p> <hr /> <h3><strong>Position Overview:</strong>
    </h3> <p>The <strong>Legal Invoice Analyst I</strong> is responsible for the prompt, accurate, and efficient auditing of electronically submitted legal fee and expense invoices from law firms and vendors. The selected candidate will ensure compliance with billing guidelines by adjusting invoice line items that violate provisions and documenting justifications for those adjustments. The analyst will also provide guidance to business unit partners on issues or opportunities within the Legal Billing Audit process.</p> <hr /> <h3><strong>Essential Responsibilities:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Efficiently and accurately review legal invoice entries.</li> <li>Receive legal invoice assignments from the Operations Support Specialist or self-assign tasks from the intake queue.</li> <li>Verify compliance with legal billing guidelines for submitted invoices.</li> <li>Ensure the accuracy of UTBMS task codes (Fee, Activity, and Expense codes) applied to invoice line items.</li> <li>Document reasons for any adjustments made to invoice line items, specifying the violated billing guideline and rationale for the adjustment amount.</li> <li>Forward audited legal invoices through the appropriate review chain as required.</li> <li>Collaborate with Legal Invoice Analysts and Quality Assurance Analysts.</li> <li>Exercise discretion and sound judgment when making audit and adjustment decisions.</li> <li>Demonstrate a strong understanding of legal terminology and claims-related legal situations, with multijurisdictional exposure preferred.</li> <li>Work independently with minimal supervision after training.</li> <li>Utilize electronic legal bill submission and auditing software efficiently.</li> <li>Organize work to ensure the prompt and efficient review of legal invoices within designated timeframes.</li> <li>Apply basic business math skills and maintain appropriate business telephone etiquette.</li> </ul> <hr /> <h3><strong>Required Skills, Qualifications, and Experience:</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Education:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Paralegal Certification or a Bachelor's Degree in a legal-related discipline, or equivalent work experience.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Experience:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>1-3 years of experience in a legal services or legal auditing environment.</li> <li>Must speak, read and write&nbsp;<strong>French</strong>--for this opening.</li> <li>Familiarity with legal billing processes.</li> <li>Strong understanding of federal and/or state rules of civil procedure.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Technical Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook).</li> <li>Experience with legal billing systems and processes.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Core Competencies:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li><strong>Teamwork:</strong> Collaborate effectively with the Legal Billing Audit Center of Excellence (LBACOE) and other business units while providing constructive feedback.</li> <li><strong>Problem Solving:</strong> Think independently and make sound decisions. Identify necessary resources to aid in decision-making and take proactive steps to resolve problems.</li> <li><strong>Leadership:</strong> Demonstrate personal accountability for day-to-day tasks and collaborate with other business units to achieve results.</li> <li><strong>Planning and Organizing:</strong> Prioritize tasks to achieve short- and long-term goals within designated timeframes.</li> <li><strong>Technology:</strong> Partner with technology experts to identify gaps and develop impactful solutions.</li> <li><strong>Learning:</strong> Adapt to changes in the marketplace and workforce by acquiring or modifying knowledge through study, experience, or instruction.</li> <li><strong>Initiative:</strong> Exhibit self-direction and translate ideas into action to achieve results.</li> </ul> INDSponsor ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Hybrid Contract Position | Minneapolis ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Minnesota ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Local to CA, TX, NY, MN, FL, IL-Technical Support Representative(W-14870608) (32583) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 01, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ MSSGCWZNTQ ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32583]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Position Title: Technical Support Representative</strong>
    <br> <strong>Location & Work Arrangement:</strong> Hybrid (2 days onsite per week)</p> <p><strong>Available Locations:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p><strong>California:</strong> Glendale, Sacramento, Torrance</p> <li> <p><strong>Florida:</strong> Tampa</p> <li> <p><strong>Illinois:</strong> Chicago, Riverwoods</p> <li> <p><strong>Minnesota:</strong> Minneapolis</p> <li> <p><strong>New York:</strong> Babylon, Colonie, Monsey, New York City</p> <li> <p><strong>Texas:</strong> Austin, Coppell, Dallas, Houston</p> </ul> <p><strong>Employment Type:</strong> W2 only<br> <strong>Contract Type:</strong> Contract<br> <strong>Note:</strong> Candidates must be local to one of the listed locations. Relocation assistance is not provided.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Position Overview</strong>
    </h3> <p>On behalf of our client, <strong>Wolters Kluwer</strong>, we are seeking a <strong>Technical Support Representative</strong> to deliver high-quality product and platform support. This role combines technical troubleshooting with exceptional customer service to ensure an optimal user experience.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Essential Responsibilities</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Resolve technical issues related to Wolters Kluwer products for both customers and internal employees</p> <li> <p>Manage support cases via multiple channels (phone, email, Salesforce)</p> <li> <p>Handle multiple cases simultaneously while maintaining accurate and detailed documentation</p> <li> <p>Conduct root cause analysis and implement effective problem resolution strategies</p> <li> <p>Provide clear, step-by-step guidance to customers</p> <li> <p>Escalate complex issues to the appropriate technical teams</p> <li> <p>Create and update procedural documentation</p> <li> <p>Support training initiatives and contribute to knowledge sharing</p> <li> <p>Participate in product testing and usability reviews</p> <li> <p>Foster and maintain strong customer relationships</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Qualifications</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Education</strong> (One of the following):</p> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree (preferred: Management Information Systems, Information Technology), or</p> <li> <p>High school diploma/GED with a minimum of 2 years of customer or technical support experience</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Technical Skills</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Proficiency in computer troubleshooting</p> <li> <p>Experience with browser and basic network troubleshooting</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with case management systems (e.g., Salesforce)</p> <li> <p>Basic technical documentation skills</p> <li> <p>Understanding of support center processes and best practices</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Professional Competencies</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills</p> <li> <p>Excellent verbal and written communication abilities</p> <li> <p>High attention to detail</p> <li> <p>Strong time management and multi-tasking capabilities</p> <li> <p>Flexibility and adaptability in a fast-paced environment</p> <li> <p>Strong customer service orientation</p> <li> <p>Ability to collaborate effectively in a team setting</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Work Requirements</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Flexibility to accommodate varying work schedules</p> <li> <p>Ability to manage multiple priorities effectively</p> <li> <p>Commitment to continuous learning and professional development</p> <li> <p>Onsite presence required two days per week</p> <li> <p>Residency in or near one of the listed work locations</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Additional Responsibilities</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Cross-training on various products and systems</p> <li> <p>Assisting in the onboarding and training of new employees</p> <li> <p>Contributing to process improvement initiatives</p> <li> <p>Supporting a collaborative and team-oriented work environment</p> <li> <p>Participating in project-related tasks as assigned</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Success Factors</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Proactive approach to identifying and resolving issues</p> <li> <p>Ability to communicate complex information clearly and effectively</p> <li> <p>Strong case management and organizational skills</p> <li> <p>Dedication to customer satisfaction</p> <li> <p>Adaptability to evolving processes and tools</p> <li> <p>Active participation in team initiatives and knowledge sharing</p> </ul> <hr> <p>This position provides the opportunity to work with a leading provider of professional information services. The role blends technical problem-solving with customer engagement in a dynamic, supportive environment.</p> <p><strong>Note:</strong> Only local candidates able to meet the onsite work requirement (2 days per week) will be considered. Relocation assistance is not available.</p> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ ion Technology) ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Oregon ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Local to MN-Hybrid, Attorney (J.D)(W-4499) (32601) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 10, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 3DSG63VIN8 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32601]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Legal Invoice Review Quality Assurance Analyst II</strong>
    <br> <strong>Location:</strong> Hybrid in St. Cloud, MN or Minneapolis, MN (Must be located in MN; flexible for 2 days per week onsite)<br> <strong>Contract Type:</strong> Hybrid Contract Position<br> <strong>Employment Type:</strong> W2 only<br> <br> <strong>NOTE:</strong> Bilingual (French, German, Italian and/or Spanish) would be a plus, medical malpractice experience would be nice as well.<br> <br> Myticas&apos; direct client, based in St. Cloud, MN or Minneapolis, MN, is seeking a <strong>Legal Invoice Review Quality Assurance Analyst II</strong> (QA Analyst II) for a <strong>hybrid contract position</strong>. This role focuses on <strong>quality assurance testing</strong> within the <strong>Legal Bill Analysis Center of Excellence (LBACOE)</strong>. The ideal candidate will have deep expertise in legal concepts related to invoice auditing across multiple areas of law.</p> <h3><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li><strong>Juris Doctor (JD) degree</strong> from an <strong>ABA-accredited law school</strong> is required. <li>Strong understanding of <strong>legal billing guidelines</strong> and <strong>UTBMS task codes</strong>. <li>Ability to work independently with <strong>minimal supervision</strong> after training. <li>Excellent written communication skills, including <strong>grammar, syntax, style, spelling, and proofreading</strong>. <li>Strong analytical and <strong>problem-solving skills</strong> with attention to detail. <li><strong>Bilingual (French, German, Italian and/or Spanish) would be a plus</strong>, medical malpractice experience would be nice as well </ul> <h3><strong>Job Responsibilities:</strong>
    </h3> <h4><strong>Quality Assurance & Invoice Review:</strong>
    </h4> <ul> <li>Conduct <strong>expert peer reviews</strong> of invoice analysts&apos; work, applying specialized legal knowledge to ensure <strong>accuracy and compliance</strong> with billing guidelines. <li>Assess <strong>legal context and terminology</strong> within invoices and make necessary adjustments to previously modified line-item entries. <li>Document <strong>comprehensive justifications</strong> for adjustments, citing specific <strong>billing guideline violations</strong>. <li>Ensure <strong>accurate classification</strong> of UTBMS task, fee, activity, and expense codes. <li>Use <strong>discretion and legal expertise</strong> to correct both adjusted and non-adjusted invoice line items. </ul> <h4><strong>Appeals & Mediation:</strong>
    </h4> <ul> <li>Serve on the <strong>Appeals Team</strong>, engaging in written communication with law firms to resolve disputes over invoice adjustments. <li>Participate in <strong>legal expert-to-expert discussions</strong> to reach <strong>mutually agreeable resolutions</strong> on disputed invoice adjustments, in alignment with client directives. <li>Handle <strong>escalated appeals mediation</strong>, including drafting <strong>written summaries</strong> for clients and attending <strong>resolution conferences</strong> with law firms, management, and clients. <li>Work professionally with law firms via written communications to resolve disputes while <strong>maintaining integrity</strong> in the legal billing process. </ul> <h4><strong>Collaboration & Process Improvement:</strong>
    </h4> <ul> <li>Support <strong>business unit partners</strong> by identifying process improvements and opportunities within the <strong>Legal Bill Analysis (LBA) process</strong>. <li>Collaborate with <strong>audit and appeals teams</strong> to interpret client guidelines and resolve complex legal invoicing scenarios. <li>Provide feedback to the <strong>CIOX Artificial Intelligence Decision Science team</strong> to improve <strong>machine learning functionality</strong> for invoice auditing. </ul> <h3><strong>Additional Skills & Responsibilities:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Conduct <strong>periodic audits and data analysis</strong> to support performance metrics and reporting. <li>Organize workflow efficiently to <strong>review invoices promptly and accurately</strong>. <li>Communicate effectively in both <strong>oral and written form</strong> to obtain and deliver information. <li>Possess strong <strong>business math skills</strong> and <strong>appropriate telephone communication skills</strong>. <li>Ability to <strong>analyze legal service agreements</strong> and develop effective operational tools. <li>Proficient in <strong>electronic legal billing software</strong> and <strong>Microsoft Office Suite</strong>. <li>Maintain professionalism while working independently with <strong>minimal supervision</strong>. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Hybrid in St. Cloud ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Minnesota ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Sr Program Management Consultant - Medical Devices (32608) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 14, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ DKIUKM0N9M ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32608]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Sr Project Management Consultant </strong>
    <br> <strong>Location:</strong> Waukegan, IL (3 days onsite)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Myticas's direct client based in North Chicago, IL</p> <hr><u><strong>NOTE:</strong>
    </u><br> Need a seasoned, <strong>higher level Program Manager</strong> having experience managing projects related to <strong>medical devices or medical equipment</strong>. That kind of specialized expertise is essential given the technical and regulatory aspects of the EEG brain scan initiative. <br> Will be meeting with VP and Vendors as well as being responsible for budget management. <h3><br> <strong>Summary</strong>
    </h3> <p>One of our Direct clients is looking to add a Seasoned Sr Project/Program Management Consultant to their team. The main project is tied to an EEG brain scan technology and the person needs to have an SDLC background. Experience with medical devices and phase 1 installation would be a great nice-to-have. This individual will be meeting with VP and Vendors as well as being responsible for budget management.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Initiate and Plan Project: Works with business and IT management to establish and gain consensus on project goals, objectives, financials and deliverables. Responsible for building the plan and resources needs to accomplish the scope. <li>Project Control: Assess the degree to which changes to scope, issues and risks will affect the project working with business and IT management and sponsor to gain agreement for resolution. Measure performance to assure the project is progressing as compared to original plan and budget. <li>Executing and Closing Project: Develops and executes a work plan obtaining authorized resources to ensure all activities are performed. Leads team in delivering project scope. Gather lessons learned and obtain final project approval from sponsor and stakeholders. <li>Project Communication: Communicate project progress by producing project reports to provide timely and accurate program status and decision support information to project teams, business, and IT management. Makes recommendations based on current project status to resolve issues and manage risks. <li>Resource and Team Management: Coordinate resources to ensure project needs are addressed and effectively assign tasks and deliverables to team members based upon their abilities. Motivates project team in order to deliver project outcomes. <li>Quality Management: Responsible for compliance with applicable Corporate and functional policies and procedures. <li>Decisions: Make decisions that impact project level activities. Influences or has final decision authority for project budget. <li>Financial Control: Develops and manages a financial plan with multi-million dollar spend. Tracks actual spend, accruals, proactively creates spend estimates on a regular basis (at least monthly) and coordinates estimates and invoices with project vendors, in order to maintain spend at +/- 10% of the overall project budget. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Qualifications</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Bachelor’s degree in business, Information Systems/Computer Science or related discipline. <li>Proven Microsoft Project, PowerPoint, Excel, and Word skills are required. <li>5-10 years of experience in project management <li>Experience managing SDLC projects. <li>Key Stakeholders: <li>Business and Technology resources; varying levels of leadership </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Preferred Qualifications</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>PMP Certification <li>PPM Tool experience <li>Pharmaceutical experience <li>Experience managing projects to deliver or enhance validated systems. </ul> <hr> <p>This is a hybrid position requiring both remote and onsite work in Waukegan, IL.</p> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Waukegan ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Illinois ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Myticas Recruiter ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Security & Controls Solution Designer (IAM) (32364) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ April 14, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 8YU5PLNVGX ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32364]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our Montreal Based client is looking for an experienced <strong>Security & Controls Solution Designer</strong> for a long term Remote contract. The ideal candidate will be responsible for developing and documenting <strong>Identity and Access Management (IAM)</strong> security solutions to ensure alignment between design and operational execution. This role involves creating <strong>Solution Design Documents (SDDs)</strong> covering IAM automation, RBAC, SoX controls, and Segregation of Duties (SoD).</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Develop and maintain detailed <strong>Solution Design Documents (SDDs)</strong> for IAM security implementations <li>Collaborate with security, governance, and project teams to gather and validate technical requirements <li>Align all designs with organizational security policies and ensure proper approvals <li>Support test strategy creation and confirm design compliance throughout the project lifecycle <li>Maintain accurate, consistent, and clear documentation for all IAM solutions </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Strong background in <strong>IAM Security</strong>, with expertise in <strong>SAP</strong>, <strong>Saviynt</strong>, <strong>Active Directory</strong>, and <strong>ServiceNow</strong> <li>Experience with <strong>IAM Automation</strong>, <strong>Role-Based Access Control (RBAC)</strong>, <strong>SoX Controls</strong>, and <strong>Segregation of Duties (SoD)</strong> <li>Excellent <strong>technical writing and documentation skills</strong> <li>Ability to effectively communicate and collaborate with security, architecture, and project stakeholders </ul> <p><strong>Technical Expertise:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>SAP, Saviynt, Active Directory, ServiceNow <li>IAM automation & RBAC frameworks <li>SoX compliance and SoD principles <li>Security solution design best practices </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Montreal ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ High Performance Computing (HPC) Administrator (32447) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ OD63EP2UPR ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32447]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>The HPC Administrator’s primary focus is to monitor, maintain, troubleshoot and support HPC nodes which are integral to the day-to-day operation of our client. These activities include managing the hardware, software installations and configuration, optimization and management of the environment. Other activities include operational, day-to-day requests including migration of nodes, system access requests, resolution of security alerts, and providing second level problem assessment, triage, research, and resolution of incidents and requests, and capable of applying technical expertise at a superior level. Assist with the creation and publication of end user documentation as new technology is released and systems are migrated.</p> <p>Candidates must be willing to be onsite in the office at least 4 days per week.</p> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Identify, diagnose, and resolve level two problems for users of the software and hardware, LAN and WAN, VPN, the Internet, mobile devices, and new computer technology; communicate solutions to end-users. <li>Respond to more complex issues (second line support) escalated by the first line support using problem-solving skills and analysis to identify root causes of issues, determine course of action and propose creative solutions. <li>Manage day-day operations and support of the HPC environment (Linux). <li>Take ownership of capacity, availability and performance of the HPC cluster(s). <li>Support end users in the submission and management of jobs based on Slurm and OpenHPC. <li>Migrate existing nodes as required to Linux. <li>Implement and manage a system based on Foreman or similar to manage patching and oversee cluster management. <li>Implement patches and upgrades to Linux, Slurm and OpenHPC as required. <li>Install new servers and storage, build new clusters, configure and manage Linux distributions, hypervisors (KVM) and tooling. <li>Automate where possible to increase efficiency of operations. <li>Execute upon firewall access requests to the environment. <li>Escalate priority support issues to senior staff and/or other corporate technology groups <li>Collect and document all relevant information prior to escalation to allow senior staff to operate efficiently <li>Document, track and monitor problems to ensure timely resolution. <li>Assist in tracking helpdesk calls pertaining to application, networking, and systems problems and issues. <li>Assign username, password and access right permissions for multiple proprietary applications, as well as client software. <li>Identity Management and multifactor authentication with integration between Active Directory and Linux platforms. <li>Perform hardware & software audits. <li>Product research and evaluation. <li>Provide emergency support on incidents as required. <li>Perform occasional after-hours maintenance. <li>Incident on-call rotation as required. <li>Day-to-day operational support. </ul> <p><strong>Education & Experience Required</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>A Diploma or Degree in a relevant area of study with a preference for Computer Science together with demonstrated operational network-related experience. <li>Minimum of 2 years in Information Technology (with a related University Degree) or minimum of 7 years in Information Technology (with a three-year College Diploma). <li>Industry certifications such as MCSE, CISSP are a strong asset. </ul> <p><strong>Specialized Skills, Knowledge & Abilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>In-depth and demonstrated experience in the installation and operation of Linux platforms in an Enterprise environment (Ubuntu/RedHat). <li>Experience in the use of KVM or other hypervisors. <li>Experience in HPC tools such as Slurm, LSF or GridEngine. <li>Demonstrated knowledge of HPC clusters and use cases. <li>Working technical knowledge of network systems. <li>Working technical knowledge of current systems software, protocols and standards including Active Directory. <li>Identity management using Microsoft Identity Manager and Azure AD Connect. <li>Solid understanding of the Windows based endpoints. <li>Solid scripting experience (e.g. Bash) <li>Excellent written and oral communication skills. <li>Excellent problem-solving skills. <li>Strong analytical and troubleshooting skills <li>Strong interpersonal and organizational skills. <li>Must be well organized and able to grasp system concepts and communicate their applications. <li>Must be capable of quickly learning new systems and associated software applications for proficient execution of tasks. <li>Ability to manage multiple demands with time related constraints in a fast-paced environment. <li>Prioritize and schedule work as necessary to maintain department standards and service level agreements <li>Ability to speak effectively before groups of internal employees, communicate technical information, create and deliver presentations and information sessions to both technical and nontechnical personnel. <li>Demonstrated experience in applying technical expertise and in-depth evaluation to solve complex problems in own area of expertise. <li>Ability to create and maintain documentation and training materials, including KB articles, for technical staff and end-user audiences. <li>Microsoft Windows experience is an asset. <li>Bilingualism (English/French) is an asset. </ul> <p><strong>Decision Making & Supervision</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Make decisions and recommendations within established procedures, based on troubleshooting and analysis. <li>Manage operating system and tooling upgrades. <li>Coordination with helpdesk, network/telecom, platform, and security teams. <li>Work under minimum supervision. </ul> <p><strong>Working Conditions</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Generally comfortable working conditions with lifting and onsite installations. <li>Moderate visual concentration in use of video display terminal. <li>Appropriate security clearances required. <li>Occasional off-hours support may be required. <li>Participation in group pager rotation (‘on call’). </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Onsite ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ NMS Developer (32446) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ YDF3PV1BAE ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32446]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>As a Network Management System Developer, you’ll be responsible for ensuring the smooth operation of our network by designing, implementing, testing and maintaining Operational Support Systems (OSS). Your role will be instrumental in optimizing network performance, enhancing efficiency, and ensuring a seamless customer experience.</p> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Design network management solutions to monitor and manage Carrier <li>Ethernet and IP services, ensuring optimal capacity, performance and reliability <li>Define configurations and notification data models using YANG <li>Define real-time network monitoring solutions <li>Program network automation with gNMI/gNOI/NETCONF/RESTCONF <li>Design, Develop and maintain automated scripts and tools to verify NMS functionality <li>Work with vendors to implement new OSS/NMS solutions <li>Review and approve design documents, test strategies, plans, and scripts <li>Maintain accurate documentation of OSS/NMS requirements, configurations, processes, and procedures <li>Resolve complex OSS/NMS implementation and network problems with cross-functional teams <li>Enforce security best practices to protect network systems and data integrity </ul> <p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Bachelor’s in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field <li>2-5 experience in a similar role. <li>Proficient in Layer 2/3 protocols, YANG modeling, gRPC/gNMI/gNOI <li>Experience designing network management systems using Layer 2/3 protocols <li>Programming skills in modern C++, GNU C, Go, Python 3.x <li>TDD and BDD test frameworks <li>Knowledge of developing software in container hosted in <strong>Linux </strong>environment and microservices <li>Knowledge of Protobuf, XML, JSON IETF encoding, and template language (Jinja2) <li>Good problem-solving, and communication skills <li>Experience with NMS products like Netcracker Digital OSS, ONAP, Ciena Blue Planet, Amdocs </ul> <p><strong>Knowledge in Protocols and Standards:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Layer 3 protocols: IP, OSPF, BGP, MPLS, SR-MPLS <li>Layer 2 protocols: Ethernet, VLAN, STP, LACP <li>MEF and TMF Standards </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Onsite ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Software Developer - Network Management System (32445) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 13, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ Z4PTDOQ8TN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32445]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>As a Network Management System Developer, you’ll be responsible for ensuring the smooth operation of our network by designing, implementing, testing and maintaining Operational Support Systems (OSS). Your role will be instrumental in optimizing network performance, enhancing efficiency, and ensuring a seamless customer experience.</p> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Design network management solutions to monitor and manage Carrier <li>Ethernet and IP services, ensuring optimal capacity, performance and reliability <li>Define configurations and notification data models using YANG <li>Define real-time network monitoring solutions <li>Program network automation with gNMI/gNOI/NETCONF/RESTCONF <li>Design, Develop and maintain automated scripts and tools to verify NMS functionality <li>Work with vendors to implement new OSS/NMS solutions <li>Review and approve design documents, test strategies, plans, and scripts <li>Maintain accurate documentation of OSS/NMS requirements, configurations, processes, and procedures <li>Resolve complex OSS/NMS implementation and network problems with cross-functional teams <li>Enforce security best practices to protect network systems and data integrity </ul> <p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Bachelor’s in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field <li>2-5 experience in a similar role. <li>Proficient in Layer 2/3 protocols, YANG modeling, gRPC/gNMI/gNOI <li>Experience designing network management systems using Layer 2/3 protocols <li>Programming skills in modern C++, GNU C, Go, Python 3.x <li>TDD and BDD test frameworks <li>Knowledge of developing software in container hosted in <strong>Linux </strong>environment and microservices <li>Knowledge of Protobuf, XML, JSON IETF encoding, and template language (Jinja2) <li>Good problem-solving, and communication skills <li>Experience with NMS products like Netcracker Digital OSS, ONAP, Ciena Blue Planet, Amdocs </ul> <p><strong>Knowledge in Protocols and Standards:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Layer 3 protocols: IP, OSPF, BGP, MPLS, SR-MPLS <li>Layer 2 protocols: Ethernet, VLAN, STP, LACP <li>MEF and TMF Standards </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Organizational Change Management Consultant – Bilingual (French/English) (32523) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 09, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ XIO3557NK1 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32523]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Description:</strong>
    <br> Our client is seeking a Senior-level Organizational Change Management (OCM) Consultant to support a post-acquisition workforce integration project<strong> ON-SITE in Montreal. </strong>The consultant will lead change initiatives focused on people transitions (not technology), partnering closely with leadership and cross-functional teams.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Develop and execute change management and communication plans.</p> <li> <p>Lead stakeholder engagement, organizational design, training, and workforce transition activities.</p> <li> <p>Collaborate with leadership to guide workforce integration across business functions.</p> <li> <p>Support organizational design and HR transformation efforts.</p> <li> <p>Manage multiple stakeholders and ensure strong change adoption.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Required Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5+ years of OCM consulting or advisory experience.</p> <li> <p>Strong experience with: change management, stakeholder engagement, communications, organizational design, workforce strategies, HR transformation.</p> <li> <p>Excellent communication skills (verbal & written) in both French and English.</p> <li> <p>Strong project leadership, adaptability, and problem-solving capabilities.</p> <li> <p>Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Business, HR, Psychology or related fields.</p> <li> <p>Previous consulting (Big 4 or advisory firm) experience is an asset.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Additional Notes:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Must be available to work onsite; no remote option.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Montreal ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Project Manager (Bilingual – Remote with Some Travel) (32531) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 11, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ T5HTGZ7KN8 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32531]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Job Title:</strong> Senior Project Manager (Bilingual – Remote with Some Travel)<br> <strong>Client:</strong> National HR & Benefits Services Provider</span>
    </span><br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Term:</strong> 6-Month Contract + Extension<br> <strong>Location:</strong> Remote – Ontario/Quebec(occasional travel to Montrea,, QC<br> <strong>Start:</strong> ASAP</span>
    </span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Overview:</strong>
    <br> Our client, a leading provider of employee-focused business services, is seeking a <strong>Senior Project Manager</strong> to lead <strong>business integration efforts</strong> across their internal operations teams. Reporting to the VP of Finance, this role will help streamline processes across Finance, HR, and Technology functions. It is best suited for a bilingual PM with <strong>strong stakeholder management</strong> and experience supporting <strong>organizational consolidation or cross-functional business alignment.</strong>
    </span></span>
    <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Must-Haves:</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">8+ years’ experience in project management</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">Demonstrated success in managing business integration initiatives (Specifically: Post M&A (Mergers & Acquisitions / Organizational Consolidations) Experience)</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">Excellent communication and stakeholder engagement skills</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">Fully bilingual (English and French)</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">Background in group benefits, HR services, or financial operations is a strong asset</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">Familiarity with <strong>Workday</strong> is a definite plus or like ERP (I.e. Oracle, SAP etc..)</span>
    </span> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dominic Scaletta ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ FPGA Developer, Senior (32549) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 17, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 014QZNQURY ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32549]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Overview:</strong>
    <br /> A leading provider of real-time video processing technology is seeking a <strong>Senior FPGA Developer</strong> to join its core signal processing team. This group is responsible for developing high-performance media transport and processing systems used by global clients in live production, broadcast, and media environments.</p> <p>This is an opportunity to work on cutting-edge, high-bandwidth systems built on advanced FPGA platforms—delivering critical real-time features that enable professional-grade media production. You’ll be surrounded by a highly experienced team that values innovation, collaboration, and practical problem solving.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Design and implement RTL for advanced real-time media systems with interfaces including memory, PCIe, and hardware-accelerated video processing.</p> </li> <li> <p>Develop transport protocol implementations (e.g., SDI, SMPTE 2110) within FPGAs.</p> </li> <li> <p>Collaborate on system architecture—reviewing schematics, optimizing clocking, thermal considerations, and FPGA resource allocation.</p> </li> <li> <p>Perform full IO ring designs for leading FPGA families (e.g., Arria10, Stratix-10, Ultrascale+, Agilex).</p> </li> <li> <p>Define and document high-level system requirements; support component selection and scheduling.</p> </li> <li> <p>Create simulation testbenches (Verilog/SystemVerilog); perform functional verification and debugging.</p> </li> <li> <p>Collaborate cross-functionally with software, hardware, and manufacturing teams through the full product lifecycle.</p> </li> <li> <p>Mentor peers and support technical knowledge sharing within the team.</p> </li> </ul> <p><strong>Requirements:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5+ years of hands-on FPGA design experience, preferably with exposure to video or audio systems.</p> </li> <li> <p>Strong Verilog/SystemVerilog and scripting skills (TCL).</p> </li> <li> <p>Experience with Intel and/or Xilinx FPGAs and their respective toolchains (Quartus, Vivado).</p> </li> <li> <p>Familiarity with high-speed serial interfaces, DDR3/4, HBM, PLLs, and signal integrity principles.</p> </li> <li> <p>Excellent debugging and validation skills; proficiency with lab tools (oscilloscopes, logic analyzers, WFMs, etc.).</p> </li> <li> <p>Background in embedded systems (Linux, bash, C/C++) considered a plus.</p> </li> <li> <p>Understanding of media production workflows and digital video standards (SMPTE, HDR, SDI) is advantageous.</p> </li> <li> <p>Ability to work independently and collaboratively in a fast-paced engineering environment.</p> </li> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[  ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michael Theodossiou ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ IT Director (PMO - Project Management Office) - THREE DAYS ONSITE (32554) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 9LGE6TAUGS ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32554]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Director, IT (PMO)<br> <strong>Location:</strong> Ottawa – Hybrid (3 Days On-Site, Mandatory and Non-Negotiable)<br> <strong>Type:</strong> Full-Time, Permanent (8-Hour Workday)<br> <strong>Language Requirement:</strong> Bilingual Preferred (French/English)<br> <strong>Security Clearance:</strong> Must obtain clearance equivalent to Enhanced Reliability Status (Canada)<br> <strong>Eligibility:</strong> Must be a Canadian Citizen or Permanent Resident</p> <hr> <h3><strong>About the Role</strong>
    </h3> <p>The Director of IT (PMO) is a strategic leadership position responsible for aligning IT initiatives with enterprise objectives and ensuring the successful delivery of high-impact technology projects. The Director will provide expert guidance, foster cross-functional collaboration, and oversee a portfolio of projects that deliver long-term organizational value.</p> <p>This role will lead the development and enforcement of a consistent IT project management framework, ensuring compliance with standardized methodologies and governance practices. The Director will also provide senior leadership with timely insights into project health, risk exposure, and emerging opportunities across the portfolio.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Strategic Portfolio Oversight</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Drive the evolution and adoption of the IT PMO framework to ensure alignment with organizational goals.</p> <li> <p>Manage the enterprise-wide IT project portfolio, prioritizing initiatives and optimizing resource allocation.</p> <li> <p>Advise executive stakeholders using data-driven insights to support strategic investment and resource planning.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Project Leadership and Governance</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead and mentor project managers and support staff to promote high performance and accountability.</p> <li> <p>Establish and enforce governance standards across all projects.</p> <li> <p>Proactively identify and manage risks, implementing mitigation strategies to ensure successful delivery.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Executive Collaboration</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Engage regularly with senior leadership to align on digital strategy, planning, and delivery progress.</p> <li> <p>Prepare and deliver executive-level reports and presentations that support informed decision-making.</p> <li> <p>Handle sensitive and confidential project data with integrity and discretion.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Risk Management</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Identify risks across individual projects and the broader portfolio, escalating critical issues as required.</p> <li> <p>Develop and implement contingency plans to ensure project continuity.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Process Optimization and Continuous Improvement</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Analyze project outcomes to identify areas for improvement and incorporate lessons learned.</p> <li> <p>Promote the use of modern tools and delivery methodologies, including Agile and hybrid approaches.</p> <li> <p>Continuously refine PMO structures and practices to enhance organizational effectiveness.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Reporting and Metrics</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Define and track key performance indicators (KPIs) for project and portfolio success.</p> <li> <p>Provide concise, data-driven reports and dashboards to executive stakeholders.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Project Execution</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead the end-to-end delivery of complex, high-impact IT projects, ensuring they are completed on time, within budget, and with strong stakeholder engagement.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Qualifications and Experience</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Education</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Post-secondary degree or diploma in Business Administration, Computer Science, Information Technology, or a related field.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Experience</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum of 8 years of progressive experience in IT project management.</p> <li> <p>At least 2 years in a leadership role managing a PMO or IT project portfolio.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Certifications</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Project Management Professional (PMP) certification is required.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Key Skills</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Demonstrated experience leading enterprise-wide IT projects and managing PMO teams.</p> <li> <p>Proven ability to work with C-suite executives and handle confidential information.</p> <li> <p>In-depth knowledge of project management methodologies, including Waterfall, Agile, and hybrid models.</p> <li> <p>Proficiency in tools such as Microsoft Project, Jira, and Smartsheet.</p> <li> <p>Strong interpersonal, analytical, and organizational skills.</p> <li> <p>Ability to manage multiple projects and competing priorities in a fast-paced environment.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Amanda Messina ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ SAP EWM Consultant (x2) (32555) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ WJ9EM7F6ET ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32555]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our client, a global organization, is seeking two experienced&nbsp;<strong>SAP EWM Consultants</strong>&nbsp;for upcoming contract engagements. The successful candidates will support a hybrid work environment in the Greater Toronto Area and bring strong functional and technical expertise in Extended Warehouse Management.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Deliver end-to-end SAP EWM solutions across inbound, outbound, and internal warehouse processes</p> </li> <li> <p>Configure and integrate SAP EWM with SAP TM or third-party TMS</p> </li> <li> <p>Support integration with production (Advanced Production Integration), SD, and MM modules</p> </li> <li> <p>Develop and maintain warehouse structures (e.g., Storage Types, Activity Areas)</p> </li> <li> <p>Configure RF transactions and support associated development</p> </li> <li> <p>Assist with S/4HANA plant configuration and go-live readiness</p> </li> </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum 10 years of hands-on SAP EWM consulting experience</p> </li> <li> <p>Proven track record on multiple full-cycle SAP EWM implementations</p> </li> <li> <p>Deep functional knowledge across core EWM processes</p> </li> <li> <p>Strong integration experience with SAP TM, SD, MM, and production modules</p> </li> <li> <p>Experience with S/4HANA is a strong asset</p> </li> <li> <p>Prior consulting experience with large, complex environments is preferred</p> </li> </ul> <p><strong>Work Model:</strong>&nbsp;Hybrid – candidates must be able to attend onsite meetings in the GTA up to 3 times per week, as needed.</p> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Toronto ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Optical Resident Engineer (32419) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 05, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ D9SPTN4BKN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32419]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title: Optical Resident Engineer</strong>
    <br> <strong>Primary Location: Charlotte, NC</strong>
    <br> <em>Other Considered Locations: Columbus, OH; Tampa, FL; Austin, TX; Cerritos, CA</em>
    <br> <em>Note: Please indicate your desired work location at the top of your resume upon submission.</em>
    </p> <h3><strong>Job Summary</strong>
    </h3> <p>We are seeking an experienced <strong>Optical Resident Engineer</strong> to work on-site at a customer location. While Charlotte, NC is the preferred location, candidates located near Columbus, OH; Tampa, FL; Austin, TX; or Cerritos, CA will also be considered. Periodic travel to Dallas, TX will be required. All business travel must receive prior written managerial approval, which must accompany receipt submissions via Fieldglass.</p> <h3><strong>Key Requirements</strong>
    </h3> <p>Candidates <strong>must</strong> meet the following requirements, be able to clearly discuss relevant experience during a technical interview, and ensure such experience is reflected in the resume:</p> <ul> <li>10+ years of experience with a telecom equipment vendor or service provider, specifically configuring, monitoring, and troubleshooting Long Haul (LH) and Metro Optical DWDM networks. <li>7+ years of hands-on experience using optical design tools for generating design packages, managing optical power budgets, and applying knowledge of various amplifier types. <li>7+ years of experience with optical network management systems, particularly <strong>NFM-T</strong>. <li>Experience in IP networking. <li>Practical experience with the implementation of <strong>GMPLS</strong> and <strong>CDC</strong> technologies in DWDM networks is preferred. <li>Product knowledge preferred: <strong>1830 PSS, 1350 OMS (WS-NOC), EPT, and CPB tools</strong>. <li>Strong verbal and written communication skills with clients. </ul> <h3><strong>Role Responsibilities</strong>
    </h3> <p>The Optical Resident Engineer will serve in a consultative capacity, working closely with customers and internal teams across network strategy, design, implementation, and support activities. Key responsibilities include:</p> <ul> <li>Developing network architectures and service designs aligned with customer requirements and industry best practices. <li>Producing network implementation and migration plans. <li>Configuring optical equipment and services. <li>Supporting and testing networks during all stages of deployment. <li>Conducting audits and assessments to ensure network compliance with customer expectations. <li>Formulating and implementing network management strategies. <li>Preparing and reviewing technical statements of work. <li>Creating and delivering customer training materials. <li>Evaluating network performance, scalability, manageability, and security. <li>Recommending strategies for network performance optimization. <li>Collaborating with internal teams to drive product enhancements. <li>Conducting network and customer readiness testing. <li>Building and maintaining strong relationships with both technical and management stakeholders. <li>Supporting critical network events during scheduled maintenance windows, which may require work during off-hours. </ul> <h3><strong>Qualifications</strong>
    </h3> <p><strong>Education:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or a related field; equivalent work experience will also be considered.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Experience:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>10+ years of hands-on experience in optical DWDM network engineering. <li>7+ years of experience in optical design and network management. <li>Familiarity with 1830 PSS, 1350 OMS, EPT, and CPB tools. <li>Experience with GMPLS and CDC technologies is a plus. <li>Proven ability to communicate complex technical information to clients effectively. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Charlotte ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ NC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Full Stack Developer (.NET 8 / Angular 17) (32481) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 26, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ E37W35ISQO ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32481]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Senior Full Stack Developer<br> <strong>Location:</strong> Remote / Ontario, Canada</p> <p><strong>Must-Have Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or a related field</p> <li> <p>Minimum of 5 years of experience in front-end development using frameworks such as React.js or Angular (preferably Angular 17)</p> <li> <p>Minimum of 5 years of experience in back-end software development using C# and .NET (preferably .NET 8)</p> <li> <p>Strong proficiency in working with SQL and NoSQL databases</p> <li> <p>Hands-on experience with Microsoft Azure services, including App Services, Functions, Logic Apps, Service Bus, Cosmos DB, Azure SQL, and Key Vault</p> <li> <p>Solid understanding of object-oriented programming (OOP) principles</p> <li> <p>Proficiency with Azure DevOps, Git repositories, CI/CD pipelines, and deployment automation</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with generative AI and/or machine learning tools such as GitHub Copilot, Cursor, or AI agents</p> </ul> <p><strong>Nice-to-Have Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Experience developing web applications using .NET Core</p> <li> <p>Knowledge of cross-platform development frameworks</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with the ABP Framework (ABP.io)</p> <li> <p>Experience with containerization tools such as Docker and orchestration platforms like Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</p> <li> <p>Understanding of Agile methodologies, particularly Scrum</p> <li> <p>Strong analytical, communication, and collaboration skills</p> <li> <p>Microsoft certifications, such as Azure Developer Associate</p> <li> <p>Development experience in other cloud environments, such as AWS or Google Cloud Platform (GCP)</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Toronto ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michael Theodossiou ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ D365 Finance Configuration Consultant (32537) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 12, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 9011VGYCHF ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32537]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our client is in the build stage of a D365 Finance & Operations and Commerce implementation for a retail organization based in New Brunswick. The go-live is targeted for August 2026.</p> <p><strong>Role Overview:</strong>
    <br> We are seeking an experienced <strong>Finance Configuration Consultant</strong> with deep expertise in <strong>Microsoft D365 F&O</strong>. The ideal candidate will lead client-facing design sessions, provide hands-on system configuration, and support testing initiatives across the Finance workstreams.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Facilitate and lead finance-related design workshops</p> <li> <p>Configure the D365 F&O system to meet business requirements</p> <li> <p>Support client-side testing and validation activities</p> <li> <p>Collaborate with business stakeholders and technical teams</p> <li> <p>Provide input and expertise on best practices for D365 Finance implementations</p> </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum 10 years of experience in Microsoft D365 Finance</p> <li> <p>Hands-on configuration experience across core finance modules</p> <li> <p>Strong communication and client engagement skills</p> <li> <p>Microsoft certification in D365 Finance (asset)</p> <li> <p>Experience in retail or public sector projects (asset)</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ NB ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ IP Network Architect (32569) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 24, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ LAVOQUNQR5 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32569]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">The Senior IP Network Architect is a Subject Matter Expert (SME) on all aspects of the Network design and works with internal teams and external contractors to ensure designs, implementation decisions, validation plans and documentation reflect the business requirements and objectives of the program.</span>
    </span><br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><strong>Networking</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Lead the design of complex IP network architectures, considering business requirements, scalability, and performance.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Possess a strong command of network platforms and appliances, including routers, switches, firewalls, SDWAN controllers, IPSEC VPN gateways, and deep packet inspection tools.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">In coordination with the Network and System Engineering teams attend, contribute and produce materials for internal and external design and system engineering reviews for Network Engineering related activities.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Prepare and deliver materials including presentations, reference documentation and test strategies for network equipment deployment and operation.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Develop and oversee plans including product idea investigations, proof of concept, service validation and product demonstrations in lab.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Maintain a deep understanding of industry standards and protocols related to segment routing, such as IS-IS, OSPF, BGP, and MPLS.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Maintain familiarity with transport network technologies including Segment Routing (SR-MPLS) and Software Defined Networking (SDN).</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Assess, evaluate, and recommend network platforms and appliances, hardware, and software solutions to meet business requirements.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Represent the Network Engineering team by documenting and delivering network requirements to hardware and software development teams specifically in the areas of customer facing MEF 3.0 interface and networking design support requirements.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><strong>Security and Compliance</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Security and Compliance:</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Design and implement secure network solutions with a focus on firewall configurations, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection techniques.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Ensure compliance with industry standards and best practices for network security.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Optimization and Performance:</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Continuously monitor network performance, analyzing metrics and conducting assessments to identify bottlenecks, vulnerabilities, and areas for improvement. Develop strategies to optimize network performance, enhance security, and ensure high availability.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Collaborate with cross-functional teams to enhance network performance and reliability.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Experience with network automation and scripting using tools such as Python, Ansible, or similar.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Emerging Technologies:</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Stay current with industry trends, emerging technologies, and best practices related to IP networking and network appliances.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Proactively recommend and lead the adoption of new technologies that align with business goals.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><strong>Vendor Management</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Collaborate with vendors to evaluate products, negotiate contracts, and ensure the successful deployment and operation of network appliances.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Technical Leadership:</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Provide mentorship and guidance to junior network engineers, sharing your expertise and promoting professional growth.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Troubleshooting and Support:</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Lead in-depth troubleshooting and root cause analysis of network issues, providing timely and effective resolutions.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><strong>Education & Experience</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Bachelor&apos;s degree in computer science, Information Technology, or a related field or equivalent work experience.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">10+ years of progressive experience in designing and architecting IP networks, with a focus on routing, firewalls, SDWAN, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Understanding of Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) standards and objectives as they relate to Carrier Ethernet Services.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Professional certifications such as CCIE, CCNP, CISSP or equivalent are highly desirable.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Expertise in network appliance evaluation, selection, and integration.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">In-depth understanding of security principles and practices as they relate to network architecture.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Proven experience with network troubleshooting, performance optimization, and security enhancement.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Strong knowledge of industry-leading routing protocols, firewall technologies, SDWAN solutions, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection methods.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Experience with network automation and scripting using tools such as Python, Ansible, or similar.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Leadership experience and the ability to mentor junior team members.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Excellent communication (verbal, written, presentation) and interpersonal skills.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Comfortable leading meetings and able to communicate issues and trends to senior management and other groups at the appropriate level of detail.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Communicates well with own team and across organizational boundaries to ensure the successful completion of shared goals.</span>
    </span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><strong>Working Conditions</strong>
    </span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Working conditions are generally comfortable typical of an office environment with occasional work within Data Centres.</span>
    </span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 8.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Occasional international travel is anticipated.</span>
    </span> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Onsite ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior Packet Processing Software Developer (32079) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ December 17, 2024 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 405BPVPK1I ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32079]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>We are seeking a highly skilled <strong>Senior Software Engineer</strong> with expertise in <strong>Packet Processing</strong> to join our team. The ideal candidate will have extensive experience in designing and optimizing high-performance network systems, with a strong background in developing scalable, low-latency solutions for data-intensive environments. In this role, you will work on cutting-edge technologies to enhance network protocols and packet processing frameworks. Your contributions will play a key role in delivering robust, reliable, and efficient network operations, ensuring our systems meet the evolving demands of modern infrastructure.</p> <hr> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Collaborate with experienced engineers in the design, coding, testing, and maintenance of software applications. <li>Develop and maintain embedded software modules using programming languages such as <strong>C++</strong> and <strong>Python</strong>. <li>Design and implement high-performance packet processing applications using <strong>DPDK</strong> and similar frameworks. <li>Optimize network functions for maximum throughput and minimal latency. <li>Develop and maintain packet processing pipelines for various network functions. <li>Troubleshoot complex performance issues in packet processing applications. <li>Assist in the implementation of networking solutions to ensure seamless communication between software components. <li>Contribute to the development of software tools, libraries, and frameworks to enhance overall product quality and efficiency. <li>Participate in code reviews and provide constructive feedback to improve code quality and adherence to coding standards. <li>Collaborate with the team to troubleshoot and resolve software defects and technical issues. <li>Support the integration of software components on <strong>Linux</strong> operating systems. <li>Assist in the testing and validation of software features to ensure functionality and performance meet specified requirements. <li>Utilize cloud technologies to enhance software deployment and management. <li>Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including product managers and designers, to understand requirements and contribute to technical discussions. <li>Maintain clear and organized documentation of software designs, processes, and development tasks. <li>Demonstrate effective teamwork and communication skills, both orally and in writing. <li>Lead the design, development, and implementation of advanced satellite ground segment software systems, ensuring high performance, scalability, and reliability. </ul> <hr> <p><strong>Education & Experience Required:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Bachelor&apos;s or Master&apos;s degree in <strong>Computer Science</strong>, <strong>Computer Engineering</strong>, <strong>Electrical Engineering</strong>, or a related field. <li>In-depth knowledge of <strong>packet processing development</strong>. <li>Experience with the <strong>Vector Packet Processing (VPP)</strong> framework is a plus. <li>Deep understanding of <strong>DPDK architecture and APIs</strong>. <li>Familiarity with modern <strong>NIC features</strong> (e.g., RSS, checksum offload, scatter-gather). <li>Experience with <strong>AF_XDP</strong> or similar kernel bypass technologies. <li>Strong understanding of <strong>Linux-based network stacks</strong>, kernel modules, and performance optimization. <li>Ideally <strong>8+ years</strong> of experience in <strong>C/C++</strong> for low-level network programming and high-performance packet processing. <li>Solid understanding of networking concepts and protocols, including <strong>TCP/IP</strong>, <strong>UDP</strong>, <strong>VXLAN</strong>, <strong>GRE</strong>, etc. <li>Familiarity with cloud technologies is a plus. <li>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills. <li>Ability to collaborate effectively within a diverse team. <li>Excellent oral and written communication skills. <li>Enthusiasm for learning new technologies and tools. <li>Detail-oriented with a commitment to producing high-quality software. <li>Ability to design software with consideration for hardware resource constraints. <li>Experience in <strong>software development</strong> for <strong>satellite communication systems</strong> is a plus. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Cloud Operations Manager (Senior Lead, Operations) (32293) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ March 19, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ YB88D7GLX1 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32293]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>SCOPE</strong>
    </p> <p>We are seeking a highly skilled and motivated Manager, Cloud Operations to lead and optimize our Azure cloud infrastructure and services. This role is critical in ensuring the scalability, reliability, and security of our cloud environments while driving operational excellence. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of cloud architectures, automation, and best-in-class operational practices.</p> <p><strong>RESPONSIBILITIES</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Lead the Cloud Operations team to ensure high availability, performance, and security of cloud-based applications and services. <li>Develop and execute a strategic roadmap for cloud operations, aligning with business objectives. <li>Oversee incident management, disaster recovery, and business continuity strategies for cloud environments to support and align efforts to meet customer needs. <li>Drive automation and infrastructure-as-code (IaC) adoption to improve efficiency and reduce operational overhead. <li>Optimize cloud cost management and governance to ensure cost-effective usage of resources. <li>Collaborate with security, compliance, and IT teams to enforce best practices and regulatory requirements. <li>Establish and monitor KPIs, SLAs, and performance metrics to continuously improve service delivery. <li>Provide leadership, mentorship, and development opportunities for a team of cloud engineers and operations professionals. <li>Communicate proactively with customers and internal team members to deliver business value as a part of daily work management. <li>Stay up to date with emerging technologies, trends, and industry best practices to drive innovation. </ul> <p><strong>REQUIRED TECHNICAL SKILLS & QUALIFICATIONS</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Bachelor&apos;s or Master&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Information Technology, or a related field. <li>Certifications in cloud technologies. <li>Industry-accepted certifications in management. <li>Domain knowledge of banking and financial institutions and/or large enterprise IT environment is desirable. <li>10+ years of experience in IT operations with at least 5 years focused on cloud services. <li>Proven experience in managing cloud environments (AWS or Azure) at an enterprise scale. <li>Strong understanding of automation tools (Terraform, Ansible, CloudFormation) and CI/CD pipelines. <li>Hands-on experience with monitoring, logging, and observability tools (Datadog, Splunk, Prometheus, Azure Monitoring, etc.). <li>Deep knowledge of networking, security best practices, and compliance frameworks (ISO, SOC2, NIST, etc.). <li>Strong leadership and team management skills with experience in developing high-performing teams. <li>Excellent problem-solving skills with a proactive approach to operational challenges. <li>Strong communication and stakeholder management skills. </ul> <p><strong>SOFT SKILLS</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Customer-facing skills: Connect, Engage, Listen, Explain, Facilitate, Coordinate, Follow-through. <li>Strong, clear, and concise written and verbal communication skills. <li>Ability to communicate effectively at all levels of the organization. <li>Strong interpersonal skills and ability to foster team collaboration. <li>Ability to negotiate and convince. <li>Ability to identify innovative solutions to problems. <li>Out-of-the-box thinking approach. <li>Ability to conceptualize and articulate new approaches and solutions. <li>Ability to collaborate and communicate to achieve positive outcomes. <li>Detail-oriented. <li>Strong ability to prioritize and meet deadlines. <li>Able to work under stress and conflicting timelines when necessary. <li>Proactive with a strong desire to learn. <li>Self-driven, with high enthusiasm and ambition to succeed. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dominic Scaletta ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior  Software Technical Support Specialist (32305) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ March 24, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ KCY8U21691 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32305]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>The Senior SoftwareTechnical Support Specialist will provide expert-level technical assistance and strategic support the customers, partners, and cross-functional teams. This role involves complex issue resolution, leadership in support process improvement, ownership of professional service projects focused on product customization and integrations, deploying software solutions, onboarding new customers, and proactive engagement in optimizing team tools, processes, and customer issues. This individual will drive support initiatives, lead escalations, and act as a liaison with the engineering team to implement solutions resolving customer-reported bugs and issues.</p> <p><strong>Requirements</strong>
    </p> <p><strong>Essential Functions</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Lead and Resolve Advanced Technical Issues: Provide exceptional, senior-level support by diagnosing and resolving complex technical issues for customers, partners, and sales engineers, demonstrating technical leadership and initiative. <li>Deployment and Customer Onboarding: Manage the deployment of our clients software solutions, ensuring smooth transitions for new customers and providing comprehensive onboarding to maximize product adoption and success. <li>Customer Impact Focus: Act as the primary point of escalation for challenging, high-impact technical issues, driving timely and effective resolutions for mission-critical customer needs. <li>Project Leadership in Professional Services: Lead professional service projects aimed at product customization and integrations, coordinating with customers to understand requirements and deliver solutions aligned with their business needs. <li>Critical Availability: Provide on-call support for critical escalations outside standard business hours as needed, prioritizing rapid resolution and customer satisfaction. <li>Cross-functional Collaboration: Work closely with development, QA, and product management teams to assist in developing and testing patches, updates, and scripts for issue resolution and software enhancements. <li>Team Mentorship and Skill Development: Mentor junior team members, fostering skill enhancement and knowledge-sharing across the support team. </ul> <p><strong>Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities</strong>
    </p> <p><strong>Experience & Expertise:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Minimum of 7 years of experience in technical support or related fields in a software company, with a track record of successfully managing complex production environments. <li>Hands-on experience with Windows, Linux, and Mac OS environments, as well as multi-platform troubleshooting. <li>Networking knowledge, including TCP/IP, DNS, and SSL, with experience in packet capture and analysis. </ul> <p><strong>Technical Proficiency:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Background in cloud infrastructure services (AWS, Azure) and familiarity with modern cloud-native architectures. <li>Familiarity with database administration (e.g., MySQL, PostgreSQL) and system automation tools to enhance support processes. <li>Competency in scripting or coding in one or more languages and familiarity with automation tools. <li>Experience with real-time data integrations using webhooks, API listeners, and other middleware solutions to enhance system interoperability. </ul> <p><strong>Analytical & Troubleshooting Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Strong diagnostic skills and proficiency in root-cause analysis, with the ability to implement proactive, preventative measures. <li>Ability to synthesize data insights to predict and address system bottlenecks and inefficiencies. </ul> <p><strong>Leadership & Communication:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Exceptional communication skills, both written and verbal, for conveying complex technical information to diverse audiences. <li>Proven ability to lead support projects and initiatives, with a strong focus on customer satisfaction, teamwork, and collaboration. </ul> <p><strong>Additional Desirable Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Experience in technical support leadership roles, with the ability to delegate, prioritize, and coach effectively. <li>Expertise in technical documentation and knowledge management systems to empower both internal teams and end-users. <li>Ability to work flexible hours to support a 24/7 environment and provide guidance in high-pressure, critical situations. </ul> INDSponsor ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Kanata ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Project Manager (IT) (32567) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 23, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ FBY80N8UFN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32567]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>BACKGROUND</strong>
    </p> <p>Algonquin College of Applied Arts and Technology (AC) is a publicly funded English-language college and a member of Polytechnics Canada, located in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada. The College serves the National Capital Region and the surrounding areas of Eastern Ontario, Western Quebec, and Upstate New York. AC has three campuses: the main campus in Ottawa, Ontario, and two secondary campuses in Perth and Pembroke, Ontario.</p> <p>The Information Technology Services (ITS) department at Algonquin College provides support to approximately 65,000 individuals, including students, faculty, administrative staff, and distance learners.</p> <hr /> <p><strong>DESCRIPTION OF WORK / DELIVERABLES</strong>
    </p> <p>The Senior Project Manager will support the ITS department by leading and implementing multiple initiatives. The consultant will collaborate with IT leadership and other key stakeholders to ensure the effective planning, development, and execution of these initiatives, delivering all assigned projects on time, within scope, and on budget, in alignment with ITS PMO standards and best practices.</p> <p>The Senior Project Manager will be responsible for the following:</p> <ol> <li>Oversee the established project vision. Define project objectives, scope, and deliverables in collaboration with project sponsors and stakeholders.</li> <li>Develop and maintain detailed project plans, identifying deliverables, estimating durations, and allocating resources. Manage comprehensive project documentation (e.g., requirements, scope, schedule, cost, communication, resources, risks, issues, change management, and quality).</li> <li>Monitor and control project progress in accordance with corporate policies and standards. Facilitate effective meetings and deliver milestone presentations, issue resolution strategies, and regular status updates. Provide comprehensive reporting and proactive problem-solving.</li> <li>Manage project risks, including contingency planning and critical path analysis. Ensure risk mitigation strategies are in place and executed effectively.</li> <li>Integrate and evaluate change management strategies. Monitor implementation efforts, address transition issues, and ensure business risks are mitigated through appropriate recommendations and follow-up.</li> <li>Ensure adherence to appropriate project management methodologies throughout the project lifecycle. Provide teams with necessary tools and support.</li> <li>Apply high-quality project and program management practices across all stages of the project lifecycle.</li> <li>Lead and manage cross-functional, multi-disciplinary teams to achieve project objectives.</li> <li>Manage communications and maintain effective working relationships with clients and stakeholders.</li> <li>Produce and deliver monthly reports, including project schedules, risk registers, and progress summaries.</li> <li>Collaborate with stakeholders and business partners to develop and implement comprehensive business cases supporting project recommendations.</li> </ol> <hr /> <p><strong>REQUIREMENTS</strong>
    </p> <p>The ideal candidate will possess the following qualifications:</p> <ul> <li>Bachelor’s degree in Business, Computer Science, Management Information Systems, Computer Engineering, or a related IT field.</li> <li>Project Management Professional (PMP) certification or equivalent experience.</li> <li>8 to 10 years of project or program management experience, including at least 5 years managing large-scale projects.</li> <li>Strong collaboration and communication skills, with experience engaging a wide range of stakeholders.</li> <li>Proven ability to lead cross-functional teams and work collaboratively across departments.</li> <li>Expertise in project management methodologies, including issue resolution, risk management, resource planning, and effective team facilitation.</li> <li>Ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously and work closely with Product Managers.</li> <li>Detail-oriented, while maintaining a strong focus on strategic objectives and results.</li> <li>Demonstrated leadership capabilities, with a proven ability to motivate teams and foster collaboration.</li> <li>Strong problem-solving skills with the ability to address complex challenges through analysis and innovation.</li> </ul> INDSponsor ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dominic Scaletta ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Full Stack Developer (.Net, Angular, JavaScript) (32575) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 25, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 9QXCITA5VH ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32575]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">POSITION OVERVIEW</span>
    </strong><br> <br> Looking for a <strong><span style="">Senior .NET Full Stack Developer</span>
    </strong> to support the architecture and development of critical application features. The ideal candidate is a well-rounded developer who enjoys both front-end and back-end work, and thrives in collaborative, agile, and remote-first teams.</span>
    </span><br> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">CORE QUALIFICATIONS</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li>5+ years of experience in full-stack development delivering scalable, production-ready solutions <li>Strong knowledge of:<br> • C#, ASP.NET MVC<br> • Entity Framework and SQL Server<br> • JavaScript, HTML5, CSS <li>Solid understanding of software architecture principles, design patterns, and clean coding standards <li>Hands-on experience with Git and modern source control practices <li>Bachelor’s in Computer Science or equivalent practical experience <li>Must be authorized to work in the U.S. <li>Open to limited travel (2–4 times annually) for team collaboration </ul> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="">PREFERRED EXPERIENCE / NICE TO HAVE</span>
    </strong></span>
    </span> <ul> <li>Experience with modern .NET (.NET Core / .NET 6+) <li>Familiarity with Microsoft Azure and DevOps tools <li>Understanding of containerization (Docker, Linux containers) <li>Proficiency with RESTful API development <li>Exposure to cloud-based services (Azure preferred, AWS acceptable) <li>Experience with modern front-end frameworks like React, Angular, or Vue.js <li>Knowledge of CI/CD tools such as Azure DevOps, GitHub Actions, or Jenkins <li>Test-driven development (TDD) and experience with testing frameworks (xUnit, MSTest, NUnit, Jest, Mocha) <li>Security/authentication protocols (OAuth2, OpenID Connect, IdentityServer) <li>Event-driven architecture and messaging systems (e.g., RabbitMQ, Azure Service Bus, Kafka) </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[  ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michael Theodossiou ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Internal Controls Analyst - SOX/ICFR (32579) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 28, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ SF4D4WR80W ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32579]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our client is seeking a skilled Internal Controls Analyst (SOX/ICFR) to support internal control and financial reporting activities. The successful candidate will participate in or lead client meetings, address inquiries related to information request lists, and perform and review ICFR control testing. Strong project management capabilities are also required.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Participate in and potentially lead meetings with clients <li>Respond to client questions related to information request lists <li>Perform and review testing of internal controls over financial reporting (ICFR) <li>Support project management and tracking of control testing activities </ul> <p><strong>Must-Have Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Practical working experience with ICFR, SOX 404, and NI 52-109 <li>Strong understanding of internal control frameworks <li>Excellent communication and client-facing skills </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>CA, CPA, or CIA designation <li>Experience in the retail sector </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Toronto  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Cloud Support Analyst (32517) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ June 06, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 3UQEV1MF1V ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32517]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>POSITION OVERVIEW:</strong>
    <br> We are seeking a <strong>Cloud Support Analyst (Level II)</strong> to join a growing technology operations team. Reporting into a senior leadership role within the cloud support function, this individual will work directly with internal users and stakeholders to resolve issues related to enterprise systems and data. The role also involves identifying opportunities to enhance system functionality and streamline operational processes. This position requires regular engagement with third-party vendors on implementations, enhancements, and complex troubleshooting initiatives.</p> <hr> <p><strong>KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Apply process and workflow methodologies to enhance support outcomes</p> <li> <p>Demonstrate strong business acumen and understanding of organizational systems</p> <li> <p>Collaborate effectively within both immediate and cross-functional teams</p> <li> <p>Manage assigned tasks and engagements with minimal supervision</p> <li> <p>Build credibility quickly through professional presence and subject-matter expertise</p> <li> <p>Operate effectively in an office-based setting</p> <li> <p>Navigate high-demand environments with fast turnarounds</p> <li> <p>Provide occasional support across global time zones</p> </ul> <hr> <p><strong>QUALIFICATIONS:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Post-secondary education in IT, computer science, or a related field</p> <li> <p>Proven experience supporting enterprise-grade cloud platforms (e.g., Azure, AWS, GCP)</p> <li> <p>Strong SQL skills used in root cause analysis and issue resolution</p> <li> <p>Experience working with databases and scripting for support-related automation</p> <li> <p>Certifications in one or more cloud technologies</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with at least one programming language (e.g., Java)</p> <li> <p>Exposure to automation tools or scripting repeatable support tasks</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Toronto ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Dominic Scaletta ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior FPGA Developer (32589) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 03, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 5CESGZMG2W ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32589]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Overview & Role Focus</strong>
    </p> <p>This role is centered on innovating and advancing state-of-the-art video processing and transport capabilities, delivering high-performance solutions on some of the most integrated poadcast hardware platforms available today. The successful candidate will work hands-on with FPGA design, real-time media interfaces, and poadcast protocol implementation, playing a key role across architecture, development, testing, and cross-functional support.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Lead the development and continuous improvement of advanced video transport and processing features within tightly integrated poadcast hardware. <li>Design RTL for real-time, high-throughput media systems involving advanced interfaces—such as PCIe, memory, and specialized hardware acceleration (e.g., video scaling, HDR/SDR conversion). <li>Implement FPGA-based real-time transport protocols like SMPTE 2110 and SDI. <li>Participate in architectural planning: advise on FPGA density, schematic reviews, clocking strategies, and thermal considerations. <li>Build complete IO ring designs across modern FPGAs (Arria10, Stratix-10, Ultrascale+, MPSoC, Agilex) and validate pin-outs/IP within Quartus and Vivado environments. <li>Define and negotiate high-level design specs, assist in part selection, and align with aggressive project timelines. <li>Contribute to design specifications and documentation used by cross-functional teams. <li>Collaborate closely with peers on design verification and testing of FPGA and hardware systems. <li>Tackle debugging with a methodical and efficient approach. <li>Support team members throughout the entire New Product Introduction (NPI) lifecycle—from design through manufacturing to customer support. </ul> <p><strong>Required Skills & Background</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>5+ years in FPGA and hardware development, with a strong preference for experience in video/audio-centric technologies. <li>Intermediate to senior-level expertise in FPGA architecture and core components. <li>Deep understanding of high-speed serial interfaces, clock domains, timing closure, and transceiver integration. <li>Proficiency in Verilog, SystemVerilog, and TCL scripting; capable of creating testbenches and running simulations (e.g., VCS). <li>Familiarity with modern Intel and Xilinx FPGA families and their development/debugging toolchains. <li>Hands-on experience with interfaces like DDR3/DDR4, HBM, PLLs, and gigabit transceivers. <li>Skilled in lab-based debugging using oscilloscopes, JBERTs, network analyzers, waveform monitors, etc. <li>Embedded system awareness—experience with Linux, C/C++, bash scripting, and networking considered valuable. <li>Broadcast studio domain knowledge is highly desirable, especially within video production and distribution workflows. <li>A strong grasp of digital video/audio standards and signal integrity is considered a plus. <li>Driven and independent, yet collaborative—equally adept at working solo or influencing poader team strategies. <li>Quick learner with a creative mindset and ability to push ideas from concept to market. <li>Comfortable making bold decisions that balance quality, speed, and cost for optimal business outcomes. <li>Effective communicator with sharp observational skills and a problem-solving mindset. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Michael Theodossiou ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ IT Service Management  Advisor  (32479) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 23, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ QQWWARQRGM ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32479]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Overview:</strong>
    </p> <p>Seeking an experienced ITSM Advisor to establish and lead the development of a comprehensive IT Service Management practice. This engagement focuses on creating a structured framework from the ground up, enhancing service delivery operations, and advising on tooling strategies as part of a poader IT modernization effort.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Spearhead the establishment of the organization’s ITSM function, including defining structure, scope, and governance. <li>Develop and document a formal ITSM framework aligned with industry best practices (I.e. ITIL). <li>Provide strategic consultation on tool selection, working closely with stakeholders to assess current platforms and recommend a future-state ITSM solution. <li>Guide the onboarding of a technical ITSM specialist to configure and implement the selected tooling. <li>Design and implement core ITSM processes, including incident, problem, change, and service request management. <li>Define performance metrics and reporting mechanisms to monitor service quality and operational efficiency (I.e. KPI, SLA). <li>Support the organization in evolving how IT services are delivered, focusing on modernizing processes, enhancing cross-functional collaboration, and improving overall IT maturity. <li>Offer guidance and mentoring to internal teams to foster adoption of the new ITSM framework and tools. <li>Maintain awareness of emerging technologies and evolving service management methodologies to inform continuous improvement efforts. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Minimum 3–5 years of experience in ITSM strategy, consulting, or IT operations leadership. <li>Hands-on experience with leading ITSM platforms such as Zendesk, ServiceNow and BMC Remedy to name a few. <li>Proven success leading the stand-up of an ITSM practice, including framework design and tool recommendation. <li>Background in guiding organizations through the transition from multiple ITSM platforms to a unified solution. </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Assets:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Participation in procurement and vendor assessment processes for ITSM platforms. <li>ITIL certification (Foundation or higher); additional certifications such as COBIT, ISO 20000, PMP, or Agile are considered an asset. <li>Familiarity with cloud-based service management solutions and IT governance frameworks. <li>Experience integrating automation and AI into ITSM operations. <li>Prior exposure to enterprise architecture principles and service delivery modernization. </ul> <p><strong>Note:</strong>
    </p> <p>This is a strategic advisory role designed for a consultant with both the vision and execution experience to transform IT service delivery capabilities in a dynamic environment.</p> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Matheo Theodossiou ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ ASIC Development Engineer (32477) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 22, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ JU81IASKQU ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32477]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Position: Senior ASIC Design Engineer – Optical Communication Systems</strong>
    </p> <p>Our client’s team is expanding and seeking highly motivated, experienced professional engineers to help develop next-generation systems in a rapidly growing and competitive industry. This is an excellent opportunity to contribute to cutting-edge technologies in optical communication. Candidates must hold a degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, or possess equivalent professional experience.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Develop state-of-the-art electronic devices and intellectual property (IP) for optical communication systems. <li>Apply proven expertise in deep sub-micron silicon technologies. <li>Collaborate effectively within a multi-site, international development team. <li>Design ASIC devices for the processing of optical signals. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications and Skills:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Master’s degree or PhD in Electronic Engineering, Telecommunication Engineering, or a related discipline. <li>A minimum of 8 years of demonstrated experience in deep sub-micron ASIC design. <li>Proficiency in VHDL and/or Verilog for development and ASIC verification. <li>Preferred experience in digital signal processing (DSP) and forward error correction (FEC) design. <li>Experience with high-speed analog design is a plus. <li>Strong analytical thinking and problem-solving capabilities. <li>Excellent teamwork skills, with the ability to collaborate across international teams and time zones. <li>Effective communication skills, including fluency in English. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Mountain View ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ CA ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ SAP Data Migration Lead (32597) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 08, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 82X668A814 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32597]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is hiring an experienced <strong>SAP Data Migration Lead</strong> to join a long-term S/4HANA transformation engagement with a major Canadian enterprise client. The role will focus on leading complex SAP data migration activities with a strong emphasis on SAP BODS, technical leadership, and cross-functional collaboration with finance and business teams.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Lead SAP data conversion strategy and execution for large-scale SAP S/4HANA migration projects. <li>Interface daily with client stakeholders including executives, project managers, and technical teams. <li>Manage full data migration lifecycle: data readiness, architecture, mock loads, validation, and cutover. <li>Provide technical leadership to SAP BODS development teams. <li>Collaborate across modules including FI, CO, MM, EWM, PM, PPM, and HR. <li>Deliver high-quality migration outputs on schedule and budget. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Experience & Skills:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>8–10 years in SAP MDM/Data Migration; 5+ full-cycle implementations. <li>Deep hands-on expertise with <strong>SAP BODS (BusinessObjects Data Services)</strong> for ETLV tasks. <li>Solid understanding of SAP data migration tools (LTMC, LSMW, IDOCs, custom programs). <li>Strong experience with data profiling, cleansing, validation, de-duplication, and transformation. <li>Experience migrating data between SAP ECC, SAP CFIN, and SAP S/4HANA (brownfield migration). <li>Knowledge of master and transactional data objects (e.g., Company Code, Legal Entity, FI/CO). <li>Proficient in SQL and data quality reporting dashboards. <li>Previous experience supporting data migration for clients in the <strong>Energy sector</strong> is an asset. </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Soft Skills:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li>Strong communication and presentation skills. <li>Proven ability to lead client workshops and technical teams. <li>Ability to challenge and advise stakeholders with innovative solutions. <li>Comfortable working in fast-paced, client-facing environments. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Calgary ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ AB ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Bilingual Salesforce Business Analyst – Grantmaking (32602) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 10, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ LKFIUC6XDH ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32602]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our client, a leading financial institution, is seeking a skilled<strong> Bilingual</strong> <strong>Salesforce Business Analyst</strong> with hands-on experience in <strong>Salesforce Non-Profit Cloud and grantmaking processes</strong> to support a high-impact digital transformation initiative within their Banking Technology division.</p> <p>This role is ideal for a <strong>business-oriented professional</strong> who brings strong <strong>financial services experience</strong>, paired with <strong>Salesforce consulting expertise</strong>. The selected candidate will drive actionable insights and process improvements across Salesforce platforms, enabling smarter decision-making and operational efficiency.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p>Collaborate with stakeholders to gather, document, and analyze business requirements.</p> <li> <p>Evaluate and streamline current business processes.</p> <li> <p>Create functional specifications, business cases, and support implementation efforts.</p> <li> <p>Generate reports, dashboards, and visualizations using Salesforce and data tools.</p> <li> <p>Facilitate stakeholder meetings and communicate findings effectively.</p> <li> <p>Support testing and project planning within Agile/Scrum environments.</p> <li> <p>Ensure alignment with business goals, compliance, and technology best practices.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </h3> <ul> <li> <p><strong>Mandatory:</strong> Experience with <strong>Salesforce Non-Profit Cloud</strong> and grantmaking workflows.</p> <li> <p>Minimum <strong>3+ years</strong> of experience as a Business Analyst in the <strong>financial services industry</strong>.</p> <li> <p><strong>2+ years</strong> of experience in a <strong>consulting environment</strong>.</p> <li> <p>Strong analytical skills; experience with <strong>Excel, SQL, Power BI/Tableau</strong>, and project tools.</p> <li> <p>Experience with multiple Salesforce clouds, including:</p> <ul> </ul> <li> <p><strong>Sales Cloud</strong>
    </p> <li> <p><strong>Service Cloud</strong>
    </p> <li> <p><strong>Experience Cloud</strong>
    </p> <li> <p><strong>Financial Services Cloud</strong>
    </p> </ul> <ul> <li> <p>Exceptional BILINGUAL communication and stakeholder engagement skills. (FRENCH)</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with Agile/Scrum methodology.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Montreal ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ RAN Network - Customer Support (32467) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 21, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ AIHRRDO0ZX ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32467]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;">Customer Support Engineer</span>
    </span> <p><strong>Customer Support Engineer – RAN (Radio Access Network)</strong>
    <br> <strong>Location:</strong> Onsite in Chicago, IL<br> <strong>Note:</strong> No Corp-to-Corp engagements.<br> <strong>Security Clearance:</strong> Must be able to obtain and maintain security clearance.</p> <p><strong>Job Overview:</strong>
    <br> We are seeking an experienced Customer Support Engineer specializing in RAN to work as an onsite Resident Engineer with our customer in Chicago. The ideal candidate will have recent, hands-on experience supporting RAN technologies and meeting the responsibilities outlined below.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Perform first-level troubleshooting and respond to anomalies in RAN network elements. <li>Escalate unresolved issues by creating detailed support tickets. <li>Support network activities including migrations, upgrades, and change implementations on behalf of the customer. <li>Prepare and review Methods of Procedure (MOPs) for planned activities, as outlined in the statement of work (SOW). <li>Participate in Operational Readiness Testing (ORT) and Acceptance Testing Procedures (ATP), as per the SOW. <li>Generate and deliver incident reports and KPI reports when required. <li>Provide technical support and troubleshooting to end-users and internal stakeholders. <li>Maintain accurate documentation of network configurations, changes, and system upgrades. <li>Lead trained contractors and BSS engineers during the installation and integration of telecommunications equipment. <li>Conduct trials, feature testing, and new product launches, as outlined in the SOW. </ul> <p><strong>Requirements:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Hands-on experience with Operations and Maintenance (O&M) for AirScale and FlexiZone (Indoor & Outdoor) BTS site solutions. <li>Proficiency in BTS Element Management tools, including Web User Interface, BTS Site Manager, and BTS CLI. <li>Strong troubleshooting skills using tools such as EMIL Toolkit, DCAP, UTF, and 5G Tool Kit. <li>Experience working with OSS applications including Mantray, CM Operation Manager, CM Editor, Workflow Tool, Software Manager, and Monitor Application. <li>Familiarity with documentation and knowledge portals. </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Chicago ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ IL ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[  ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Adam Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Banking Technology Integration Consultant - Lockbox/Payments (32606) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 10, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 2E0AYUF432 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32606]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>We are seeking an experienced Banking Technology Integration Consultant (Lockbox/Payments) Implementation Specialist to support a large financial institution’s transformation project. This role focuses on the implementation and integration of cheque imaging, lockbox services, exception/returns handling, and ensuring compliance with North American regulatory requirements.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead and support the implementation of cheque processing technologies and lockbox solutions.</p> <li> <p>Conduct discovery sessions with business stakeholders and product owners.</p> <li> <p>Develop strategy, planning documentation, and ensure smooth technical integration.</p> <li> <p>Interface with vendors and internal stakeholders to gather requirements and deliver end-to-end solutions.</p> <li> <p>Ensure compliance with Canada and U.S. cheque processing regulations.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>10+ years of experience in financial services or banking technology.</p> <li> <p>Proven experience in cheque processing and lockbox solution implementation.</p> <li> <p>Familiarity with North American regulatory requirements.</p> <li> <p>Experience working at Symcor or implementing similar solutions in the U.S. is highly desirable.</p> <li> <p>Strong communication and stakeholder engagement skills.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Scarborough ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Product Line Manager - CIP (31639) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 10, 2024 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ XN7F1JIM1D ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[31639]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>The recruitment team at Myticas Consulting is currently seeking an experienced Optical Networking resource who would be interested in working within the CIP vertical. </p> <p>We are looking for a candidate who is currently based in Canada since this is offered on a remote full-time permanent basis and requires the resource to be located within the country.</p> <p>The candidate in this role should have the following requirements:</p> <ul> <li>Highly experienced in CIP Optical Networking Deployment <li>Over 8 Years of Optical Networking expertise <li>Experience with Optical Network deployment and system development <li>Experience with Optical PLM <li>Experience with Operational Support Systems <li>Experience with Open Standards and Concepts </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[  ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[  ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Remote ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Amanda Messina ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[  Senior Change Management Specialist (32612) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 15, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ TLKK0YQPW9 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32612]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Our client, a leading professional services firm, is urgently seeking an experienced <strong>Senior Change Management Specialist</strong> to support a critical engagement in Halifax. The ideal candidate will have deep experience driving change management initiatives across large-scale IT or ERP transformation projects—ideally in the public sector. This position requires a skilled professional who can plan, manage, and execute structured change initiatives while collaborating with various stakeholder groups.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead the delivery of change management work plans, including activities like stakeholder engagement, change impact assessment, and organizational change action planning.</p> <li> <p>Coordinate logistics, communications, meeting schedules, and prep materials for change management initiatives.</p> <li> <p>Oversee and guide Change Specialists involved in associated streams.</p> <li> <p>Track and report weekly progress to the OCM or Communications Lead.</p> <li> <p>Identify, document, and escalate risks, issues, or decisions related to business readiness and delivery.</p> <li> <p>Champion continuous improvement within the change stream.</p> <li> <p>Develop and deliver change management knowledge transfer plans.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5+ years of experience leading change initiatives, particularly focused on:</p> <ul> <li> <p>People & business process change</p> <li> <p>IT implementation change</p> </ul> <li> <p>Hands-on delivery of change management programs using frameworks such as PROSCI or similar.</p> <li> <p>Strong workshop facilitation experience (1-on-1, small and large groups).</p> <li> <p>Excellent communication, problem-solving, and stakeholder engagement skills.</p> <li> <p>Strong organizational and prioritization capabilities.</p> <li> <p>Proficiency in MS Office tools.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Halifax ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ NS ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Business System Analyst - Banking (32617) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ FT20B9GOK7 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32617]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is actively seeking a <strong>Business Systems Analyst</strong> for a high-impact HYBRID contract opportunity within a leading financial institution in Montreal. This role supports the <strong>Banking Services and Payments</strong> portfolio during a critical implementation phase, requiring strong delivery focus, flexibility, and a hands-on consulting background.</p> <p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead business requirements gathering and functional analysis aligned to project objectives.</p> <li> <p>Translate business needs into clear specifications for technical and operational teams.</p> <li> <p>Take ownership of deliverables across the full SDLC — from planning to post-implementation.</p> <li> <p>Manage cross-functional collaboration and drive stakeholder alignment.</p> <li> <p>Leverage knowledge of banking services, system integrations, and payment processes.</p> <li> <p>Participate in production events, including occasional overtime or weekend support.</p> <li> <p>Use Jira to manage tasks, track progress, and ensure accountability.</p> <li> <p>Support a collaborative team culture and contribute to continuous improvement.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Key Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>5+ years’ experience as a Business Systems Analyst in consulting or financial services.</p> <li> <p>Proven success in delivering <strong>end-to-end system implementation projects</strong>.</p> <li> <p>Knowledge of banking and payments systems is required.</p> <li> <p>Technically savvy — able to liaise effectively with development and infrastructure teams.</p> <li> <p>Demonstrated accountability, attention to detail, and strong organizational skills.</p> <li> <p>Experience using Jira is an asset.</p> <li> <p>Must be available to work on-site 3+ days per week and during key production windows.</p> <li> <p>No upcoming vacation during contract period.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Montreal ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Delivery Lead-Banking Intergration (32618) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 1QF6XVIPTZ ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32618]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title: Delivery Lead – Banking Integration Program (Hybrid)</strong>
    </p> <p>We are seeking an experienced <strong>Delivery Lead</strong> to support a critical banking integration program. This <strong>hybrid role</strong> is pivotal during a high-impact phase of the project, with multiple production events planned over the coming months. The successful candidate must understand that the program is at a crucial juncture and be prepared to work overtime, including weekends, as needed.</p> <hr> <h3>Key Responsibilities</h3> <p><strong>1. Program Management</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead the delivery of the banking integration program across approximately 10 squads, ensuring alignment with strategic goals and delivery timelines.</p> <li> <p>Develop, manage, and maintain the overall program plan, tracking progress against scope and schedule.</p> </ul> <p><strong>2. Servant Leadership</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Collaborate closely with squad leads, fostering a servant-leader approach to empower and support teams.</p> <li> <p>Promote a culture of collaboration, ownership, and accountability.</p> </ul> <p><strong>3. Risk and Issue Management</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Identify, manage, and resolve risks and issues that could impact project delivery.</p> <li> <p>Facilitate timely decision-making to maintain momentum.</p> </ul> <p><strong>4. Stakeholder Collaboration</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Engage and communicate effectively with stakeholders to align expectations, drive outcomes, and overcome challenges.</p> <li> <p>Support innovative problem-solving to meet aggressive delivery goals.</p> </ul> <p><strong>5. Jira Management</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Use advanced Jira skills, including proficiency with JQL, to monitor project status, manage tasks, and generate insightful reports.</p> <li> <p>Ensure consistent Jira usage across all squads, support administrative needs, and maintain dashboard and hygiene standards.</p> </ul> <p><strong>6. On-Site Presence</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Must be based in Montreal, or if located in Toronto, willing to travel to Montreal for key production events.</p> <li> <p>Commit to working in the office at least <strong>three days per week</strong> to promote collaboration and alignment.</p> </ul> <p><strong>7. Availability</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Flexible and prepared to work overtime and weekends in alignment with the project schedule.</p> <li> <p>No vacation should be scheduled during the contract period to ensure full availability.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3>Key Qualifications</h3> <ul> <li> <p>Demonstrated experience in program management, ideally within large-scale banking integration projects.</p> <li> <p>Strong servant-leader mindset with a commitment to team success.</p> <li> <p>Advanced Jira expertise, including proficiency in JQL.</p> <li> <p>Proven ability to solve complex problems and engage constructively with demanding stakeholders.</p> <li> <p>Comfortable working in a fast-paced, high-pressure environment with aggressive deadlines.</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Montreal ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ QC ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ ASIC Development Engineer (32476) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ May 22, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ K8DCUBAGSN ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32476]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Job Title: Senior ASIC Design Engineer – Optical Communication Systems</strong>
    </p> <p>Our client’s team is expanding and seeking highly motivated, experienced professional engineers to join in the development of next-generation systems within a fast-growing and competitive environment. Candidates must hold a degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, or possess equivalent experience.</p> <p><strong>Main Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Design and development of state-of-the-art electronic devices and intellectual property (IP) for optical communication systems <li>Demonstrated experience working with deep sub-micron silicon technologies <li>Collaboration within multi-site international development teams <li>Design of ASIC devices for optical signal processing </ul> <p><strong>Required Skills and Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li>Master’s degree or Ph.D. in Electronic Engineering, Telecommunication Engineering, or a related discipline <li>Minimum of 8 years of proven experience in deep sub-micron ASIC design <li>Proficiency in VHDL/Verilog development and ASIC verification <li>Preferred experience in digital signal processing (DSP) and forward error correction (FEC) design <li>Experience in high-speed analog design <li>Strong analytical thinking and problem-solving skills <li>Effective teamwork and ability to collaborate with international teams across multiple time zones <li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills <li>Proficiency in English </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ Ontario ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Mike Gebara ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ SAP Functional Lead – Project Systems - PS (32621) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 32BPTNNCU8 ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32621]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is looking for a senior <strong>SAP Functional Lead – Project Systems (PS)</strong> for a long-term HYBRID (Winnipeg) consulting engagement with a major utility and energy client. The successful candidate will be responsible for leading the design and implementation of SAP Project Systems solutions, ensuring alignment with business needs across project lifecycle management, finance integration, and operational workflows.</p> <p>This is a high-visibility role requiring strong leadership, communication, and problem-solving skills. The position is hybrid with 50–70% travel to Winnipeg, MB. Candidates must be flexible with on-site travel and able to engage with stakeholders at all levels, including executives.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead the configuration and implementation of SAP PS solutions, including integration with maintenance, service, and finance modules</p> <li> <p>Collaborate with business and technical teams to gather and translate business requirements</p> <li> <p>Drive client discussions, challenging stakeholders when needed to ensure alignment with SAP best practices</p> <li> <p>Participate in project blueprinting, documentation, and testing activities</p> <li> <p>Support change management, training, and go-live planning</p> <li> <p>Monitor project progress, manage risks, and communicate outcomes effectively</p> </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum 5 years (preferably 8+) SAP PS and/or PPM experience</p> <li> <p>Experience in at least 2–3 full lifecycle SAP implementations</p> <li> <p>Prior consulting experience with strong client-facing communication skills</p> <li> <p>Background in utilities, energy, oil, or gas is a strong asset</p> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Finance, or a related field</p> <li> <p>SAP certifications highly preferred</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Winnipeg ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ MB ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[  SAP FICO/RTR Lead (32631) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 16, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ 88L0G7OZ6L ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32631]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p>Myticas Consulting is seeking an experienced <strong>SAP FICO/RTR Lead</strong> for a long-term HYBRID contract with a major utility and energy client. This is a senior-level <strong>techo-functional</strong> role requiring a mix of <strong>deep functional finance expertise</strong> and <strong>strong technical capabilities</strong> within the SAP ecosystem. The position requires frequent travel (50–70%) to Winnipeg, MB, and the consultant may be based anywhere in Canada.</p> <p><strong>Project Scope:</strong>
    <br> The successful candidate will help develop methodologies, tools, and thought leadership in SAP Finance as part of a critical ERP initiative. The role requires strong hands-on knowledge of <strong>SAP Finance (FICO/RTR)</strong> and integration with other modules, along with experience in <strong>end-to-end implementations</strong> and <strong>strategic financial processes</strong>.</p> <hr> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Lead SAP FICO/RTR workstream across implementation and integration efforts</p> <li> <p>Provide hands-on configuration and design of SAP Finance modules (GL, AP, AR, AA, CO, Treasury, SAC-Planning, etc.)</p> <li> <p>Collaborate with business and technical teams to document requirements, define process flows, and ensure high-quality solution delivery</p> <li> <p>Integrate SAP FICO with PS, PM, MM, IS-U, and SCM modules</p> <li> <p>Contribute to finance strategy, reporting systems, and regulatory requirements specific to utilities</p> </ul> <hr> <p><strong>Key Qualifications:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>8+ years of SAP Finance experience across GL, AR, AP, AA, CO, etc.</p> <li> <p>Experience leading large-scale SAP S/4HANA implementations</p> <li> <p>Functional and technical experience with finance and cost accounting processes</p> <li> <p>Strong familiarity with SAP integrations across IS-U, MM, CS, EWM, PS</p> <li> <p>Understanding of Power & Utilities finance regulations is a plus</p> <li> <p>SAP Certifications highly preferred</p> <li> <p>Degree in Accounting, Finance, or Computer Science (MBA a strong asset)</p> <li> <p>Experience with Datasphere, SAC, and Analysis for Office is a bonus</p> </ul> <hr> <p><strong>Additional Details:</strong>
    </p> <ul> <li> <p>Travel to Winnipeg is mandatory (50–70%)</p> <li> <p>Must be flexible with on-site scheduling</p> <li> <p>This is a client-facing leadership role requiring excellent communication and stakeholder engagement skills</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Winnipeg ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ MB ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ Canada                                                           ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Runa Parmar ]]></assignedrecruiter>
  </job>
  </source>
