<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<source>
  <title>Myticas Consulting</title>
  <link>https://www.myticas.com</link>
  <job><title><![CDATA[ Business Development Manager – IT Staffing Services (34025) ]]></title><company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company><date><![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]></date><referencenumber><![CDATA[ H32SSVFBQD ]]></referencenumber><bhatsid><![CDATA[ 34025 ]]></bhatsid><url><![CDATA[ https://apply.myticas.com/34025/Business%20Development%20Manager%20%E2%80%93%20IT%20Staffing%20Services/?source=LinkedIn ]]></url><description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Title: </strong>Business Development Manager – IT Staffing Services.<br>
<br>
<strong><u>About us:</u></strong> Myticas Consulting Group of Companies. Myticas specializes in IT Staffing and Recruitment Services with over 50 years of combined experience in the IT Staffing industry. We serve clients in all industries in the United States and Canada with offices in Ottawa, Chicago, Atlanta, Cleveland, and Grand Rapids. <br>
<br>
<strong><u>About the position:</u></strong> The Sr. Business Development professional will sit in our Chicago, Illinois office This position is a hybrid role and requires some travel. This position is responsible for Business Development in this area as a priority, but able to develop business in OH, PA, WV, IN, IL, etc. This position comes with a competitive salary, commission, bonus potential, medical, dental, vision, 401K, and PTO. This professional would have full access to training, access to and support from the marketing department and technical tools in support of their success. <br>
<br>
<strong>Job Duties and Responsibilities:</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Initiate contact, develop relationships, and conduct business development activities with clients and professionals; networking and connecting with IT professionals, executives, managers, and other professionals and resources at potential, new, and existing clients.
	</li><li>Research and qualify new clients, conducting business development activities and negotiating terms of service and agreements with new clients.
	</li><li>Provided expert level staffing support to clients, hiring managers, and professionals. Qualifying technical position requirements and coordinating with technical recruiters to fulfill staffing needs for new and existing clients.
	</li><li>Represent and market the  Myticas Consulting Group brands.
	</li><li>Participate, network at, support, and sponsor events involving the technical community.
	</li><li>Sell via telephone, face-to-face and videoconferencing.
	</li><li>Utilize Bullhorn CRM/Application tracking system for client and manager outreach and keep CRM documentation, agreements, resources, and paperwork up to date.
</li></ul>

<p><strong>Required Experience:</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>3-5 years’ demonstrated record of success selling staffing services, preferably with experience in the IT environment.
	</li><li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills.
	</li><li>Outstanding customer service, integrity, and interpersonal skills.  
	</li><li>Energetic, enthusiastic, self-motivated, collaborative.
	</li><li>Passion for the staffing industry, excellent work ethic, and strong desire to succeed.
</li></ul> ]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[ Direct Hire ]]></jobtype><city><![CDATA[ Chicago ]]></city><state><![CDATA[ Illinois ]]></state><country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country><category><![CDATA[  ]]></category><apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email><remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype><assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ Chris Halkai ]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[  ]]></jobfunction><jobindustries><![CDATA[  ]]></jobindustries><senioritylevel><![CDATA[  ]]></senioritylevel></job></source>
