<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<source>
  <publisherurl>https://myticas.com</publisherurl>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Senior IAM Consultant (34089) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 31, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ BWKMR9BUNO ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 34089 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ Must Haves: Minimum 7 years experience as a solution Architect on Oracle Identity Access Management systems ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ ON ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Onsite ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ #LI-AG ]]></assignedrecruiter>
    <jobfunction><![CDATA[ Consulting ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ Environmental Engineer (34088) ]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[ July 31, 2025 ]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ Y9AWX1CUCT ]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[ 34088 ]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[ https://myticas.com/ ]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Environmental Engineer</strong><br> <strong>Location:</strong> Indianapolis, IN<br> <strong>Position Type:</strong> 100% Contract<br> <strong>Work Schedule:</strong> 37.5 hours/week | Monday–Friday, 8:15 AM – 4:45 PM EST<br> <strong>Client:</strong> Myticas’ Direct Client (Indiana Department of Health)</p> <p><strong>NOTE FROM HIRING MANAGER:</strong><br> This is a long-term, full-time contract position with a standard weekly schedule of 37.5 hours. The candidate must be available to work during regular state office hours (8:15 AM – 4:45 PM EST). Please confirm your understanding of and availability for this schedule.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Job Summary:</strong></h3> <p>The Environmental Engineer is responsible for conducting plan reviews and related tasks to ensure compliance with all relevant laws, rules, and standards. This work supports the Indiana Department of Health's mission to protect public health in the construction and operation of healthcare facilities and other regulated structures. The role emphasizes the application of architectural and engineering standards across multiple disciplines, including safety, sanitation, water supply, sewage disposal, mechanical systems, electrical systems, plumbing, and applicable licensing requirements for facilities in Indiana.</p> <p>This position also requires effective communication and timely responses to inquiries from the public, consultants, contractors, and the regulated community.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>Review and evaluate architectural and engineering plans to ensure regulatory compliance.</p> <li> <p>Apply environmental and public health principles to design evaluations.</p> <li> <p>Provide timely, professional responses to inquiries from the public and regulated entities.</p> <li> <p>Interpret and apply relevant state and federal codes and standards.</p> <li> <p>Recommend actionable plans based on technical data and plan analysis.</p> <li> <p>Ensure compliance with environmental engineering policies and sanitation practices.</p> <li> <p>Support public health initiatives through the review of facility plans requiring state approval.</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Technical Knowledge and Experience:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum 1 year of experience reading blueprints/plans, analyzing data, and recommending corrective or actionable solutions.</p> <li> <p>Working knowledge of:</p> <ul> <li> <p>Environmental engineering laws, rules, and technical guidelines</p> <li> <p>On-site sewage disposal and sanitation policies</p> <li> <p>Public health science and environmental health principles</p> <li> <p>Soil science and applied mathematics</p> <li> <p>FGI (Facility Guidelines Institute) healthcare facility design guidelines (hospitals, outpatient, residential)</p> <li> <p>NFPA (National Fire Protection Association) codes and standards</p> </ul> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Education and Certification:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>Bachelor’s degree in Environmental Engineering or a related field (Required)</p> <li> <p>Indiana Professional Engineering (PE) License (Preferred but not required)</p> </ul> ]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[ Contract ]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[ Indianapolis ]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ IN ]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[ United States                                                    ]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[ Hybrid ]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[ #LI-MYT ]]></assignedrecruiter>
    <jobfunction><![CDATA[ Engineering ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Civil Engineering ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Business Objects SQL Developer (32539)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 13, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[L7G0OI7S2P]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32539]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/SQL Developer </strong></p> <p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/SQL Developer</p> <p><strong>Location:</strong> Remote (with occasional travel to Springfield, IL)</p> <p><strong>Contract: </strong>12 months with possibly multiyear extension/s</p> <p><strong>Functional Description: </strong></p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is seeking a skilled and experienced BI BusinessObjects/SQL Developer to design, develop, and maintain business intelligence solutions using SAP BusinessObjects and SQL. This role supports Medicaid/CHIP claims and other healthcare data systems, ensuring accurate reporting and data integrity for state and federal stakeholders.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Design, develop, and maintain BusinessObjects reports using Medicaid/CHIP claims and subsystem data. <li>Write, optimize, and maintain complex SQL scripts and queries for data marts and reporting. <li>Create and manage BusinessObjects Universes and metadata layers. <li>Develop and maintain database systems to support efficient data storage and reporting. <li>Manage server backups and ensure system reliability. <li>Collaborate with stakeholders to gather requirements and recommend technical solutions. <li>Participate in unit, integration, and system testing. <li>Provide regular project updates to customers and maintain strong communication. <li>Mentor junior team members and provide technical training as needed. <li>Stay current with emerging technologies and industry best practices. <li>Perform additional duties as required to support project and organizational goals. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>5+ years of experience in SAP BusinessObjects development and reporting including report Universe designing. <li>5+ years of SQL development, including 4+ years of performance tuning. <li>2+ years of experience in data warehouse projects. <li>2+ years of experience with Teradata (v15+), including SQL Assistant. <li>Strong communication skills and the ability to work directly with clients. <li>Bachelor’s or advanced degree in IT, Computer Science, Mathematics, Statistics, or a related field. <li>Excellent organizational skills and ability to manage multiple priorities. <li>Strong team collaboration and adaptability. </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications: </strong></p> <ul> <li>2+ years of experience as Business Objects server administrator <li>Familiarity with Medicaid, Medicare, or healthcare-related applications. <li>Experience with Tableau or BusinessObjects version upgrades. 2025 Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/S </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Illinois]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-DS]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Information Technology ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lab Technician (32645)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 21, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[IBYZCJL6I0]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32645]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Myticas direct client is seeking<strong> Jr Lab Technician</strong> at Waukegan, IL <strong>(Hybrid-3 days onsite)</strong><br> <br> <strong>Duration: 6</strong><strong> months</strong><strong> (with a possibility of extension)</strong><br> <br> <strong>Description:</strong><br> <br> One of our direct clients is looking for a Jr Lab Technician who would be responsible for performing highly automated compound management department utilizing robotic instruments to manage the tasks of adding or removing samples from storage banks, along with electronic barcodes to facilitate record-keeping and sample preparation tailored to research scientists’ experimental needs. Automation not only accelerates sample delivery but also promises enhanced consistency of samples regarding concentration accuracy and the uniformity of physical properties across experimental runs. These improvements are crucial in advancing early drug discovery.<br> <br> Responsibilities:<br> <br> Work cross-functionally to develop a deep understanding of the scientific processes and identify key bottlenecks that could be improved with automation to increase research velocity.<br> • Develop appropriate automation protocols to meet the needs research scientists.<br> • Maintain instrumentation through routine maintenance and Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) to minimize equipment downtime.<br> • Write and update protocols for new automation workflows using robotic-specific software for laboratory instruments, e.g., Tecan, Beckman Coulter, Agilent Technologies, and SPT.<br> • Draft, edit, and review laboratory Standard Operating Procedures for the automated platforms and the protocols necessary to support sample delivery.<br> • Promptly enter all data to support the needs of the research scientist.<br> • Interpret results, identify anomalies or unexpected outcomes, and provide appropriate remedies.<br> <br> Qualifications:<br> List required and preferred qualifications (up to 10). Include education, skills, and experience.<br> • Bachelor’s degree in a scientific discipline (e.g., biology, chemistry, or similar).<br> • Experience with robotic liquid handlers from Hamilton, TECAN, Agilent Technologies, or Beckman Coulter.<br> • Experience in compound management preferred.<br> • Ability to work upright and stationary and/or standing for typical working hours.<br> • Ability to lift and move objects up to 25 pounds.<br> • Ability to work in non-traditional work environments.<br> • Ability to use and learn standard office equipment and technology proficiently.<br> • May have exposure to potentially hazardous elements typically found in laboratory environments (PPE required).</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[IL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Science ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Biotechnology ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Entry level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst (32542)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 13, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[L6Q2S6PKX6]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32542]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst</strong></p> <p><strong>Duration: </strong>12 months with possible multi-year extension/s</p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is are seeking a highly experienced <strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst </strong>for a large, direct client in Springfield, IL. </p> <p><strong>Primary Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Gathering and analyzing technical information from various sources to be included in the documentation. <li>Planning, writing, and maintaining detailed technical, operational, and process documentation. <li>Leading, developing, and maintaining a library of technical and business documentation source code and reports. <li>Analyze Medicaid program including claims, eligibility, and provider data supporting data warehouse downstream reporting and analytics. <li>Developing and supporting technical training materials. <li>Modifying existing technical documentation for business needs. <li>Participating in and leading technical and business requirements sessions. <li>Meeting with the project team regularly to consolidate project status and reporting. <li>Engaging with the customer as needed to provide updates on technical documentation and project work. <li>Working with the development and QA team to assure each document has been thoroughly reviewed and support process improvements and operational efficiency. <li>Mentoring/Coaching other project team members on effective writing skills and strategies for consistency. <li>Performing additional duties that are typically associated with this position, as assigned. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>5+ years of healthcare business analysis experience supporting business initiatives through data analysis, writing business requirements and user acceptance testing of various systems. <li>5+ years of experience serving as a technical analyst in healthcare (payor). <li>3+ years of experience working specifically with Medicaid programs, MMIS/MES or related systems. <li>3+ years of experience in knowledge management creating, organizing, sharing, and optimizing knowledge within an enterprise organization using tools such as Microsoft 365, AI-enabled search, MS SharePoint/Teams, and JIRA. <li>Proven ability to lead communication (written and verbal) at the customer leadership level. <li>Knowledge of health insurance, HMO, and managed care principles including Medicaid and Medicare regulation. <li>Ability to interpret federal and state Medicaid policy and translate it into business and technical requirements. <li>Effective organizational, analytical, time management, problem-solving, and multi-tasking skills, and habits; ability to complete assignments under tight deadlines with little/no direct supervision. <li>Bachelor’s degree in business, information systems, Public Health, or a related field </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Master’s Degree in related field is preferred. <li>5+ years of experience as a technical analyst in payor healthcare. <li>3+ years of experience writing SQL using large-scale database management tools. <li>3+ years of experience working with State Medicaid and CHIP agencies including federal reporting (CMS 64/21, TMSIS, PERM). Enterprise Data Warehouse - Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst <li>Knowledge of data integration, software enhancements/planning and agile methodologies <li>Experience with using Azure DevOps, SharePoint, MS Project, Visio </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Illinois]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-DS]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Analyst ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Hospitals and Health Care ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Manager - Manufacturing (32619)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 16, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[17WZZFTR14]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32619]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p> </p> <p><strong>IT Infrastructure Manager - Manufacturing</strong><br> <strong>Direct hire</strong><br> <strong>Onsite - Orion, MI</strong><br> <br> Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is seeking an <strong>IT Plant Manager</strong> for a large client in Orion, MI. This role is crucial in managing all IT-related activities at the local plant, with key responsibilities encompassing infrastructure, manufacturing software, and business operations. Local candidates are strongly preferred.<br> <br> <strong> Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Manage daily IT activity at plant level including employee related issues. <li>Assist in budget (cap-ex/allocation) for plant and corporate level. <li>Maintain budget for plant related IT expenses. <li>Provide direct supervision for IT Plant Support Specialist assigned to respective plant. <li>Manages the third-party maintenance for network, hardware, software, and telecommunications services. <li>Participate in budget planning, implementation, and monitoring for purchase and maintenance of hardware and software for the plant <li>Prepare plans for applications, physical infrastructure and the acquisition of the necessary resources to support these items and assure responsiveness of the plans relating to corporate objectives. <li>Manage the installation of hardware and software by others. <li>Manage provisioning of end user workstations/laptops based on corporate standards. <li>Reasonable accommodation may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions. </ul> <p><strong>Qualifications</strong></p> <ul> <li>A minimum of six years of experience in an IT Manager role. <li>Bachelor's degree in Information Technology, Computer Science or a related field <li>Six (6) years of experience creating strategic plans <li>A minimum of four (4) years of experience working with cross-functional teams <li>Four (4) years of experience managing a budget <li>A minimum of 4 years of project management experience <li>A minimum of three (3) years of experience training and developing direct reports <li>Six (6) years of organization and planning experience <li>A minimum of six years of experience with the following technical skills: <li>SQL Server database software <li>Microsoft operating systems and Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Access) <li>VMWare <li>PC <li>RF <li>Printing <li>Server <li>Network Storage systems <li>Knowledge of networking <li>Backup technologies to support troubleshooting efforts <li>Industry based IT tools <li>Must be able to regularly lift and/or move up to 30 pounds. </ul> <p><br> <strong>Preferred skills/Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>IT automotive systems <li>ERP such as Plex <li>MES <li>Plant floor applications and networks preferred. </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Direct Hire]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Auburn Hills]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Michigan]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Onsite]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Information Technology ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Electrical/Electronic Manufacturing ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Legal Analyst/Attorney (34082)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 30, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[704ZVYHGOA]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[34082]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[Myticas&apos;s direct client, based in Minneapolis, MN, is seeking a <strong><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">Legal Analyst/Attorney with J.D.</span></span></span></span></span></strong> for a hybrid contract position.<br> <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Job Title:</span></span></strong> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">Legal Analyst/Attorney with J.D.</span></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Work Location:</span></span></strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> <strong>Hybrid, 2 days onsite/week <em><u>at either of locations</u> - </em></strong></span></span><strong><em><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">St. Cloud, MN or Minneapolis MN</span></span></span></em></strong></span></span></span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Duration:</span></span></strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;"> 6+ month contract-to-Hire</span></span></span></span></span><br> <br> <br> <div style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: yellow;"><span style="color: black;">NOTE</span></span></span></u></strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">:<strong><u> MUST HAVE,</u></strong></span></span></span></span></div> <ol> <li style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><strong style="color: rgb(33,33,33);font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;font-size: 11.0pt;"><u>Juris Doctor (J.D.) degree</u></strong><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;font-size: 11.0pt;">.</span> <li><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">Ability to review documents.</span></span></span></span></span> </ol> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">JOB SUMMARY:</span></span></strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">The Legal Invoice Analyst for client, Fulfilment Center of Excellence will be responsible for performing the quality assurance testing for the Legal Bill Analysis Center of Excellence (LBACOE). </span></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Understanding of legal terminology and claims legal situations, multijurisdictional exposure preferred.</span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">Using sound discretion and legal expertise, analyze and condense legal service agreements to produce effective operational outputs meeting and in some cases exceeding customer expectations.</span> </ul> <br class="Apple-interchange-newline">]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Minneapolis]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[MN]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Legal ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Legal Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Warehouse Sr. Business Analyst (34075)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 29, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[RIQVWCHUFE]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[34075]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;"><strong>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) has a direct client in Springfield, IL in need of a Data Warehouse BA for a REMOTE, long-term contract. Travel to Springfield may be required 2-4 times/year. Qualified candidates please provide resume. <br> <br> Functional Description: </strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">We are seeking a highly motivated Senior Business Analyst to support a large-scale Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) project. This role will serve as a critical liaison between business stakeholders and technical teams, ensuring that data warehouse solutions align with business goals. This role involves gathering and translating business requirements into functional specifications, supporting data modeling efforts, and facilitating testing and validation of data warehouse deliverables.</span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;"><strong> </strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;"><strong>Primary Responsibilities </strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Collaborate with business users, data engineers, and BI developers to define and document business and data requirements. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Analyze existing data sources and business processes to identify gaps and opportunities for improvement. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Translate business needs into detailed functional and technical specifications for data warehouse development. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Support the design and implementation of ETL processes, interfaces, data marts, reports, and data analytics. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Work with our testing team to develop and execute test plans to validate data accuracy and integrity. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Facilitate user acceptance testing (UAT) and ensure stakeholder sign-off. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Create and maintain documentation including data dictionaries, process flows, and reporting specifications. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Act as a subject matter expert on data warehouse capabilities and best practices. </span></span></span> <li style="margin-top: 0.0in;margin-right: 0.0in;margin-bottom: 12.0pt;margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Support change management and training efforts related to new data solutions. </span></span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;"><strong>Required Qualifications: </strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Bachelor’s degree or higher degree in business intelligence, analytics, computer science, engineering, or related STEM field. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">5+ years of healthcare business analysis experience supporting business initiatives through data analysis, writing business requirements and supporting testing of various systems. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Good understanding of Fee for Service (FFS), Managed Care claim adjudication processes from eligibility and enrollment to claims processing to funding/finance. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Experience working on a Medicaid Enterprise System (MES)/MMIS, or EDW DDI or equivalent. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Proficient in MS Word, MS Excel, MS Project, SharePoint, Teams, and MS PowerPoint. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Be a self-starter and able to thrive in an environment with little guidance. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Excellent interpersonal, oral, and written communication skills. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Ability to effectively communicate findings clearly and concisely in writing and verbally to both technical and non-technical audiences </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Ability to work in a challenging environment with multiple teams and competing priorities </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Experience with facilitating meetings. </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Effective organizational, analytical, time management, problem-solving, and multi-tasking skills </span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0in 0.0in 0.7pt 0.5pt;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;">Ability to complete assignments under tight deadlines with little/no direct supervision. </span></span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Calibri , sans-serif;"><span style="color: black;"> </span></span></span><br>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Springfied]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Illinois]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Analyst ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior AWS Cloud Project Manager (32652)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 22, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[MSO9O8BV2R]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32652]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Job Title: Sr AWS Cloud Project Manager </span></span></strong></span></span><br> <strong>Location:</strong> Waukegan, IL (3 days onsite)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Myticas's direct client based in North Chicago, IL<br> <br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Duration: 5</span></span></strong><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;">+ months<span style="color: black;"> (with a possibility of extension)</span></span></strong></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">TOP Skills:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span> <ol> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 0.0cm 36.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(29,45,62);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">5-10 years of experience of technical project management.</span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 0.0cm 36.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(29,45,62);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Ability to lead cross-functional teams and manage multiple stakeholders effectively.</span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 0.0cm 36.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(29,45,62);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience with <strong>cloud platforms, especially AWS</strong></span></span><strong>.</strong></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm 0.0cm 0.0cm 36.0pt;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(29,45,62);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience managing SDLC projects.</span></span></span></span></span> </ol> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Primary Function:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Develop, execute, and manage multiple IT projects within their defined scope(s). Manage a multitude of interrelated project activities and lead all aspects of the project lifecycle, working with project sponsors/key stakeholders, team members, and management to oversee all phases of project completion. Build and manage project’s work breakdown structure, milestones, risks, issues, and deliverables within the constraints of human and financial resources and changing priorities to ensure the successful completion of the project. Ensure transparent reporting of project status, issues, risks, and financials.</span></span></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Key Responsibilities:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Initiate and Plan Project:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Collaborate with business and IT management to establish project goals, objectives, financials, and deliverables.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Build and manage the project plan, resources, and Gantt charts to accomplish the project scope.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Control and Quality Management:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Evaluate scope changes, issues, and risks, working with stakeholders to resolve them.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Measure performance against the original plan and budget, ensuring compliance with corporate and functional policies and procedures.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Maintain and update the RAID log to track project risks, actions, and issues.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Execute and Close Project:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Develop and execute work plans, securing authorized resources to complete all activities.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Lead the team in delivering the project scope, gather lessons learned, and obtain final project approval.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Assist in managing the process to ensure all validation deliverables are completed.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Communication:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Produce and distribute project reports to provide accurate status and decision support to stakeholders.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Make recommendations to resolve issues and manage risks based on the current project status.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Resource and Team Management:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Coordinate and assign resources to ensure project needs are met, effectively assign tasks based on team members’ abilities.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Motivate the project team to achieve desired outcomes.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Decisions and Financial Control:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Make decisions impacting project-level activities; influence or have authority over the project budget.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Develop and manage a financial plan, maintaining spend within +/- 10% of the overall budget.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Track and update financials in Clarity, coordinating estimates and invoices with vendors.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Vendor Coordination:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Coordinate vendor activities and ensure timely milestone delivery.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Ensure vendor purchase orders (POs) are processed promptly.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Meetings:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style="list-style-type: circle;"> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Facilitate Project Management meetings to oversee execution activities with IT System Owner and Principal Business Systems Consultant.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Qualifications:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Bachelor’s degree in business, Information Systems/Computer Science or related discipline.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Proven Microsoft Project, PowerPoint, Excel, and Word skills are required.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">5-10 years of experience in Information Technology project management.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Proven experience with <strong><u>cloud platforms, especially AWS</u></strong>, experience with on-premise HPC clusters, and familiarity with data management tools and best practices a must</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience managing SDLC projects.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Flexibility needed while collaborating with the global project team and vendors (eg 7 AM meetings and /or 4 pm meetings).</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Preferred Qualifications:</span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">PMP Certification</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">PPM Tool experience</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Pharmaceutical experience</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience managing projects to deliver or enhance validated systems.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Key Stakeholders:</span></span></span></strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Business and Technology resources; varying levels of leadership.</span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[IL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Project Management ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Information Technology and Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Systems Administrator/Trainer (32661)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 24, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[I6708ZKCYB]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32661]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Technical Systems Administrator / Trainer<br> <strong>Location:</strong> Irvine, CA (Dupont Drive) – Hybrid (3 days onsite, 2 days remote)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Myticas’s direct client based in Irvine, CA<br> <strong>Duration:</strong> 12+ months (possibility of extension)</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Top Skills, Experience, and Education Required:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>2–4 years of experience with SharePoint, including site creation and administration</p> <li> <p>2–4 years of professional experience in one or more of the following roles:</p> <ul> </ul><li> <p>Functional Systems Administrator</p> <li> <p>Configuration Manager</p> <li> <p>Solution Architect</p> <li> <p>Project Manager</p> <li> <p>Consultant</p> <li> <p>Trainer</p> </ul> <li> <p>At least 2 years of experience administering Atlassian products (Confluence or Jira preferred)</p> <li> <p>Strong interpersonal and relationship-building skills</p> <li> <p>Proven ability to communicate effectively and partner with key stakeholders</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Job Summary:</strong></h3> <p>Our client is seeking a <strong>Technical Systems Administrator / Trainer</strong> to support the development, management, and daily operations of SharePoint sites and Atlassian tools. This role plays a critical part in enhancing user adoption, building effective training programs, and optimizing system workflows.</p> <p>You will provide hands-on support to users, lead training initiatives, and act as a technical liaison across teams to ensure the platforms are being used efficiently and effectively. Your responsibilities will include system administration, process improvement, user onboarding, and cross-functional collaboration to drive tool adoption and process scalability.</p> <p>The ideal candidate is experienced in SharePoint and Atlassian products, thrives in a dynamic environment, enjoys solving complex problems, and excels in working with a diverse team.</p> <hr> <h3><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>Collaborate with Business Technology and Implementation teams to identify customization opportunities and optimize SharePoint usage</p> <li> <p>Build and configure SharePoint sites and folder structures tailored to specific business needs</p> <li> <p>Serve as the primary administrator for SharePoint and Atlassian (Confluence, Jira), ensuring system functionality, content quality, and process alignment</p> <li> <p>Generate and distribute regular and ad hoc reports to measure system performance and KPIs</p> <li> <p>Design and document workflows, processes, and best practices for system usage</p> <li> <p>Translate business requirements into system enhancements and workflow improvements</p> <li> <p>Assess and recommend integration opportunities for additional tools and platforms</p> <li> <p>Work closely with IT to test, implement, and maintain system updates and functionalities</p> <li> <p>Lead special projects, including training development, project management, and system reporting</p> <li> <p>Conduct training sessions and maintain user support documentation</p> <li> <p>Liaise with vendors for technical support and coordinate training resources</p> <li> <p>Promote proper system usage and best practices among team members</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>2–4 years of experience building and managing SharePoint sites</p> <li> <p>2–4 years of professional experience in a systems administration, training, or related role</p> <li> <p>Creative problem-solving skills with a focus on workflow optimization</p> <li> <p>Ability to lead projects, manage deadlines, and balance multiple priorities</p> <li> <p>Strong communication and collaboration skills with the ability to influence stakeholders</p> <li> <p>Demonstrated ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment</p> </ul> <hr> <h3><strong>Preferred Qualifications (Nice to Have):</strong></h3> <ul> <li> <p>1–2 years of experience administering Atlassian tools (Confluence, Jira)</p> <li> <p>Experience using APIs to build tool integrations (e.g., Slack API, Jira API)</p> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Irvine]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[CA]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Information Technology ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Technical Product Manager (34086)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 31, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[FSZH4BPVI8]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[34086]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Job Title: Senior Technical Product Manager</strong><br> <strong>Location: Coppell, TX (Hybrid)</strong><br> <strong>Type: Contract (W2 Only)</strong></p> <p><strong>About the Role:</strong><br> Myticas is seeking a <strong>Senior Technical Product Manager</strong> to support our direct client in Coppell, TX. This is a hybrid contract position available exclusively on a W2 basis.</p> <p>The Senior Technical Product Manager will serve as the critical link between customers, internal stakeholders, and development teams. This role involves deeply understanding customer needs, translating strategic product vision into actionable development tasks, and leading cross-functional collaboration to ensure the successful delivery of software solutions.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li> <p>Develop a comprehensive understanding of the product vision, target customer segments, and long-term priorities, while ensuring alignment with senior leadership and stakeholders.</p> <li> <p>Partner with internal teams—including engineering, marketing, sales, implementation, training, and support—to gather insights, align priorities, and ensure effective product development and launch execution.</p> <li> <p>Serve as the voice of the customer, working closely with UX and development teams to validate and refine solutions throughout the development lifecycle.</p> <li> <p>Conduct and facilitate customer engagements, in collaboration with UX teams, to explore unmet needs and test concepts and prototypes.</p> <li> <p>Translate business requirements into user stories and detailed acceptance criteria for development teams.</p> <li> <p>Lead Agile ceremonies including backlog grooming, sprint planning, and sprint reviews, ensuring outcomes align with business objectives.</p> <li> <p>Drive quarterly Agile planning and continuously build subject matter expertise to identify and implement product improvements.</p> <li> <p>Maintain and evolve detailed product roadmaps, prioritizing features across multiple quarters.</p> <li> <p>Coordinate with project managers and other product managers to manage dependencies, monitor progress, and adjust plans to stay on track.</p> <li> <p>Proactively manage cross-functional risks and dependencies to drive continuous improvement and team alignment.</p> <li> <p>Monitor product performance and track key performance indicators (KPIs) to assess impact and adjust strategies accordingly.</p> <li> <p>Review completed development work to validate acceptance criteria, ensuring products meet expectations and deliver value.</p> <li> <p>Perform other duties as assigned by the supervisor.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Education:</strong><br> Bachelor’s degree in Business Administration, Information Systems, Business Management, or a related field. Equivalent practical experience will be considered.</p> <p><strong>Required Qualifications and Experience:</strong></p> <ul> <li> <p>Minimum of 5 years of experience as a Senior Product Manager.</p> <li> <p>Minimum of 3 years of product management experience for software products, preferably in B2B enterprise SaaS or Tax & Accounting domains (CPA firm experience a plus).</p> <li> <p>Proven hands-on experience with Agile Scrum methodologies in a Product Owner or Technical Product Manager capacity.</p> <li> <p>Strong understanding of the software development lifecycle, including backlog management, user story writing, and iterative development planning.</p> <li> <p>Demonstrated ability to work closely with UX and technical teams to design and refine products based on user research and testing.</p> </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Skills and Competencies:</strong></p> <ul> <li> <p><strong>Strategic Thinking & Influence:</strong> Ability to align stakeholders, manage competing priorities, and drive a cohesive product vision.</p> <li> <p><strong>Data-Driven Decision-Making:</strong> Skilled in leveraging data and customer insights to inform product strategy and decisions.</p> <li> <p><strong>Technical Fluency & Problem Solving:</strong> Capable of translating complex business requirements into clear, actionable development tasks.</p> <li> <p><strong>Agility & Adaptability:</strong> Comfortable working in a fast-paced, changing environment with the flexibility to shift priorities as needed.</p> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Coppell]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[TX]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Business &amp; Program Management Consultant (32660)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 24, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[EWGRQQOWGF]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32660]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<strong>Senior Business & Program Management Consultant (GxP/Clinical)</strong><br> <strong>Location:</strong> Waukegan, IL (3 days onsite)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Myticas's direct client based in North Chicago, IL<br> <br> <u><strong>MUST Have:</strong></u> <ol> <li>8-10 years of Senior IT project experience: System Lifecycle (SLC) Expertise. <li><strong>GXP system</strong> experience required - GXP system implementation including custom development and validated systems. <li>Portfolio / <strong>Program management experience.</strong> <li><strong>Clinical Systems</strong> <li>Project financial management, and vendor management expertise. </ol> <br> <strong>Description:</strong><br> Senior Business Management Consultant to manage and drive all aspects of TWO in-flight system development (custom build) and enhancement projects, complete contracting / pre-SLC assessments for new projects, and assess new business capability requests.<br> <br> <strong>Required:</strong> <ul> <li>8-10 years of Senior IT project experience: System Lifecycle (SLC) Expertise, Portfolio / Program management experience, project financial management expertise, vendor management expertise. <li>Must have the ability to create / review SLC documents <li>Track record of successful GXP system implementation including custom development and validated systems. <li>GXP system experience required, <li>Clinical experience strongly preferred <li>Methodology used: Waterfall and Agile </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[IL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Consulting ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Biotechnology ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Local to Chicago-Sr Business Systems Analyst (32632)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 16, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[T4Z7ADCTG1]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32632]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">Myticas direct client is seeking Business Systems Analyst with QA experience at </span></span></span></span><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Waukegan, IL <strong>(Hybrid-3 days onsite)</strong></span></span></span></span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Duration: </span></span></strong><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);">5 months</span></span></strong><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;"> (with a possibility of extension)</span></span></strong></span></span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Description</span></span></span></strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">The BSA/QA will play a critical role in bridging the gap between business needs and technology solutions. This individual will work closely with the project team and stakeholders to understand their business requirements and do document them in User Stories to then be developed. The BSA/QA will create test cases for user stories and will execute these tests and clearly documenting results and creating defects where needed.</span></span></span></span></span></span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Key Responsibilities:</span></span></span></strong></span></span></span> <ul> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Collaborate with business stakeholders to gather and document detailed business requirements and functional specifications.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Analyze existing business processes, identify areas for improvement, and evaluate potential solutions to increase efficiency and effectiveness.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Assist in the design and implementation of software solutions that meet the business needs and integrate with existing systems where necessary.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Develop test plans and coordinate testing efforts to ensure that solutions meet business requirements and provide a high level of quality.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Create and maintain comprehensive documentation including process flows, business rules, and user guides.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Work closely with project managers and other team members to ensure timely delivery of project milestones and resolution of any issues that may arise.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Serve as a liaison between the IT department and business units by communicating project status, changes, and potential impacts to stakeholders.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Perform manual testing of software applications to ensure they meet user requirements.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Extensive experience on different types of testing that includes Functional testing, System Integration testing, Regression testing and UAT.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Experience in Agile/Scrum Environments on multiple Projects.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Experience in developing test plans, strategies, and test Scenarios.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Create, execute, and maintain test cases and test scripts. Collaborate with the development team to address and resolve identified issues in a timely manner.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="">Expertise in using JIRA for writing the Test Cases and tracking the Defects.</span></span></span></span></span></span> <li class="elementtoproof" style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;margin-right: 0.0cm;"><span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style=""><span style="color: rgb(66,66,66);">Excellent Communication skills-Verbal and written.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span> </ul> <br> <br>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[IL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Analyst ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Information Technology and Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr Program Management Consultant (32608)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 14, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[44FXXDNL8E]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32608]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Sr Project Management Consultant </strong><br> <strong>Location:</strong> Waukegan, IL (3 days onsite)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Myticas&apos;s direct client based in North Chicago, IL</p> <hr><u><strong>NOTE:</strong></u><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style=""><em><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">**Need a seasoned, <strong><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">higher level Program Management Consultant/Program Leader</span></strong>-</span></span></em></span><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><em><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">managing multiple programs/projects.</span></span></span></em></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">Job Summary </span></span></u></strong></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="color: black;">One of our Direct clients is looking to add a Seasoned Sr Project/Program Management Consultant to their team. </span></span></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Primary Function:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Develop, execute, and manage multiple IT projects within their defined scope(s). Manage a multitude of interrelated project activities and lead all aspects of the project lifecycle, working with project sponsors/key stakeholders, team members, and management to oversee all phases of project completion. Build and manage project’s work breakdown structure, milestones, risks, issues, and deliverables within the constraints of human and financial resources and changing priorities to ensure the successful completion of the project. Ensure transparent reporting of project status, issues, risks, and financials.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Key Responsibilities:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span></span> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Initiate and Plan Project:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Build and manage the project plan, resources, and Gantt charts to accomplish the project scope.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Collaborate with business and IT management to establish project goals, objectives, financials, and deliverables.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Control and Quality Management:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Maintain and update the RAID log to track project risks, actions, and issues.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Measure performance against the original plan and budget, ensuring compliance with corporate and functional policies and procedures.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Evaluate scope changes, issues, and risks, working with stakeholders to resolve them.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Execute and Close Project:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Assist in managing the process to ensure all validation deliverables are completed.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Lead the team in delivering the project scope, gather lessons learned, and obtain final project approval.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Develop and execute work plans, securing authorized resources to complete all activities.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Communication:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Make recommendations to resolve issues and manage risks based on the current project status.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Produce and distribute project reports to provide accurate status and decision support to stakeholders.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Resource and Team Management:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Motivate the project team to achieve desired outcomes.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Coordinate and assign resources to ensure project needs are met, effectively assign tasks based on team members’ abilities.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Decisions and Financial Control:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Track and update financials in Clarity, coordinating estimates and invoices with vendors.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Develop and manage a financial plan, maintaining spend within +/- 10% of the overall budget.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Make decisions impacting project-level activities; influence or have authority over the project budget.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Vendor Coordination:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Ensure vendor purchase orders (POs) are processed promptly.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Coordinate vendor activities and ensure timely milestone delivery.</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Project Meetings:</span></span> </ul> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Facilitate Project Management meetings to oversee execution activities with IT System Owner and Principal Business Systems Consultant.</span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><u><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Qualifications:</span></span></span></u></strong></span></span></span></span> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Bachelor’s degree in business, Information Systems/Computer Science or related discipline.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Proven Microsoft Project, PowerPoint, Excel, and Word skills are required.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">5-10 years of experience in Information Technology project management.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience managing SDLC projects.</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Flexibility needed while collaborating with the global project team and vendors (eg 7 AM meetings and /or 4 pm meetings).</span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Preferred Qualifications:</span></span></span></span></span></span></span> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">PMP Certification</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">PPM Tool experience</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Pharmaceutical experience</span></span> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Experience managing projects to deliver or enhance validated systems.</span></span> </ul> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"> </span></span></span></span><br> <span style="font-size: 10.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><span style="color: rgb(33,33,33);"><strong><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;"><span style="color: black;">Key Stakeholders:</span></span></span></strong></span></span></span></span> <ul style=""> <li style="margin: 0.0cm;font-size: 10.0pt;font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;color: black;background: white;vertical-align: baseline;"><span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"><span style="background-color: white;">Business and Technology resources; varying levels of leadership.</span></span> </ul> <p><br> This is a hybrid position requiring both remote and onsite work in Waukegan, IL.</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[IL]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MYT]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Project Management ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Information Technology and Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[EDW Informatica ETL Developer (32541)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 13, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[OP0KXY7DHU]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32541]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>EDW Informatica ETL Developer </strong></p> <p><strong>Job Title: </strong>Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) Informatica ETL Developer</p> <p><strong>Duration: </strong>12 months with possible multi-year extension/s</p> <p><strong>Job Summary: </strong></p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is are seeking a highly experienced Informatica Extract Transform Load (ETL) Developer for a large, direct client in Springfield, IL. This opportunity will be an assent to the Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) team.</p> <p>This role is responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining robust ETL processes using Informatica PowerCenter and Teradata. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of data integration, performance tuning, and data warehousing best practices, with a focus on supporting healthcare-related data systems.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities: </strong></p> <ul> <li>Design and implement ETL solutions using Informatica PowerCenter to extract, transform, and load data from various agency sources. <li>Automate data staging processes and optimize ETL job scheduling for performance and efficiency. <li>Administer and support ETL environments, including development and production systems. <li>Perform repository backups, recovery operations, and system maintenance. <li>Develop mappings, mapplets, sessions, and workflows using a wide range of Informatica transformations. <li>Monitor and troubleshoot ETL jobs across development, testing, and production environments. <li>Write and optimize complex SQL queries and Unix Shell scripts for data marts and interfaces in Teradata. <li>Collaborate with stakeholders to define requirements, document technical solutions, and support project planning. <li>Participate in unit, integration, and system testing. <li>Provide technical support, mentoring, and guidance to team members. <li>Communicate project status and deliverables to leadership and clients. <li>Continuously learn and apply new technologies to enhance system performance and capabilities. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>7+ years of experience with Informatica PowerCenter and ETL development. <li>5+ years of experience writing complex SQL and performance tuning. <li>5+ years of experience with Teradata (v17+), including Fastload, TPT, and Multiload utilities. <li>5+ years of Informatica PowerCenter administration experience. <li>2+ years of Unix Shell (Bash/Korn) scripting experience. <li>Strong communication, collaboration, and mentoring skills. <li>Bachelor’s or advanced degree in IT, Computer Science, Mathematics, or a related field. <li>Strong organizational and time management skills. 2025 Page 1 of 2 Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) ETL/Informatica Developer </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications: </strong></p> <ul> <li>Residing in or near Springfield, IL. <li>5+ years of data warehouse development experience. <li>5+ years of data modeling experience using ERWIN or similar tools. <li>2+ years of experience with Azure Data Factory and Snowflake. <li>Experience with scripting languages such as Python, R, or JavaScript (React). <li>Familiarity with Informatica Data Quality (IDQ), Address Doctor, and Metadata Manager. <li>Experience with Medicaid, Medicare, or healthcare data systems. <li>Experience working in Agile environments. <li>Knowledge of BI and data integration technologies across relational and multidimensional systems. </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Illinois]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Information Technology ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Computer Software ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Support and Customer Service Associate (32581)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 30, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[88HRSO0VM8]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32581]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<strong>Technical Support and Customer Service Associate </strong><strong>- REMOTE<br> <br> Contract: 12 months with possible CTH</strong><br> <strong>Schedule: 3rd shift - 12 am to 9 am, Tuesday thru Saturday<br> Work Type: Fully Remote</strong><br> <br> Myticas is actively seeking a <strong>Technical Support and </strong><strong>Customer Service Associate </strong>for a direct client to join their <strong>Personal Support Center (PSC)</strong> team. This role is perfect for someone with a passion for helping others, a knack for troubleshooting, and the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, tech-forward environment.<br> <br> As a PSC Associate, you’ll be the first point of contact for users via phone, email, and chat—working to resolve technical issues, answer questions, and ensure a seamless customer experience. You'll be supported by extensive training, a detailed knowledge base, and a collaborative team ready to help you grow.<br> <br> <strong>What You’ll Do:</strong> <ul> <li>Provide Tier 1 technical support for software, hardware, and connectivity issues <li>Assist with password resets, software installations, VPN setups, and general troubleshooting <li>Escalate complex issues to senior team members when needed <li>Maintain clear, professional communication across all customer interactions <li>Simultaneously manage support requests via phone, email, and chat <li>Accurately log cases using tools like ServiceNow and Zendesk </ul> <strong>What We’re Looking For:</strong> <ul> <li>Strong customer service and communication skills <li>Comfort working in a flexible, 24/7/365 support environment <li>Ability to adapt to new tools, systems, and processes quickly <li>Team player who’s open to ongoing feedback, learning, and development </ul> <strong>Why Join Us:</strong> <ul> <li>Hands-on training and mentoring <li>Access to a robust internal knowledge base <li>Opportunities to collaborate with tech experts and leadership <li>A supportive team environment where growth is encouraged </ul> If you're ready to jump into a dynamic support role where no two days are the same, apply now or reach out to learn more. We’re excited to meet you!]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city/>
    <state/>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-MC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Customer Service ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Consumer Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Associate ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Digital Content Specialist (32576)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 26, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[PPJOZ5REX5]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32576]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Job Title: Digital Content Specialist</strong><br> <strong>Location:</strong> On-Site – Grand Rapids, MI<br> <strong>Contract Duration:</strong> 6+ Months (Extensions Likely)<br> <strong>Company:</strong> Clover Consulting (a Myticas Company)<br> <strong>Client:</strong> Direct Client in Grand Rapids, MI<br> <strong>Note:</strong> Local candidates preferred. This role is not eligible for sponsorship.</p> <p><strong>Job Overview:</strong><br> Clover Consulting is seeking a <strong>Digital Content Specialist</strong> to support our client’s marketing efforts in Grand Rapids, MI. This is a full-time, on-site contract opportunity with a strong possibility of extension. The successful candidate will assist in the development and execution of CRM campaigns using a newly implemented customer 360 database and marketing automation platform.</p> <p><strong>About the Team:</strong><br> The North American CRM team designs and implements marketing strategies that leverage automation software to enhance lead generation, sales, retention, productivity, and customer loyalty—particularly focused on Independent Business Owners (IBOs) and consumers.</p> <p><strong>Role Summary:</strong><br> As a Digital Content Specialist, you will be responsible for supporting the planning, development, deployment, and analysis of CRM campaigns. These communications target IBOs, customers, or a combination of both. Your primary responsibility is to ensure all campaigns are executed accurately and on schedule.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Serve as the main liaison between internal stakeholders, external agencies, and the CRM production team. <li>Manage CRM campaign deliverables, including planning, timelines, risk management, and resource allocation. <li>Submit use cases and other documentation for internal review and approval. <li>Schedule creative briefings and manage content development updates. <li>Route creative materials, compile proof comments, and finalize HTML content for translation. <li>Conduct thorough quality assurance checks on email content in all supported languages and markets (including verification of links, artwork, and videos). <li>Educate stakeholders on the capabilities of the CRM platform. <li>Track campaign progress and update timelines and work estimates as needed. <li>Distribute final CRM creative assets to internal stakeholders for reference. <li>Provide on-call support for end-of-month and urgent field email communications, per established protocols. <li>Serve as a backup to the Email Coordinator. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Associate&apos;s or Bachelor’s degree in Marketing, Communications, or a related field; equivalent certifications will also be considered. <li>Minimum of 2 years of experience in Communications, Marketing, or a related discipline. <li>Basic knowledge of CRM platforms. <li>Ability to independently resolve routine issues. <li>Capable of performing assigned tasks and supporting projects under supervision. </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Skills and Attributes:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Strong passion for marketing and delivering a top-tier user experience to engage both customers and IBOs. <li>Solid understanding of email marketing strategies, triggered campaigns, and A/B testing to optimize business performance. <li>Proven ability to collaborate effectively with internal teams and external vendors. <li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills. <li>Strong organizational skills with the ability to manage multiple priorities in a fast-paced environment. <li>Flexible and able to perform well under pressure and tight deadlines. <li>Critical thinking, problem-solving, and follow-through skills. <li>High level of professionalism and attention to detail. <li>Ability to work independently and as part of a team. <li>Willingness and ability to work on-site at the client location in Grand Rapids, MI. </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Ada]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Michigan]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Onsite]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-CC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Marketing ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Consumer Services ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineer (32643)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 21, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[FOM1070B58]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32643]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) has a direct client in Grand Rapids, MI in need of a MANUFACTURING ENGINEER - willing to consider all experience levels - this is a contract role to start, with conversion to perm the goal. <br> <br> <br> Planned 2nd shift hours of 4pm-12pm/1am, to support production.<br> <br> We are hiring Associate to Sr. Manufacturing Engineer to lead and provide ongoing support through our manufacturing life cycle!<br> <br> What You Will Be Doing:<br> With general direction, will lead the introduction of new products into the facility, improve productivity and profitability of existing production procedures, and provide ongoing support through the manufacturing life cycle. Acts as a technical expert in process technology<br> <br> <em>Improvements:</em> Independently, with innovation and creativity, evaluates manufacturing processes to ensure optimal labor and material costs to increase productivity and profitability. Through justifications and evaluations, identifies prime areas for improvement. Tracks expenditures to ensure outlays are within budgeted amounts. Identifies, reduces, and eliminates worker exposure(s) to ergonomic stress(es) in the work place.<br> <br> <em>Floor Support</em>: Provides timely product and process support for any manufacturing area to diagnose problems and implement solutions to minimize interruptions to production.<br> <br> <em>Special Projects</em>: Leads the implementation of significant product, process, or other corporate change initiatives being introduced into the plant.<br> <br> <em>Strategic/Manufacturing Planning:</em> Provides advanced research to introduce/integrate new processes, equipment, and technologies into the company<br> <br> <br> Who You Are:<br> Preferred Skills and Competencies <ul> <li>Very strong analysis skills: process, capacity, cost/benefit, waste stream, and quality tools. <li>Internal and external quality support/management <li>Knowledge in lean manufacturing techniques: flow, PQ, equipment reliability, and set up reduction. <li>Facilitation and negotiation skills <li>Knowledge of material handling <li>Productivity improvement techniques: RCI’s <li>Behavior sciences (logic, sociology, etc.) <li>Economics and financial analysis <li>Work measurement <li>Interpersonal skills <li>Computer skills; advanced level required to utilize Excel and Access programs <li>Experience in design, specification, purchase, and installation of new equipment <li>Experience in the Engineering Design Process <li>Knowledge of simulation, process modeling, and value stream mapping <li>Project management and leadership ability <li>Occupational Bio Mechanics/Human Factors Engineering <li>Strategic planning </ul> <br> Required Skills and Competencies <ul> <li>4 year technical degree or equivalent education </ul> <br>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract to Hire]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Grand Rapids]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Michigan]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Onsite]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-CC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Engineering ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Electrical/Electronic Manufacturing ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Digital Marketing Consultant (32563)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 23, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[1EABEN6CEH]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32563]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[Clover Consulting has a direct client in Grand Rapids, MI in need of a Digital Marketing Consulting to support Search Engine Optimization activities. This is an ON-SITE role starting as a 5 months contract, with likely extensions. Candidates local to the Grand Rapids area, are preferred. Qualified candidates please provide resume. Thank you!<br> <table id="Master_PageContentPlaceHolder_screen_selectedTab_beelineForm_generalSection_Body"> <tbody> <tr id="Master_PageContentPlaceHolder_screen_selectedTab_beelineForm_jobDescriptionTextRow"> <th id="Master_PageContentPlaceHolder_screen_selectedTab_beelineForm_jobDescriptionTextLabel">Job Description (Visible to Supplier):</th> <td>Digital Marketing Contractor – Job Responsibilities<br> <br> In response to evolving digital marketing priorities and the growing importance of AI in search, we are expanding the role of our current SEO lead and seeking a Digital Marketing Contractor to provide support for core SEO responsibilities. This role will help ensure continuity in execution and performance monitoring while allowing the team to focus on broader strategic initiatives. The contractor will support global SEO operations and partner with market teams to enhance visibility, discoverability, and performance across digital properties.<br> <br> Duration: July – December 2025, with potential extension<br> Location: Grand Rapids, MI (Onsite)<br> Reports to: Global SEO Lead<br> <br> Key Responsibilities<br> <br> Operational SEO Execution<br> • Conduct keyword research to support market-level needs and content planning.<br> • Perform technical SEO audits using tools like Ahrefs and Google Search Console.<br> • Support content optimization efforts, including metadata, on-page structure, and internal linking.<br> • Compile and deliver monthly SEO performance reports using platforms such as Ahrefs, Heap, and GSC.<br> • Troubleshoot SEO issues reported by markets and provide actionable solutions.<br> • Leverage AI tools and approaches to generate recommendations for content optimization, keyword discovery, link-building, and landing page refinement.<br> • Integrate AI-enabled tools to automate repetitive SEO tasks and improve execution speed and scalability.<br> <br> SEO Training and Enablement<br> • Assist in delivering SEO onboarding sessions and office hours for market teams.<br> • Help maintain and update SEO playbooks, best practices, and documentation on SharePoint.<br> • Create or revise modular self-serve resources to enable independent market optimization.<br> • Support the creation and management of a centralized SharePoint hub for training.<br> <br> Performance Monitoring and Insights<br> • Support organic search sentiment analysis and reputation tracking.<br> • Monitor and extract insights from dashboards (Heap, Ahrefs) to identify trends and risks.<br> • Assist in evaluating SEO impact for major product launches and post-launch performance reviews.<br> • Apply AI-powered tools to surface deeper insights from large-scale performance data.<br> <br> Collaboration and Coordination<br> • Work cross-functionally with content, analytics, and technical teams to integrate SEO best practices.<br> • Participate in global team meetings or planning sessions to ensure SEO considerations are included.<br> • Escalate technical SEO issues or strategic risks to the Global SEO Lead.<br> <br> Tool and Vendor Support<br> • Assist with user access management, licensing coordination, and onboarding for SEO tools.<br> • Support evaluations of SEO tool usage and effectiveness.<br> • Coordinate with vendors to troubleshoot issues or implement platform improvements.<br> <br> ?<br> <br> Qualifications<br> • 5+ years of experience in digital marketing and hands-on SEO in global or multi-market settings.<br> • Proficiency with SEO tools like Heap, Ahrefs, Google Search Console, and Lumar (or equivalent).<br> • Strong analytical skills; able to turn performance data into clear, actionable insights.<br> • Excellent writing and editing skills, with an understanding of search-optimized content.<br> • Demonstrated experience creating or reviewing metadata, headers, and on-page copy for SEO.<br> • Familiarity with CMS platforms and technical SEO concepts (indexing, crawling, Core Web Vitals).<br> • Strong understanding of how AI can be applied to SEO (e.g., prompt engineering, content summarization, automated content audits, keyword clustering).<br> • Experience working with cross-functional teams across content, marketing, and tech.<br> • Ability to work independently, manage multiple priorities, and adapt in a fast-paced environment.<br> </td> </tr> </tbody> </table>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Ada]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Michigan]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category/>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Onsite]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[#LI-CC]]></assignedrecruiter><jobfunction><![CDATA[ Consulting ]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[ Marketing and Advertising ]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[ Mid-Senior level ]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  </source>
