<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<source>
  <publisherurl><![CDATA[https://myticas.com]]></publisherurl>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Business Objects SQL Developer (32539)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 13, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[L7G0OI7S2P]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32539]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/SQL Developer </strong></p> <p><strong>Job Title:</strong> Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/SQL Developer</p> <p><strong>Location:</strong> Remote (with occasional travel to Springfield, IL)</p> <p><strong>Contract: </strong>12 months with possibly multiyear extension/s</p> <p><strong>Functional Description: </strong></p> <p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is seeking a skilled and experienced BI BusinessObjects/SQL Developer to design, develop, and maintain business intelligence solutions using SAP BusinessObjects and SQL. This role supports Medicaid/CHIP claims and other healthcare data systems, ensuring accurate reporting and data integrity for state and federal stakeholders.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Design, develop, and maintain BusinessObjects reports using Medicaid/CHIP claims and subsystem data. <li>Write, optimize, and maintain complex SQL scripts and queries for data marts and reporting. <li>Create and manage BusinessObjects Universes and metadata layers. <li>Develop and maintain database systems to support efficient data storage and reporting. <li>Manage server backups and ensure system reliability. <li>Collaborate with stakeholders to gather requirements and recommend technical solutions. <li>Participate in unit, integration, and system testing. <li>Provide regular project updates to customers and maintain strong communication. <li>Mentor junior team members and provide technical training as needed. <li>Stay current with emerging technologies and industry best practices. <li>Perform additional duties as required to support project and organizational goals. </ul> <p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p> <ul> <li>5+ years of experience in SAP BusinessObjects development and reporting including report Universe designing. <li>5+ years of SQL development, including 4+ years of performance tuning. <li>2+ years of experience in data warehouse projects. <li>2+ years of experience with Teradata (v15+), including SQL Assistant. <li>Strong communication skills and the ability to work directly with clients. <li>Bachelor’s or advanced degree in IT, Computer Science, Mathematics, Statistics, or a related field. <li>Excellent organizational skills and ability to manage multiple priorities. <li>Strong team collaboration and adaptability. </ul> <p><strong>Preferred Qualifications: </strong></p> <ul> <li>2+ years of experience as Business Objects server administrator <li>Familiarity with Medicaid, Medicare, or healthcare-related applications. <li>Experience with Tableau or BusinessObjects version upgrades. 2025 Business Intelligence (BI) Business Objects/S </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Illinois]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[Dan Sifer]]></assignedrecruiter>
    <jobfunction><![CDATA[Business Intelligence]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[Information Technology and Services]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[Mid-Senior level]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Drupal Developer (32659)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[July 24, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[4AW6G48TSI]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32659]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>The recruitment team at Myticas Consulting is looking for an experienced Drupal Developer who would be interested in a long-term remote contract opportunity offered within Canada (originally headquartered in Ottawa, ON).</p> <p><strong>Previous experience required:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Experience building web applications in the Drupal (7) CMS <li>Understands key server-side web development concepts through experiences such as: <li>Interpreting graphic visual or interaction designs in HTML, CSS and Javascript. <li>Creating visually appealing web pages or interfaces. <li>Creating, editing or modifying templates for a CMS or web development framework. <li>Programming interaction with JavaScript and/or a lipary such as jQuery, YUI or Prototype. <li>Testing cross-powser, cross-platform, and/or cross-device compatibility for inconsistencies. <li>Testing for compliance to specified standards such as accessibility standards (WCAG 2.0) in the clients region or domain. <li>Conducting observational user testing, or reviewing designs against usability heuristics. <li>Domain specific knowledge or transferable skills <li>Experience with web development languages of HTML, CSS and JavaScript/jQuery. <li>HTML <ul> <li>Familiarity of HTML syntax for multiple specifications, including HTML 5. <li>Knowledge of the semantic meaning of all HTML elements. <li>Familiarity with the semantic markup for display of lists, tabular data, forms, articles, etc. <li>Knowledge of markup used for layout such as dividers. <li>Knowledge at the level to be able to hand-code markup. <li>Including media and images. </ul> <li>PHP <ul> <li>Familiarity with modifying Drupal Theme hooks to display data <li>Understanding how to utilize PHP to filter, process and output html, json, xml </ul> <li>CSS <ul> <li>Specifying different CSS for various media, devices and displays. <li>Best practices in CSS file organization and structure. <li>Methods for including CSS inline, internal and external via linked style sheets. <li>How to define, combine and group CSS selectors for HTML elements, ID, classes, pseudo classes, child or sibling. <li>Syntax of CSS declarations, properties and attributes. <li>CSS box model and methods for CSS positioning, absolute and relative. <li>Knowledge of properties and attributes to control the display. <li>Familiarity with differences in CSS 2 and CSS 3. <li>Proficient with a CSS Preprocessor such as Sass or LESS. </ul> <li>Best practices <ul> <li>Drupal standards and modules <li>Methods to ensure powser & device compatibility <li>Methods for degrading gracefully for older powsers and displays. <li>Methods to ensure accessibility. <li>File compression techniques for improving speed. </ul> <li>JavaScript <ul> <li>Knowledge of the operators, variables, datatypes, objects, properties and methods. <li>Familiarity with control structures such as objects, functions, conditional statements, arrays, loops and expressions. <li>Forms and regular expression validation and submitting data. <li>Knowledge of how to apply logical operators and conditional statements. <li>Knowledge of the DOM HTML objects and their properties. <li>Event handling. <li>Creating and controlling windows and dialogs. <li>Processes for troubleshooting and debugging <li>Familiarity with development and debugging tools for cross-powser issues. </ul> <li>jQuery <ul> <li>Knowledge of how to employ the jQuery lipary for visual effects, event handling, and document manipulation. </ul> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Ottawa]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[Ontario]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[Canada]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Remote]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[Mike Gebara]]></assignedrecruiter>
    <jobfunction><![CDATA[Web Development]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[Computer Software]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[Mid level]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior IT Project Manager (32567)]]></title>
    <company><![CDATA[Myticas Consulting]]></company>
    <date><![CDATA[June 23, 2025]]></date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[A3R5FJMZ7P]]></referencenumber>
    <bhatsid><![CDATA[32567]]></bhatsid>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url>
    <description><![CDATA[<span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Senior Project Manager (Contract)</strong></span></span><br> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Overview:</strong><br> <br> We are seeking an experienced Senior Project Manager to support the execution of multiple strategic initiatives within our client’s organization. This role is critical in ensuring the successful delivery of projects in alignment with business objectives, IT leadership direction, and established PMO frameworks.</span></span><br> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></span></span><br> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">As a Senior PM, you will work closely with business and technical stakeholders to steer initiatives from planning through to implementation, ensuring delivery is on time, within scope, and on budget. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to:</span></span><br> <ul> <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Project Planning & Scope Management:</strong><br> Define project scope and objectives in collaboration with sponsors and stakeholders. Develop detailed project schedules and comprehensive plans covering scope, timeline, budget, risk, change, communication, and quality management. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Execution & Oversight:</strong><br> Monitor project progress, manage cross-functional resources, and lead project execution according to established goals. Ensure effective team collaboration and resource alignment across all phases. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Risk & Issue Management:</strong><br> Identify, assess, and manage project risks and critical path dependencies. Escalate and resolve issues while maintaining transparency and governance. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Stakeholder Engagement & Reporting:</strong><br> Prepare and deliver executive-level updates, dashboards, and steering presentations. Facilitate workshops and status meetings; ensure stakeholder expectations are managed effectively throughout the project lifecycle. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Change Management Integration:</strong><br> Align with change management strategies to support adoption and ensure smooth transition of initiatives. Track implementation and address any business readiness concerns. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Governance & Quality Control:</strong><br> Ensure adherence to organizational PMO standards and best practices. Support continuous improvement efforts and implement lessons learned. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;"><strong>Business Case Support:</strong><br> Partner with business units and analysts to develop compelling business cases for project investment and benefits realization. </ul> <br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;"><strong>Qualifications & Skills:</strong></span></span><br> <br> <span style="font-size: 12.0pt;"><span style="font-family: Aptos , sans-serif;">We’re looking for candidates who bring both strategic foresight and executional discipline, with the following profile:</span></span><br> <ul> <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Business, IT Management, or a related discipline. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">PMP certification (or equivalent experience) is required. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">8–10 years of project management experience, with at least 5 years managing large-scale initiatives. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Proficient in project planning tools and methodologies. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Adept at managing matrixed teams and external vendors. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Excellent communication and stakeholder management skills. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Strong problem-solving capabilities and ability to navigate ambiguity. <li style="margin-top: 0.0cm;margin-bottom: 0.0cm;">Demonstrated ability to juggle multiple priorities while maintaining a focus on delivery and results. </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Contract]]></jobtype>
    <city><![CDATA[Ottawa]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[ON]]></state>
    <country><![CDATA[Canada]]></country>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[apply@myticas.com]]></apply_email>
    <remotetype><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></remotetype>
    <assignedrecruiter><![CDATA[Dominic Scaletta]]></assignedrecruiter>
    <jobfunction><![CDATA[Project Management]]></jobfunction>
    <jobindustries><![CDATA[Information Technology and Services]]></jobindustries>
    <senoritylevel><![CDATA[Senior level]]></senoritylevel>
  </job>
</source>
