<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<source>
  <publisher>Myticas Consulting Job Site</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://myticas.com/</publisherurl>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Banking Technology Integration Consultant (32606) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ July 11, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[21M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>We are seeking an experienced Banking Technology Integration Consultant (Lockbox/Payments) Implementation Specialist to support a large financial institution&rsquo;s transformation project.</p>
<p>This role focuses on the implementation and integration of cheque imaging, lockbox services, exception/returns handling, and ensuring compliance with North American regulatory requirements.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead and support the implementation of cheque processing technologies and lockbox solutions.</li>
<li>Conduct discovery sessions with business stakeholders and product owners.</li>
<li>Develop strategy, planning documentation, and ensure smooth technical integration.</li>
<li>Interface with vendors and internal stakeholders to gather requirements and deliver end-to-end solutions.</li>
<li>Ensure compliance with Canada and U.S. cheque processing regulations.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>10+ years of experience in financial services or banking technology.</li>
<li>Proven experience in cheque processing and lockbox solution implementation.</li>
<li>Familiarity with North American regulatory requirements.</li>
<li>Experience working at Symcor or implementing similar solutions in the U.S. is highly desirable.</li>
<li>Strong communication and stakeholder engagement skills.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Toronto ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior Technical Strategist (32522) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ July 10, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[20M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Senior Technical Strategist</strong></p>
<p>Location: Lansing, MI (Hybrid &ndash; On-site Tuesdays and Wednesdays)</p>
<p><strong>About the Role:</strong></p>
<p>Myticas' direct client, located in Lansing, MI, is seeking a&nbsp;<strong>Senior Technical Strategist</strong>&nbsp;to join their team on a hybrid schedule. The selected candidate will be required to work on-site two days per week (Tuesday and Wednesday).</p>
<p><strong>Please Note:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>This position is open to local candidates residing within a two-hour drive of Lansing, MI.</li>
<li>This is a hybrid role; remote-only options are not available.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Top Required Skills and Experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A minimum of 5 years of IT project management experience, preferably supporting large and complex technology initiatives.</li>
<li>A minimum of 5 years of experience providing Independent Verification and Validation (IV&amp;V) or equivalent quality assurance services.</li>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in Information Technology, Business Administration, Project Management, or a related field (required).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Preferred Skills and Certifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Project Management Professional (PMP) certification.</li>
<li>Additional certifications such as Certified ScrumMaster (CSM) or Certified Quality Auditor (CQA).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Position Summary:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Conduct IV&amp;V activities across assigned DTMB projects, ensuring objective, independent assessments of project health, deliverables, and compliance with DTMB standards.</li>
<li>Review critical project documentation, including charters, project management plans, schedules, risk registers, and contracts.</li>
<li>Evaluate deliverables for quality, completeness, and adherence to requirements.</li>
<li>Identify risks, issues, and deficiencies early, and recommend effective mitigation strategies.</li>
<li>Monitor project progress relative to scope, schedule, budget, and quality metrics.</li>
<li>Develop and deliver the following artifacts for assigned projects:</li>
<li>IV&amp;V Service Plans</li>
<li>Monthly Project Health Assessment Reports</li>
<li>Independent Deliverable Review Assessments</li>
<li>Risk and Issue Logs with mitigation recommendations</li>
<li>Executive Briefings for Steering Committees and leadership as needed</li>
<li>Final IV&amp;V Summary Reports at project closeout</li>
<li>Collaborate with project managers, agency stakeholders, and executive sponsors while maintaining independent judgment.</li>
<li>Ensure all reports and documentation meet DTMB&rsquo;s quality standards and adhere to required templates.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 5 years of IT project management experience, preferably with large, complex technology initiatives.</li>
<li>Minimum of 5 years of IV&amp;V or equivalent quality assurance experience.</li>
<li>Demonstrated experience supporting high-visibility, politically sensitive projects, ideally within public sector or highly regulated environments.</li>
<li>Strong understanding of project management frameworks (such as PMI&rsquo;s PMBOK), risk management practices, and quality assurance principles.</li>
<li>Excellent analytical, written, and verbal communication skills.</li>
<li>Ability to prepare professional-grade reports and executive-level briefings.</li>
<li>Proven ability to objectively assess project health and recommend actionable solutions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education and Certifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in Information Technology, Business Administration, Project Management, or a related field (required).</li>
<li>PMP certification (preferred).</li>
<li>Additional certifications such as CSM or CQA are a plus.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Lansing ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Michigan ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Bilingual Salesforce Business Analyst – Grantmaking (32602) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ July 10, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[19M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Our client, a leading financial institution, is seeking a skilled&nbsp;<strong>Salesforce Business Analyst</strong>&nbsp;with hands-on experience in&nbsp;<strong>Salesforce Non-Profit Cloud and grantmaking processes</strong>&nbsp;to support a high-impact digital transformation initiative within their Banking Technology division.</p>
<p>This role is ideal for a&nbsp;<strong>business-oriented professional</strong>&nbsp;who brings strong&nbsp;<strong>financial services experience</strong>, paired with&nbsp;<strong>Salesforce consulting expertise</strong>. The selected candidate will drive actionable insights and process improvements across Salesforce platforms, enabling smarter decision-making and operational efficiency.</p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Collaborate with stakeholders to gather, document, and analyze business requirements.</li>
<li>Evaluate and streamline current business processes.</li>
<li>Create functional specifications, business cases, and support implementation efforts.</li>
<li>Generate reports, dashboards, and visualizations using Salesforce and data tools.</li>
<li>Facilitate stakeholder meetings and communicate findings effectively.</li>
<li>Support testing and project planning within Agile/Scrum environments.</li>
<li>Ensure alignment with business goals, compliance, and technology best practices.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Mandatory:</strong>&nbsp;Experience with&nbsp;<strong>Salesforce Non-Profit Cloud</strong>&nbsp;and grantmaking workflows.</li>
<li>Minimum&nbsp;<strong>3+ years</strong>&nbsp;of experience as a Business Analyst in the&nbsp;<strong>financial services industry</strong>.</li>
<li><strong>2+ years</strong>&nbsp;of experience in a&nbsp;<strong>consulting environment</strong>.</li>
<li>Strong analytical skills; experience with&nbsp;<strong>Excel, SQL, Power BI/Tableau</strong>, and project tools.</li>
<li>Experience with multiple Salesforce clouds, including:</li>
<li><strong>Sales Cloud</strong></li>
<li><strong>Service Cloud</strong></li>
<li><strong>Experience Cloud</strong></li>
<li><strong>Financial Services Cloud</strong></li>
<li>Exceptional communication and stakeholder engagement skills.</li>
<li>Familiarity with Agile/Scrum methodology.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Montreal ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Quebec ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Technical Lead – Core Banking Assessment (32596) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ July 8, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[18M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Myticas Consulting is hiring an experienced&nbsp;<strong>SAP Data Migration Lead</strong>&nbsp;to join a long-term S/4HANA transformation engagement with a major Canadian enterprise client. The role will focus on leading complex SAP data migration activities with a strong emphasis on SAP BODS, technical leadership, and cross-functional collaboration with finance and business teams.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead SAP data conversion strategy and execution for large-scale SAP S/4HANA migration projects.</li>
<li>Interface daily with client stakeholders including executives, project managers, and technical teams.</li>
<li>Manage full data migration lifecycle: data readiness, architecture, mock loads, validation, and cutover.</li>
<li>Provide technical leadership to SAP BODS development teams.</li>
<li>Collaborate across modules including FI, CO, MM, EWM, PM, PPM, and HR.</li>
<li>Deliver high-quality migration outputs on schedule and budget.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Experience &amp; Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>8&ndash;10 years in SAP MDM/Data Migration; 5+ full-cycle implementations.</li>
<li>Deep hands-on expertise with&nbsp;<strong>SAP BODS (BusinessObjects Data Services)</strong>&nbsp;for ETLV tasks.</li>
<li>Solid understanding of SAP data migration tools (LTMC, LSMW, IDOCs, custom programs).</li>
<li>Strong experience with data profiling, cleansing, validation, de-duplication, and transformation.</li>
<li>Experience migrating data between SAP ECC, SAP CFIN, and SAP S/4HANA (brownfield migration).</li>
<li>Knowledge of master and transactional data objects (e.g., Company Code, Legal Entity, FI/CO).</li>
<li>Proficient in SQL and data quality reporting dashboards.</li>
<li>Previous experience supporting data migration for clients in the&nbsp;<strong>Energy sector</strong>&nbsp;is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Soft Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong communication and presentation skills.</li>
<li>Proven ability to lead client workshops and technical teams.</li>
<li>Ability to challenge and advise stakeholders with innovative solutions.</li>
<li>Comfortable working in fast-paced, client-facing environments.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Calgary ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Alberta ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Technical Lead – Core Banking Assessment (32596) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ July 8, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[17M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Myticas Consulting is seeking an experienced&nbsp;<strong>Technical Lead</strong>&nbsp;for a short-term contract engagement supporting a&nbsp;<strong>Core Banking Assessment</strong>&nbsp;for a large Canadian financial institution.</p>
<p>This role will involve both strategic and technical contributions and will be delivered in two phases: current state evaluation and future state solution recommendation.</p>
<p><strong>Project Overview:</strong></p>
<p>The engagement will support a Core Banking Assessment project structured in two phases:</p>
<p><strong>Phase 1 &ndash; Current &amp; Target State Assessment:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Understand the client&rsquo;s strategy and identify supporting core banking capabilities.</li>
<li>Define the target state core banking capability model.</li>
<li>Assess the current state of each capability, platforms in use, and gaps.</li>
<li>Recommend potential solutions to enhance/augment each capability.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Phase 2 &ndash; Solution Fit &amp; Business Case:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Conduct a market scan of available core banking solution providers.</li>
<li>Identify and assess best-fit solutions.</li>
<li>Build a detailed business case for the selected core banking platform.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Facilitate workshops with stakeholders and technical teams.</li>
<li>Translate executive strategy into defined banking capabilities.</li>
<li>Capture current state maturity and identify platform inefficiencies.</li>
<li>Analyze technical complexities of core banking systems.</li>
<li>Provide solution recommendations and market insights.</li>
<li>Develop a business case aligned with the organization&rsquo;s strategy.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>5&ndash;10 years of relevant experience, preferably in banking/financial services.</li>
<li>Strong understanding of&nbsp;<strong>core banking systems</strong>&nbsp;and platforms.</li>
<li>Familiarity with&nbsp;<strong>infrastructure, architecture, integration</strong>, and&nbsp;<strong>IT operations</strong>.</li>
<li>Experience with&nbsp;<strong>vendor management</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>IT risk</strong>, and&nbsp;<strong>compliance</strong>&nbsp;frameworks.</li>
<li>Proven ability to bridge business strategy and technical execution.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Work Model:</strong></p>
<p>Hybrid &ndash; based in Toronto, with 2&ndash;3 days per week in office</p>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Toronto ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ QA Laboratory Sample Handler (32580) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 30, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[14M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Job Title: QA Laboratory Sample Handler</strong></p>
<p><strong>Contract Duration:</strong>&nbsp;6 months (with potential for extension)</p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Onsite &ndash; Ada, MI</p>
<p><strong>Travel:</strong>&nbsp;Local transportation (between facilities)</p>
<p><strong>Pay Rate:</strong>&nbsp;$19.00 per hour</p>
<p><strong>Company Overview:</strong></p>
<p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas company) is currently seeking a QA Laboratory Sample Handler for a well-established client located in Ada, MI. This is a contract position with strong potential for extension. Please note, this is&nbsp;<strong>not</strong>&nbsp;a laboratory testing role but may offer future opportunities to gain laboratory experience.</p>
<p><strong>Position Summary:</strong></p>
<p>The QA Laboratory Sample Handler is responsible for transporting a variety of sample types&mdash;including in-process materials, finished products, raw materials, and miscellaneous samples&mdash;between different locations on the Ada complex and the Spaulding facility.</p>
<p>Sample pickups are scheduled throughout the day via a paging system and are transported using a Ford Transit minivan. A significant portion of the collected samples will also require entry into the enterprise QA data system (LIMS).</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Collect, verify, and distribute samples as scheduled</li>
<li>Log sample information into the LIMS system</li>
<li>Perform minimal verification testing as needed</li>
<li>Maintain proper documentation and sample tracking</li>
<li>Manage daily tasks with strong organizational and time-management skills</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Valid State of Michigan driver's license (travel required between Ada complex and Spaulding facility)</li>
<li>Basic computer skills</li>
<li>Background in science or a related field is preferred, but not required</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Grand Rapids ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Michigan ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Technical Support and Customer Service Associate (32581) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 30, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[13M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Technical Support and Customer Service Associate - REMOTE</strong></p>
<p><strong>Contract: 12 months with possible CTH</strong></p>
<p><strong>Schedule: 2nd shift - 12 pm to 9 pm, Tuesday thru Saturday</strong></p>
<p><strong>Work Type: Fully Remote</strong></p>
<p>Myticas is actively seeking a&nbsp;<strong>Technical Support and Customer Service Associate&nbsp;</strong>for a direct client to join their&nbsp;<strong>Personal Support Center (PSC)</strong>&nbsp;team. This role is perfect for someone with a passion for helping others, a knack for troubleshooting, and the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, tech-forward environment.</p>
<p>As a PSC Associate, you&rsquo;ll be the first point of contact for users via phone, email, and chat&mdash;working to resolve technical issues, answer questions, and ensure a seamless customer experience. You'll be supported by extensive training, a detailed knowledge base, and a collaborative team ready to help you grow.</p>
<p><strong>What You&rsquo;ll Do:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Provide Tier 1 technical support for software, hardware, and connectivity issues</li>
<li>Assist with password resets, software installations, VPN setups, and general troubleshooting</li>
<li>Escalate complex issues to senior team members when needed</li>
<li>Maintain clear, professional communication across all customer interactions</li>
<li>Simultaneously manage support requests via phone, email, and chat</li>
<li>Accurately log cases using tools like ServiceNow and Zendesk</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>What We&rsquo;re Looking For:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong customer service and communication skills</li>
<li>Comfort working in a flexible, 24/7/365 support environment</li>
<li>Ability to adapt to new tools, systems, and processes quickly</li>
<li>Team player who&rsquo;s open to ongoing feedback, learning, and development</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Why Join Us:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Hands-on training and mentoring</li>
<li>Access to a robust internal knowledge base</li>
<li>Opportunities to collaborate with tech experts and leadership</li>
<li>A supportive team environment where growth is encouraged</li>
<li>If you're ready to jump into a dynamic support role where no two days are the same, apply now or reach out to learn more. We&rsquo;re excited to meet you!</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Chicago ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Illinois ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Digital Content Specialist (32576) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 26, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[12M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Job Title: Digital Content Specialist</strong></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;On-Site &ndash; Grand Rapids, MI</p>
<p><strong>Contract Duration:</strong>&nbsp;6+ Months (Extensions Likely)</p>
<p><strong>Company:</strong>&nbsp;Clover Consulting (a Myticas Company)</p>
<p><strong>Client:</strong>&nbsp;Direct Client in Grand Rapids, MI</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong>&nbsp;Local candidates preferred. This role is not eligible for sponsorship.</p>
<p><strong>Job Overview:</strong></p>
<p>Clover Consulting is seeking a&nbsp;<strong>Digital Content Specialist</strong>&nbsp;to support our client&rsquo;s marketing efforts in Grand Rapids, MI. This is a full-time, on-site contract opportunity with a strong possibility of extension. The successful candidate will assist in the development and execution of CRM campaigns using a newly implemented customer 360 database and marketing automation platform.</p>
<p><strong>About the Team:</strong></p>
<p>The North American CRM team designs and implements marketing strategies that leverage automation software to enhance lead generation, sales, retention, productivity, and customer loyalty&mdash;particularly focused on Independent Business Owners (IBOs) and consumers.</p>
<p><strong>Role Summary:</strong></p>
<p>As a Digital Content Specialist, you will be responsible for supporting the planning, development, deployment, and analysis of CRM campaigns. These communications target IBOs, customers, or a combination of both. Your primary responsibility is to ensure all campaigns are executed accurately and on schedule.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Serve as the main liaison between internal stakeholders, external agencies, and the CRM production team.</li>
<li>Manage CRM campaign deliverables, including planning, timelines, risk management, and resource allocation.</li>
<li>Submit use cases and other documentation for internal review and approval.</li>
<li>Schedule creative briefings and manage content development updates.</li>
<li>Route creative materials, compile proof comments, and finalize HTML content for translation.</li>
<li>Conduct thorough quality assurance checks on email content in all supported languages and markets (including verification of links, artwork, and videos).</li>
<li>Educate stakeholders on the capabilities of the CRM platform.</li>
<li>Track campaign progress and update timelines and work estimates as needed.</li>
<li>Distribute final CRM creative assets to internal stakeholders for reference.</li>
<li>Provide on-call support for end-of-month and urgent field email communications, per established protocols.</li>
<li>Serve as a backup to the Email Coordinator.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Associate's or Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in Marketing, Communications, or a related field; equivalent certifications will also be considered.</li>
<li>Minimum of 2 years of experience in Communications, Marketing, or a related discipline.</li>
<li>Basic knowledge of CRM platforms.</li>
<li>Ability to independently resolve routine issues.</li>
<li>Capable of performing assigned tasks and supporting projects under supervision.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Preferred Skills and Attributes:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong passion for marketing and delivering a top-tier user experience to engage both customers and IBOs.</li>
<li>Solid understanding of email marketing strategies, triggered campaigns, and A/B testing to optimize business performance.</li>
<li>Proven ability to collaborate effectively with internal teams and external vendors.</li>
<li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills.</li>
<li>Strong organizational skills with the ability to manage multiple priorities in a fast-paced environment.</li>
<li>Flexible and able to perform well under pressure and tight deadlines.</li>
<li>Critical thinking, problem-solving, and follow-through skills.</li>
<li>High level of professionalism and attention to detail.</li>
<li>Ability to work independently and as part of a team.</li>
<li>Willingness and ability to work on-site at the client location in Grand Rapids, MI</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Grand Rapids ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Michigan ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Lead Cloud Operations Engineer (32574) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 26, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[10M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Lead Cloud Engineer</strong></p>
<p><strong>ROLE:</strong></p>
<p>As a&nbsp;<strong>Lead Cloud Operations Engineer</strong>, you will play a critical role in the reliability, scalability, and performance of Zafin&rsquo;s SaaS platform. In addition to performing advanced technical duties, this role includes leadership responsibilities, such as mentoring team members, driving continuous improvement, and serving as a backup to the Cloud Operations Manager when needed. You will serve as a key point of contact across teams, providing both strategic and hands-on support in operational excellence and cloud-native practices.</p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Lead and execute</strong>&nbsp;the design, deployment, and maintenance of Zafin&rsquo;s SaaS environment, including infrastructure and application stacks across public cloud platforms.</li>
<li>Own the&nbsp;<strong>operational stability and performance</strong>&nbsp;of production and pre-production environments, including proactive patch management and rolling updates for both infrastructure and application layers.</li>
<li>Investigate, resolve, and perform root cause analysis for complex&nbsp;<strong>environmental and operational issues</strong>.</li>
<li>Identify and drive&nbsp;<strong>operational efficiencies</strong>&nbsp;and process improvements across the Cloud Operations team.</li>
<li>Design, build, and maintain&nbsp;<strong>automated CI/CD pipelines</strong>&nbsp;and deployment workflows to ensure rapid and reliable delivery.</li>
<li>Collaborate cross-functionally with&nbsp;<strong>engineering, QA, security, and product teams</strong>&nbsp;to champion best practices in release and environment management.</li>
<li>Serve as a&nbsp;<strong>subject matter expert (SME)</strong>&nbsp;on Zafin&rsquo;s SaaS platform architecture, operational procedures, and cloud infrastructure.</li>
<li>Lead and participate in an on-call rotation, ensuring 24/7 availability of critical services and rapid response to incidents.</li>
<li>Actively engage with internal and external stakeholders to coordinate changes, manage communications, and ensure alignment with business needs.</li>
<li><strong>Mentor junior engineers</strong>, review technical work, and foster a culture of collaboration and accountability within the team.</li>
<li>Step in as the&nbsp;<strong>acting Cloud Operations Manager</strong>&nbsp;when required, including handling escalations, representing the team</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Must Haves:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>6-12 years of proven working experience in infrastructure deployment and maintenance</li>
<li>Working experience on application security using Azure provided resources</li>
<li>Experienced with IaC (Infrastructure as Code) deployment (e.g., Terraform, Ansible)</li>
<li>Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Wiki?</li>
<li>Must be able to use and work with user interface-based applications?</li>
<li>Solid knowledge on Cloud computing</li>
<li>Solid Azure cloud hands on experience</li>
<li>Solid understanding of SRE best practices</li>
<li>Solid hands-on experience on Linux Operating System and maintenance</li>
<li>Experience working with automated deployment pipelines preferably on Azure DevOps</li>
<li>Strong knowledge and hands-on experience with Docker, Kubernetes / OpenShift</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Vancouver ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ British Columbia ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior Packet Processing Software Developer (32079) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 24, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[9M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>We are seeking a highly skilled&nbsp;<strong>Senior Software Engineer</strong>&nbsp;with expertise in&nbsp;<strong>Packet Processing</strong>&nbsp;to join our team. The ideal candidate will have extensive experience in designing and optimizing high-performance network systems, with a strong background in developing scalable, low-latency solutions for data-intensive environments. In this role, you will work on cutting-edge technologies to enhance network protocols and packet processing frameworks. Your contributions will play a key role in delivering robust, reliable, and efficient network operations, ensuring our systems meet the evolving demands of modern infrastructure.</p>
<p><strong>Main Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Collaborate with experienced engineers in the design, coding, testing, and maintenance of software applications.</li>
<li>Develop and maintain embedded software modules using programming languages such as&nbsp;<strong>C++</strong>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<strong>Python</strong>.</li>
<li>Design and implement high-performance packet processing applications using&nbsp;<strong>DPDK</strong>&nbsp;and similar frameworks.</li>
<li>Optimize network functions for maximum throughput and minimal latency.</li>
<li>Develop and maintain packet processing pipelines for various network functions.</li>
<li>Troubleshoot complex performance issues in packet processing applications.</li>
<li>Assist in the implementation of networking solutions to ensure seamless communication between software components.</li>
<li>Contribute to the development of software tools, libraries, and frameworks to enhance overall product quality and efficiency.</li>
<li>Participate in code reviews and provide constructive feedback to improve code quality and adherence to coding standards.</li>
<li>Collaborate with the team to troubleshoot and resolve software defects and technical issues.</li>
<li>Support the integration of software components on&nbsp;<strong>Linux</strong>&nbsp;operating systems.</li>
<li>Assist in the testing and validation of software features to ensure functionality and performance meet specified requirements.</li>
<li>Utilize cloud technologies to enhance software deployment and management.</li>
<li>Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including product managers and designers, to understand requirements and contribute to technical discussions.</li>
<li>Maintain clear and organized documentation of software designs, processes, and development tasks.</li>
<li>Demonstrate effective teamwork and communication skills, both orally and in writing.</li>
<li>Lead the design, development, and implementation of advanced satellite ground segment software systems, ensuring high performance, scalability, and reliability.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education &amp; Experience Required:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor's or Master's degree in&nbsp;<strong>Computer Science</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>Computer Engineering</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>Electrical Engineering</strong>, or a related field.</li>
<li>In-depth knowledge of&nbsp;<strong>packet processing development</strong>.</li>
<li>Experience with the&nbsp;<strong>Vector Packet Processing (VPP)</strong>&nbsp;framework is a plus.</li>
<li>Deep understanding of&nbsp;<strong>DPDK architecture and APIs</strong>.</li>
<li>Familiarity with modern&nbsp;<strong>NIC features</strong>&nbsp;(e.g., RSS, checksum offload, scatter-gather).</li>
<li>Experience with&nbsp;<strong>AF_XDP</strong>&nbsp;or similar kernel bypass technologies.</li>
<li>Strong understanding of&nbsp;<strong>Linux-based network stacks</strong>, kernel modules, and performance optimization.</li>
<li>Ideally&nbsp;<strong>8+ years</strong>&nbsp;of experience in&nbsp;<strong>C/C++</strong>&nbsp;for low-level network programming and high-performance packet processing.</li>
<li>Solid understanding of networking concepts and protocols, including&nbsp;<strong>TCP/IP</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>UDP</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>VXLAN</strong>,&nbsp;<strong>GRE</strong>, etc.</li>
<li>Familiarity with cloud technologies is a plus.</li>
<li>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills.</li>
<li>Ability to collaborate effectively within a diverse team.</li>
<li>Excellent oral and written communication skills.</li>
<li>Enthusiasm for learning new technologies and tools.</li>
<li>Detail-oriented with a commitment to producing high-quality software.</li>
<li>Ability to design software with consideration for hardware resource constraints.</li>
<li>Experience in&nbsp;<strong>software development</strong>&nbsp;for&nbsp;<strong>satellite communication systems</strong>&nbsp;is a plus.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Network Management System Developer (32446) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 24, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[8M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>As a Network Management System Developer, you&rsquo;ll be responsible for ensuring the smooth operation of our network by designing, implementing, testing and maintaining Operational Support Systems (OSS). Your role will be instrumental in optimizing network performance, enhancing efficiency, and ensuring a seamless customer experience.</p>
<p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Design network management solutions to monitor and manage Carrier</li>
<li>Ethernet and IP services, ensuring optimal capacity, performance and reliability</li>
<li>Define configurations and notification data models using YANG</li>
<li>Define real-time network monitoring solutions</li>
<li>Program network automation with gNMI/gNOI/NETCONF/RESTCONF</li>
<li>Design, Develop and maintain automated scripts and tools to verify NMS functionality</li>
<li>Work with vendors to implement new OSS/NMS solutions</li>
<li>Review and approve design documents, test strategies, plans, and scripts</li>
<li>Maintain accurate documentation of OSS/NMS requirements, configurations, processes, and procedures</li>
<li>Resolve complex OSS/NMS implementation and network problems with cross-functional teams</li>
<li>Enforce security best practices to protect network systems and data integrity</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field</li>
<li>2-5 experience in a similar role.</li>
<li>Proficient in Layer 2/3 protocols, YANG modeling, gRPC/gNMI/gNOI</li>
<li>Experience designing network management systems using Layer 2/3 protocols</li>
<li>Programming skills in modern C++, GNU C, Go, Python 3.x</li>
<li>TDD and BDD test frameworks</li>
<li>Knowledge of developing software in container hosted in&nbsp;<strong>Linux&nbsp;</strong>environment and microservices</li>
<li>Knowledge of Protobuf, XML, JSON IETF encoding, and template language (Jinja2)</li>
<li>Good problem-solving, and communication skills</li>
<li>Experience with NMS products like Netcracker Digital OSS, ONAP, Ciena Blue Planet, Amdocs</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Knowledge in Protocols and Standards:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Layer 3 protocols: IP, OSPF, BGP, MPLS, SR-MPLS</li>
<li>Layer 2 protocols: Ethernet, VLAN, STP, LACP</li>
<li>MEF and TMF Standards</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ IP Network Architect (32569) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 24, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[6M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>The Senior IP Network Architect is a Subject Matter Expert (SME) on all aspects of the Network design and works with internal teams and external contractors to ensure designs, implementation decisions, validation plans and documentation reflect the business requirements and objectives of the program.</p>
<p><strong>Networking</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead the design of complex IP network architectures, considering business requirements, scalability, and performance.</li>
<li>Possess a strong command of network platforms and appliances, including routers, switches, firewalls, SDWAN controllers, IPSEC VPN gateways, and deep packet inspection tools.</li>
<li>In coordination with the Network and System Engineering teams attend, contribute and produce materials for internal and external design and system engineering reviews for Network Engineering related activities.</li>
<li>Prepare and deliver materials including presentations, reference documentation and test strategies for network equipment deployment and operation.</li>
<li>Develop and oversee plans including product idea investigations, proof of concept, service validation and product demonstrations in lab.</li>
<li>Maintain a deep understanding of industry standards and protocols related to segment routing, such as IS-IS, OSPF, BGP, and MPLS.</li>
<li>Maintain familiarity with transport network technologies including Segment Routing (SR-MPLS) and Software Defined Networking (SDN).</li>
<li>Assess, evaluate, and recommend network platforms and appliances, hardware, and software solutions to meet business requirements.</li>
<li>Represent the Network Engineering team by documenting and delivering network requirements to hardware and software development teams specifically in the areas of customer facing MEF 3.0 interface and networking design support requirements.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Security and Compliance</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Security and Compliance:</li>
<li>Design and implement secure network solutions with a focus on firewall configurations, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection techniques.</li>
<li>Ensure compliance with industry standards and best practices for network security.</li>
<li>Optimization and Performance:</li>
<li>Continuously monitor network performance, analyzing metrics and conducting assessments to identify bottlenecks, vulnerabilities, and areas for improvement. Develop strategies to optimize network performance, enhance security, and ensure high availability.</li>
<li>Collaborate with cross-functional teams to enhance network performance and reliability.</li>
<li>Experience with network automation and scripting using tools such as Python, Ansible, or similar.</li>
<li>Emerging Technologies:</li>
<li>Stay current with industry trends, emerging technologies, and best practices related to IP networking and network appliances.</li>
<li>Proactively recommend and lead the adoption of new technologies that align with business goals.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Vendor Management</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Collaborate with vendors to evaluate products, negotiate contracts, and ensure the successful deployment and operation of network appliances.</li>
<li>Technical Leadership:</li>
<li>Provide mentorship and guidance to junior network engineers, sharing your expertise and promoting professional growth.</li>
<li>Troubleshooting and Support:</li>
<li>Lead in-depth troubleshooting and root cause analysis of network issues, providing timely and effective resolutions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education &amp; Experience</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor's degree in computer science, Information Technology, or a related field or equivalent work experience.</li>
<li>10+ years of progressive experience in designing and architecting IP networks, with a focus on routing, firewalls, SDWAN, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection.</li>
<li>Understanding of Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) standards and objectives as they relate to Carrier Ethernet Services.</li>
<li>Professional certifications such as CCIE, CCNP, CISSP or equivalent are highly desirable.</li>
<li>Expertise in network appliance evaluation, selection, and integration.</li>
<li>In-depth understanding of security principles and practices as they relate to network architecture.</li>
<li>Proven experience with network troubleshooting, performance optimization, and security enhancement.</li>
<li>Strong knowledge of industry-leading routing protocols, firewall technologies, SDWAN solutions, IPSEC VPNs, and deep packet inspection methods.</li>
<li>Experience with network automation and scripting using tools such as Python, Ansible, or similar.</li>
<li>Leadership experience and the ability to mentor junior team members.</li>
<li>Excellent communication (verbal, written, presentation) and interpersonal skills.</li>
<li>Comfortable leading meetings and able to communicate issues and trends to senior management and other groups at the appropriate level of detail.</li>
<li>Communicates well with own team and across organizational boundaries to ensure the successful completion of shared goals.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Working Conditions</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Working conditions are generally comfortable typical of an office environment with occasional work within Data Centres.</li>
<li>Occasional international travel is anticipated.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior Technical Support Specialist (32305) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 23, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[1M5MDWQ10]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>The Senior Technical Support Specialist will provide expert-level technical assistance and strategic support the customers, partners, and cross-functional teams. This role involves complex issue resolution, leadership in support process improvement, ownership of professional service projects focused on product customization and integrations, deploying software solutions, onboarding new customers, and proactive engagement in optimizing team tools, processes, and customer issues. This individual will drive support initiatives, lead escalations, and act as a liaison with the engineering team to implement solutions resolving customer-reported bugs and issues.</p>
<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>
<p><strong>Essential Functions</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead and Resolve Advanced Technical Issues: Provide exceptional, senior-level support by diagnosing and resolving complex technical issues for customers, partners, and sales engineers, demonstrating technical leadership and initiative.</li>
<li>Deployment and Customer Onboarding: Manage the deployment of Signiant software solutions, ensuring smooth transitions for new customers and providing comprehensive onboarding to maximize product adoption and success.</li>
<li>Customer Impact Focus: Act as the primary point of escalation for challenging, high-impact technical issues, driving timely and effective resolutions for mission-critical customer needs.</li>
<li>Project Leadership in Professional Services: Lead professional service projects aimed at product customization and integrations, coordinating with customers to understand requirements and deliver solutions aligned with their business needs.</li>
<li>Critical Availability: Provide on-call support for critical escalations outside standard business hours as needed, prioritizing rapid resolution and customer satisfaction.</li>
<li>Cross-functional Collaboration: Work closely with development, QA, and product management teams to assist in developing and testing patches, updates, and scripts for issue resolution and software enhancements.</li>
<li>Team Mentorship and Skill Development: Mentor junior team members, fostering skill enhancement and knowledge-sharing across the support team.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities</strong></p>
<p><strong>Experience &amp; Expertise:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 7 years of experience in technical support or related fields in a software company, with a track record of successfully managing complex production environments.</li>
<li>Hands-on experience with Windows, Linux, and Mac OS environments, as well as multi-platform troubleshooting.</li>
<li>Networking knowledge, including TCP/IP, DNS, and SSL, with experience in packet capture and analysis.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Technical Proficiency:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Background in cloud infrastructure services (AWS, Azure) and familiarity with modern cloud-native architectures.</li>
<li>Familiarity with database administration (e.g., MySQL, PostgreSQL) and system automation tools to enhance support processes.</li>
<li>Competency in scripting or coding in one or more languages and familiarity with automation tools.</li>
<li>Experience with real-time data integrations using webhooks, API listeners, and other middleware solutions to enhance system interoperability.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Analytical &amp; Troubleshooting Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong diagnostic skills and proficiency in root-cause analysis, with the ability to implement proactive, preventative measures.</li>
<li>Ability to synthesize data insights to predict and address system bottlenecks and inefficiencies.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Leadership &amp; Communication:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Exceptional communication skills, both written and verbal, for conveying complex technical information to diverse audiences.</li>
<li>Proven ability to lead support projects and initiatives, with a strong focus on customer satisfaction, teamwork, and collaboration.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Additional Desirable Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Experience in technical support leadership roles, with the ability to delegate, prioritize, and coach effectively.</li>
<li>Expertise in technical documentation and knowledge management systems to empower both internal teams and end-users.</li>
<li>Ability to work flexible hours to support a 24/7 environment and provide guidance in high-pressure, critical situations.</li>
</ul>
<p>Our client is seeking&nbsp;<strong>multiple SAP CM/OCM (Change Management / Organizational Change Management) Consultants</strong>&nbsp;to support a high-impact ERP transformation program. This is an ongoing SAP S/4HANA engagement with travel to Vancouver on a weekly basis.</p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead or support ERP change management strategies and transformation initiatives</li>
<li>Engage stakeholders across business and technical teams to drive user adoption</li>
<li>Develop and execute communication, training, and readiness plans</li>
<li>Align change activities with project milestones and business objectives</li>
<li>Collaborate with functional SAP teams to understand system impacts and communicate accordingly</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Skills &amp; Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong experience in&nbsp;<strong>ERP change management</strong>&nbsp;programs, specifically&nbsp;<strong>SAP S/4HANA</strong></li>
<li>Proven ability to lead large-scale transformation initiatives</li>
<li>Excellent communication, facilitation, and stakeholder engagement skills</li>
<li><strong>Mining industry experience</strong>&nbsp;is considered a strong asset</li>
<li>Flexibility for weekly travel to Vancouver</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ SAP EWM Consultant (32555) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[BLZV0O54]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Our client, a global organization, is seeking two experienced&nbsp;<strong>SAP EWM Consultants</strong>&nbsp;for upcoming contract engagements. The successful candidates will support a hybrid work environment in the Greater Toronto Area and bring strong functional and technical expertise in Extended Warehouse Management.</p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Deliver end-to-end SAP EWM solutions across inbound, outbound, and internal warehouse processes</li>
<li>Configure and integrate SAP EWM with SAP TM or third-party TMS</li>
<li>Support integration with production (Advanced Production Integration), SD, and MM modules</li>
<li>Develop and maintain warehouse structures (e.g., Storage Types, Activity Areas)</li>
<li>Configure RF transactions and support associated development</li>
<li>Assist with S/4HANA plant configuration and go-live readiness</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum 10 years of hands-on SAP EWM consulting experience</li>
<li>Proven track record on multiple full-cycle SAP EWM implementations</li>
<li>Deep functional knowledge across core EWM processes</li>
<li>Strong integration experience with SAP TM, SD, MM, and production modules</li>
<li>Experience with S/4HANA is a strong asset</li>
<li>Prior consulting experience with large, complex environments is preferred</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Work Model:</strong>&nbsp;Hybrid &ndash; candidates must be able to attend onsite meetings in the GTA up to 3 times per week, as needed.</p>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Toronto ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Lab Tech - Sampler (32552) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ZREUA9DM]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Job Title: QA Sampler</strong></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Grand Rapids, MI</p>
<p><strong>Company:</strong>&nbsp;Clover Consulting (a Myticas Company)</p>
<p><strong>Contract Length:</strong>&nbsp;6-month initial contract with potential extension up to 3 years</p>
<p><strong>Work Schedule:</strong>&nbsp;On-site | Monday&ndash;Friday, 7:00 AM &ndash; 3:30 PM</p>
<p><strong>Job Summary:</strong></p>
<p>Clover Consulting, on behalf of our direct client in Grand Rapids, MI, is seeking a QA Sampler for an on-site role. This position involves sampling raw materials and packaging components used in cosmetic, home care, and food industry products. The role includes basic quality checks and data logging, with opportunities for future growth into laboratory roles.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Sample raw materials and packaging components across multiple warehouse locations.</li>
<li>Ensure proper inspection and sampling of materials, including food-grade materials and known allergens.</li>
<li>Inspect packaging components for defects during sampling.</li>
<li>Accurately record sampling data in the QA data system.</li>
<li>Deliver samples to designated laboratories (Microbiology, Chemistry, and Packaging).</li>
<li>Maintain compliance with required safety and quality protocols.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Valid State of Michigan driver&rsquo;s license (intra-facility travel required).</li>
<li>Must wear shoes with full leather uppers during sampling.</li>
<li>Basic computer proficiency required.</li>
<li>Background or degree in science is preferred but not mandatory.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Grand Rapids ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ MI ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ IT Director - PMO - Project Management Office (32554) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 18, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[FU5LEIY7]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Job Title:</strong>&nbsp;Director, IT (PMO)</p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Ottawa &ndash; Hybrid (3 Days On-Site, Mandatory and Non-Negotiable)</p>
<p><strong>Type:</strong>&nbsp;Full-Time, Permanent (8-Hour Workday)</p>
<p><strong>Language Requirement:</strong>&nbsp;Bilingual Preferred (French/English)</p>
<p><strong>Security Clearance:</strong>&nbsp;Must obtain clearance equivalent to Enhanced Reliability Status (Canada)</p>
<p><strong>Eligibility:</strong>&nbsp;Must be a Canadian Citizen or Permanent Resident</p>
<p><strong>About the Role</strong></p>
<p>The Director of IT (PMO) is a strategic leadership position responsible for aligning IT initiatives with enterprise objectives and ensuring the successful delivery of high-impact technology projects. The Director will provide expert guidance, foster cross-functional collaboration, and oversee a portfolio of projects that deliver long-term organizational value.</p>
<p>This role will lead the development and enforcement of a consistent IT project management framework, ensuring compliance with standardized methodologies and governance practices. The Director will also provide senior leadership with timely insights into project health, risk exposure, and emerging opportunities across the portfolio.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong></p>
<p><strong>Strategic Portfolio Oversight</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Drive the evolution and adoption of the IT PMO framework to ensure alignment with organizational goals.</li>
<li>Manage the enterprise-wide IT project portfolio, prioritizing initiatives and optimizing resource allocation.</li>
<li>Advise executive stakeholders using data-driven insights to support strategic investment and resource planning.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Project Leadership and Governance</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead and mentor project managers and support staff to promote high performance and accountability.</li>
<li>Establish and enforce governance standards across all projects.</li>
<li>Proactively identify and manage risks, implementing mitigation strategies to ensure successful delivery.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Executive Collaboration</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Engage regularly with senior leadership to align on digital strategy, planning, and delivery progress.</li>
<li>Prepare and deliver executive-level reports and presentations that support informed decision-making.</li>
<li>Handle sensitive and confidential project data with integrity and discretion.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Risk Management</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Identify risks across individual projects and the broader portfolio, escalating critical issues as required.</li>
<li>Develop and implement contingency plans to ensure project continuity.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Process Optimization and Continuous Improvement</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Analyze project outcomes to identify areas for improvement and incorporate lessons learned.</li>
<li>Promote the use of modern tools and delivery methodologies, including Agile and hybrid approaches.</li>
<li>Continuously refine PMO structures and practices to enhance organizational effectiveness.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Reporting and Metrics</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Define and track key performance indicators (KPIs) for project and portfolio success.</li>
<li>Provide concise, data-driven reports and dashboards to executive stakeholders.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Project Execution</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead the end-to-end delivery of complex, high-impact IT projects, ensuring they are completed on time, within budget, and with strong stakeholder engagement.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Qualifications and Experience</strong></p>
<p><strong>Education</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Post-secondary degree or diploma in Business Administration, Computer Science, Information Technology, or a related field.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Experience</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 8 years of progressive experience in IT project management.</li>
<li>At least 2 years in a leadership role managing a PMO or IT project portfolio.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Certifications</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Project Management Professional (PMP) certification is required.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Key Skills</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Demonstrated experience leading enterprise-wide IT projects and managing PMO teams.</li>
<li>Proven ability to work with C-suite executives and handle confidential information.</li>
<li>In-depth knowledge of project management methodologies, including Waterfall, Agile, and hybrid models.</li>
<li>Proficiency in tools such as Microsoft Project, Jira, and Smartsheet.</li>
<li>Strong interpersonal, analytical, and organizational skills.</li>
<li>Ability to manage multiple projects and competing priorities in a fast-paced environment.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst (32542) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 13, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[8DILR275]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst</strong></p>
<p><strong>Job Title:&nbsp;</strong>Enterprise Data Warehouse (EDW) Informatica ETL Developer</p>
<p><strong>Contract:&nbsp;</strong>W2&ndash; Candidates must be authorized to work in the U.S. on a W2 basis. We cannot accept candidates requiring sponsorship or those from C2C vendors.</p>
<p><strong>Duration:&nbsp;</strong>12 months with possible multi-year extension/s</p>
<p>Clover Consulting (a Myticas Co.) is are seeking a highly experienced&nbsp;<strong>EDW Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst&nbsp;</strong>for a large, direct client in Springfield, IL.</p>
<p><strong>Primary Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Gathering and analyzing technical information from various sources to be included in the documentation.</li>
<li>Planning, writing, and maintaining detailed technical, operational, and process documentation.</li>
<li>Leading, developing, and maintaining a lipary of technical and business documentation source code and reports.</li>
<li>Analyze Medicaid program including claims, eligibility, and provider data supporting data warehouse downstream reporting and analytics.</li>
<li>Developing and supporting technical training materials.</li>
<li>Modifying existing technical documentation for business needs.</li>
<li>Participating in and leading technical and business requirements sessions.</li>
<li>Meeting with the project team regularly to consolidate project status and reporting.</li>
<li>Engaging with the customer as needed to provide updates on technical documentation and project work.</li>
<li>Working with the development and QA team to assure each document has been thoroughly reviewed and support process improvements and operational efficiency.</li>
<li>Mentoring/Coaching other project team members on effective writing skills and strategies for consistency.</li>
<li>Performing additional duties that are typically associated with this position, as assigned.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>5+ years of healthcare business analysis experience supporting business initiatives through data analysis, writing business requirements and user acceptance testing of various systems.</li>
<li>5+ years of experience serving as a technical analyst in healthcare (payor).</li>
<li>3+ years of experience working specifically with Medicaid programs, MMIS/MES or related systems.</li>
<li>3+ years of experience in knowledge management creating, organizing, sharing, and optimizing knowledge within an enterprise organization using tools such as Microsoft 365, AI-enabled search, MS SharePoint/Teams, and JIRA.</li>
<li>Proven ability to lead communication (written and verbal) at the customer leadership level.</li>
<li>Knowledge of health insurance, HMO, and managed care principles including Medicaid and Medicare regulation.</li>
<li>Ability to interpret federal and state Medicaid policy and translate it into business and technical requirements.</li>
<li>Effective organizational, analytical, time management, problem-solving, and multi-tasking skills, and habits; ability to complete assignments under tight deadlines with little/no direct supervision.</li>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in business, information systems, Public Health, or a related field</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Preferred Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Master&rsquo;s Degree in related field is preferred.</li>
<li>5+ years of experience as a technical analyst in payor healthcare.</li>
<li>3+ years of experience writing SQL using large-scale database management tools.</li>
<li>3+ years of experience working with State Medicaid and CHIP agencies including federal reporting (CMS 64/21, TMSIS, PERM). Enterprise Data Warehouse - Sr. Healthcare Technical Analyst</li>
<li>Knowledge of data integration, software enhancements/planning and agile methodologies</li>
<li>Experience with using Azure DevOps, SharePoint, MS Project, Visio</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Springfield ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Illinois ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior System Engineer (32529) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 10, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[GUINLLIU]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>The Senior System Engineer will contribute to our clients program in conducting advance performance assessment studies for system configurations as needed to provide solution for complex customer needs. Using his / her expertise in satellite communications, orbital configuration and large communication networks, the candidate will define solutions with enough details to enable implementation across their system.</p>
<p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Develop new solutions to commercial needs using their system, including among others solutions for low latency high capacity services, hosted satellite (space relay) services, mobile services, and other new configurations to support opportunities.</li>
<li>Support sales activities by evaluating complex use cases using internal and commercially available simulation tools.</li>
<li>Evaluate system performance boundaries by incorporating realistic user traffic profiles and terminal mix.</li>
<li>Help prepare and manage feature development roadmap in collaboration with commercial and engineering teams by evaluating value-add.</li>
<li>Develop technical documentation and reports.</li>
<li>Prepare and deliver high quality technical presentations supporting the delivery of solutions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>B. Sc. in Electrical, Computer or System Engineering and a minimum of 5 years of relevant experience in satellite communications or other large communication systems.</li>
<li>Experience in system simulations and service performance assessments.</li>
<li>Programming experience in Matlab and / or Python.</li>
<li>Knowledge of radio communication systems and/or satellite communication is desirable (experience with link budgets is an asset).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Specialized Knowledge, Skills and Abilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Creative problem-solver with thorough attention to detail.</li>
<li>Highly collaborative team-player who can quickly earn the confidence of co-workers and teammates.</li>
<li>Excellent oral and written communication skills.</li>
<li>Experience with STK for orbital analyses is an asset.</li>
<li>Fluent in English, written and oral.</li>
<li>Computers running Windows and Linux</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Network & Telecom Project Leader (32492) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 10, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[QE2CYGWF]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Network &amp; Telecom Project Lead</strong></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Onsite &ndash; Winchester, VA</p>
<p><strong>Employment Type:</strong>&nbsp;Direct Hire (W2 Only)</p>
<p><strong>Eligibility:</strong>&nbsp;Candidates must be authorized to work in the U.S. on a W2 basis. We are unable to accept candidates requiring sponsorship or those from C2C vendors.</p>
<p><strong>Company:</strong>&nbsp;Clover Consulting (a Myticas Company)</p>
<p><strong>Client:</strong>&nbsp;Direct client &ndash; Onsite, direct hire opportunity. Local candidates in or near Winchester, VA, are highly preferred.</p>
<p><strong>Position Summary</strong></p>
<p>The&nbsp;<strong>Network &amp; Telecom Project Lead</strong>&nbsp;is a key member of the Information Technology team, responsible for partnering with business and IT leaders to deliver robust network and telecommunications services that support critical business operations and applications across the enterprise.</p>
<p>This role requires deep expertise in managing and supporting network and telecom operations, including data centers, networking, telecommunications, cybersecurity, compliance, and related services. The position will also manage relationships with external vendors that provide network and telecom capabilities.</p>
<p>As a strategic contributor to the IT department, the Network &amp; Telecom Project Lead plays a vital role in the development and execution of the enterprise-wide IT strategy. The role is accountable for ensuring that network and telecommunications strategies are aligned with the broader business objectives and deliver measurable value. The position emphasizes customer service excellence, with a focus on system availability, performance, reliability, security, and adherence to established service level metrics.</p>
<p><strong>Preferred Experience</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>5+ years of experience in Network Engineering/Architecture</li>
<li>3+ years of IT support experience</li>
<li>2+ years of Cisco support experience (preferred)</li>
<li>Strong hands-on experience configuring Cisco products and other communication equipment in a global enterprise environment</li>
<li>Proven experience with installation, configuration, and management of routers, switches, and wireless devices</li>
<li>Broad networking expertise including planning, design, testing, integration, and deployment of secure, high-speed, resilient voice, data, and video networks</li>
<li>Network certification (CCNP, CCIE) or equivalent experience preferred</li>
<li>Broad knowledge of system, network, and security best practices</li>
<li>Strong understanding of IT infrastructure components</li>
<li>Familiarity with common security vulnerabilities and mitigation techniques</li>
<li>Experience with infrastructure management tools</li>
<li>Hands-on experience with virtualization platforms such as VMware and Citrix</li>
<li>Practical experience with Microsoft servers and Active Directory</li>
<li>Experience with cloud-based services such as Office 365, SSO, AWS, or Azure</li>
<li>Proficiency in networking, cloud, server, storage, and client technologies (SAN, VSAN, IaaS, automation, backup, business continuity, disaster recovery, ITSM, VoIP, LAN, WAN, SD-WAN, clients, mobile, video, VDI, SBC)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Skills</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Effective influencing and negotiation skills in cross-functional environments</li>
<li>Strong analytical, conceptual thinking, strategic planning, and execution capabilities</li>
<li>Solid business acumen, with a deep understanding of enterprise operations and industry trends</li>
<li>Ability to build consensus, make complex decisions, and drive initiatives forward</li>
<li>High standards of personal ethics, professionalism, and dedication</li>
<li>Up-to-date knowledge of current and emerging network and telecom technologies</li>
<li>Understanding of regulatory and compliance requirements related to network and telecom services</li>
<li>Expertise in IT infrastructure operations and best practices (e.g., ITIL)</li>
<li>Ability to manage and improve infrastructure processes and service delivery</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, Information Systems, or a related field</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Essential Functions</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Provide technical leadership for all network and telecom projects and technologies, ensuring alignment with strategic goals</li>
<li>Participate in the development of IT architecture, technology roadmaps, and governance related to enterprise modernization efforts</li>
<li>Define and communicate strategic direction for core technologies, including networking, cloud, servers, storage, and client systems (SAN, VSAN, IaaS, automation, backup, disaster recovery, ITSM, VoIP, LAN, WAN, SD-WAN, mobile, video, VDI, SBC)</li>
<li>Monitor and improve customer satisfaction and service delivery performance</li>
<li>Lead the design, planning, implementation, and maintenance of network and telecom services supporting business operations</li>
<li>Establish service levels and ensure performance KPIs are consistently met</li>
<li>Oversee root cause analysis for network and telecom-related incidents, including problem tracking, post-mortems, and action follow-up</li>
<li>Develop and manage a comprehensive IT Service Management (ITSM) framework based on industry best practicese</li>
<li>Provide insights on emerging technologies to enhance network and telecom services and align with business strategy</li>
<li>Support the development of sourcing strategies and manage strategic vendor relationships</li>
<li>Participate in IT planning and governance committees to drive technology standards and performance metrics</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Scope &amp; Expectations</strong></p>
<p><strong>Working Conditions:</strong></p>
<p>Primarily works in an office environment; occasional work on or around the manufacturing or distribution floor may be required. The noise level is typically moderate.</p>
<p><strong>Physical Requirements:</strong></p>
<p>Regularly required to sit, talk, or hear. Frequently uses hands to handle or feel objects and reaches with arms. Occasionally stands and walks. Infrequent lifting of items up to 20 pounds may be required.</p>
<p><strong>Equipment Used:</strong></p>
<p>Standard office equipment, including computers, software, hardware, mouse, telephones, and other necessary technology. May work in computer room environments where servers and related systems are housed.</p>
<p><strong>Reporting:</strong></p>
<p>Reports to the Manager, Network &amp; Telecom Services.</p>
<p><strong>Travel Requirements:</strong></p>
<p>Minimal to no travel required for this position.</p>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Winchester ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Virginia ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Software Architect – System Model Application (32513) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 9, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[1S69MBY1]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Job Description: Software Architect &ndash; System Model Application</strong></p>
<p>Our Software Development team architects, develops, tests, and maintains a state-of-the-art engineering software tool that runs on high-performance computing (HPC) infrastructure. This application is designed to model resource allocation and end-to-end communication system performance for a next-generation satellite constellation.</p>
<p>As a&nbsp;<strong>Software Architect</strong>, the selected candidate will play a key leadership role in the software&rsquo;s development, productization, and ongoing maintenance. This position provides critical day-to-day technical direction to team members, fostering a cohesive and productive development environment. The Software Architect will also collaborate with cross-functional engineering teams to ensure seamless integration and alignment with organizational goals.</p>
<p><strong>Main Responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead the design, development, and deployment of the System Model suite, enhancing its readiness as a production-grade engine for operational business applications running in HPC environments&mdash;both cloud-based and on-premise.</li>
<li>Provide technical leadership, mentorship, and support to the development team, encouraging innovation and collaboration.</li>
<li>Develop and propose solutions to complex technical challenges, including recommendations on software architecture and technology stacks.</li>
<li>Collaborate with system engineers, product owners, and testing teams to gather requirements and deliver robust software solutions.</li>
<li>Produce clear technical documentation for internal stakeholders and external collaborators.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education and Experience Required</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s or Master&rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or a related field.</li>
<li>Extensive hands-on experience in software development.</li>
<li>Prior experience in a technical leadership or architecture role.</li>
<li>Proficiency in programming languages including C/C++, Golang, Java, Python, SQL, and Bash.</li>
<li>Experience with tools and technologies such as Kubernetes (including Helm charts), Terraform, Packer, Ansible, containerization, and secret management (e.g., Azure Key Vault, HashiCorp Vault).</li>
<li>Familiarity with Azure Cloud services, including fundamentals, IAM, and networking.</li>
<li>Experience with Matlab and related best practices is an asset.</li>
<li>Comfortable working within Agile development environments.</li>
<li>Experience with cluster job managers.</li>
<li>Background in satellite or communication systems is beneficial but not required.</li>
<li>10+ years of professional experience in software development or system architecture.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Additional Skills and Abilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Strong problem-solving skills with meticulous attention to detail.</li>
<li>Collaborative team player who fosters a positive, innovative team environment.</li>
<li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills.</li>
<li>Proven ability to effectively engage with stakeholders, engineering teams, and partners.</li>
<li>Solid understanding of the business context and constraints of software system design and deployment.</li>
<li>Ability to manage competing priorities and project demands.</li>
<li>Passion for learning and working with complex systems and technologies.</li>
<li>Fluency in English (written and spoken); French is an asset.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior DevOps/Cloud Engineer (32515) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ June 6, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[IBC3Z1V7]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Must Haves:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You have proven expertise in designing, deploying, and managing complex cloud solutions leveraging a wide array of Azure services (IaaS, PaaS, SaaS).</li>
<li>You have deep practical experience with Docker for containerization and expert-level proficiency in managing and optimizing Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) clusters across development, UAT and production environments.</li>
<li>You are a champion of industry cloud and security standards, consistently applying best practices that can be adopted and scaled across the organization</li>
<li>You are expert in designing, implementing and maintaining comprehensive CI/CD pipelines that automate builds, deployments, and cloud infrastructure, ensuring seamless and efficient delivery of software solutions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>RESPONSIBILITIES:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Design, build and support cloud environments to create digital products</li>
<li>Monitor and assess the performance of applications in a cloud environment to ensure solutions are available</li>
<li>Create, test and implement safeguards to maintain data integrity and protect against unauthorized access</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>GENERAL SKILLS:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Experience in one of the leading cloud platforms such as AWS, Azure or Google Cloud, etc</li>
<li>Experience in maintaining complex Linux cloud environments, like CentOS, Ubuntu, or CoreOS, to support modern web technologies: LAMP, MEAN, Drupal and Elasticsearch</li>
<li>Experience setting up development environments and mechanism using tools such as JIRA, Confluence, Maven and Jenkins or similar tools</li>
<li>Experience in scripting languages like Python, Bash, PHP, Java, JavaScript, Node, etc.</li>
<li>Experience in build tools like Git, Ansible, Chef, Puppet etc. for continuous integration</li>
<li>Knowledge of container-based virtualization technology like Docker</li>
<li>Integration experience in building and using APIs</li>
<li>Experience applying industry web, architectural and security standards and best practices</li>
<li>Experience in mobile device management for various versions of cellular and tablets</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>EXPERIENCE AND SKILL SET REQUIREMENTS</strong></p>
<p><strong>Technical Knowledge and Cloud Architecture - 55%</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You have proven expertise in designing, deploying, and managing complex cloud solutions leveraging a wide array of Azure services (IaaS, PaaS, SaaS).</li>
<li>You have deep practical experience with Docker for containerization and expert-level proficiency in managing and optimizing Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) clusters across development, UAT and production environments.</li>
<li>You have proven experience designing, implementing, and supporting microservices.</li>
<li>You have strong track record of integrating with and building robust APIs to deliver API-enabled solutions, improving overall functionality, scalability, security and interoperability.</li>
<li>You have in-depth technical knowledge of complex system architectures, encompassing technical, data, application, and network layers.</li>
<li>You are fluent in multiple scripting and programming languages including Python, Bash, C#, and JavaScript, Node.js</li>
<li>You are proficient in using Git for source code management and automation tools like Ansible, Puppet, Chef, or Terraform for continuous integration</li>
<li>Hands-on experience with both relational and non-relational databases.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>DevOps Standards and Best Practices - 25 %</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are a champion of industry cloud and security standards, consistently applying best practices that can be adopted and scaled across the organization</li>
<li>You are expert in designing, implementing and maintaining comprehensive CI/CD pipelines that automate builds, deployments, and cloud infrastructure, ensuring seamless and efficient delivery of software solutions.</li>
<li>Skilled at balancing the resolution of technical debt with the delivery of innovative enhancements through continuous iteration, ensuring system stability and ongoing improvements.</li>
<li>You are proactively researching industry best practices to support DevOps standards and applying them to improve existing workflows and systems</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Leadership, Communication and Project Delivery - 20%</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are a strong communicator who collaborates closely with multi-disciplinary teams, translating complex technical concepts to technical and non-technical stakeholder</li>
<li>You have strong leadership skills, providing guidance and mentorship to team members</li>
<li>You are skilled in identifying IT risks and developing effective contingency plans</li>
<li>You are able to influence others through persuasive communication rather than authority</li>
<li>You are comfortable leading technical discussions, effectively presenting ideas to product team as well as senior managers</li>
<li>You are expert in analyzing designs to identify coding and/or integration issues, and providing practical resolutions and support.</li>
<li>You are experienced in providing support for multiple products across multiple cloud environments with a strong focus on security, reliability, scalability and quality.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Toronto ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Microsoft Power Platform Developer (32497) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 30, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[SJ1VM7LI]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Microsoft Power Platform Developer &ndash; Hybrid (Lansing, MI)</strong><br /><strong>Client:</strong>&nbsp;Myticas' direct client<br /><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Lansing, MI (Hybrid &ndash; On-site 2 days per week)<br /><strong>Relocation:</strong>&nbsp;Open to local candidates and non-local candidates willing to relocate at their own expense.&nbsp;<em>Remote-only candidates will not be considered.</em></p>
<hr />
<p><strong>Top Required Skills and Experience</strong><br />Experience with Microsoft Power Platform development; including but not limited to Microsoft Dynamics and Power Portal development (4-8 years)<br />Experience with Object Oriented Languages, XML/SOAP, JSON, REST API and Structured Query Language (4-8 years)<br />Knowledge of application and database development and access methods (4-8 years)<br /><br /></p>
<hr />
<p><strong>Job Summary</strong><br />This position functions as an information technology professional, participating in or overseeing a variety of analytical and programming assignments that provide for the development, enhancement, and maintenance of automated information systems. These applications may run in network, client server, and/or web server environments. Duties include problem analysis, programming, peer code review, unit/system testing, testing related to Platform upgrades and Security updates, data loading using tools, Integrations with other applications, executing system tests, and managing software source control and versioning for developed code. This position will perform new development, enhancement, and maintenance work. This position will also require working with other Agency Services team(s) and DTMB enterprise teams.<br /><br />Skills:</p>
<ul>
<li>Experience with Microsoft Power Platform development; including but not limited to Microsoft Dynamics and Power Portal development (4-8 years)</li>
<li>Experience with Object Oriented Languages, XML/SOAP, JSON, REST API and Structured Query Language (4-8 years)</li>
<li>Knowledge of application and database development and access methods (4-8 years)</li>
<li>Knowledge of browser based (web) and object-oriented application design techniques and tools (3-5 years)</li>
<li>Ability to recognize, gather, assemble, correlate, and analyze facts; draw conclusions; investigate and define problems; and devise solutions and alternatives for automated information technology systems (3-5 years)</li>
<li>Ability to prepare detailed written instructions and documentation (3-5 years)</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Lansing ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Michigan ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ MES Analyst/SAP MII Developer (32486) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 28, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[TO45VHKB]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Myticas Consulting has a direct client in need of a MES Analyst/SAP MII Developer in Manchester, Michigan.&nbsp;</strong>This is a&nbsp;<strong>HYBRID</strong>&nbsp;direct hire role. Prefer candidates located in Michigan.</p>
<p>Provide business support to manufacturing operations utilizing the SAP MII platform custom-developed shop floor application. Maintain and develop SAP MII application for customized functionality as required for shop floor data collection and transactional execution. Manage interfaces to external systems (including OPC Servers, PLCs, and other connectors for collecting data) transforming as needed and loading into SAP ECC. Specific responsibilities and duties include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Support global SAP MII implementation and projects (Netweaver, MII, PCo, and NWDI).</li>
<li>Support and/or develop MII custom application.</li>
<li>Develop interfaces to manufacturing equipment as needed for automated data collection.</li>
<li>Manage all code in a formal source control system (NWDI) including change management procedures.</li>
<li>Develop barcode labels needed for internal and external customers.</li>
<li>Develop and manage interfaces to SAP ECC.</li>
<li>Develop systems documentation and training materials.</li>
<li>Train end users across various levels of Amcor&rsquo;s organization.</li>
<li>Implement on-going release management processes to support the shop floor functions.</li>
<li>Provide manufacturing business post go-live support.</li>
<li>Domestic travel to Amcor manufacturing plants may require up to 50% of the time during projects; International travel up to 2 trips per year. This position is located at Amcor&rsquo;s Manchester, MI site, with option to telecommute from anywhere in the United States; Required attendance of special events and meetings at Manchester, MI site, as assigned by supervisor.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Minimum Requirements:</strong>&nbsp;Bachelor&rsquo;s degree or the foreign equivalent in Electrical and Computer Engineering, Manufacturing Engineering Systems Technology, Computer Science or a closely related engineering or computer science field and 10 years of progressively responsible post-Bachelor&rsquo;s experience as MES Analyst/SAP MII Developer, Programmer Analyst, Software Engineer, or in a closely related occupation involving SAP.</p>
<p><strong>Experience to include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>10 years performing SAP MII analysis, development, and project implementation.</li>
<li>10 years designing and implementing complex solutions with SAP MII.</li>
<li>10 years creating query templates, display templates, business logic transactions, reports, and web page user interfaces.</li>
<li>5 years working for a manufacturing company.</li>
<li>5 years working with Oracle and DB2 databases.</li>
<li>5 years performing web development, including Java Scripting.</li>
<li>2 years establishing, configuring, and maintaining SAP ECC interfaces to SAP MII MES systems.</li>
</ul>
<p>All education, experience, and training may be gained concurrently. Applicants must be U.S. workers (includes U.S. citizens, permanent residents, foreign nationals granted temporary residence under one of the 1986 legalization programs, refugees, and asylees).</p>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ann Arbor ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Michigan ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Senior Java AWS Developer (32485) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 27, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[GOIOLATY]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Myticas direct client is seeking Senior Java AWS Developer/Engineer, Onsite/Hybrid at Chicago, IL.</p>
<p>MUST be a US Citizen or Green Card Holder who is able/willing to work on W2 Contract ONLY.</p>
<p><strong>NOT considering candidates requiring visa sponsorship.</strong></p>
<p><strong>NOTE:</strong>&nbsp;**This position requires a 2-step background check process (ANACI) which may take 6-8 weeks for completion.**</p>
<p><strong>Contract Duration &ndash; 1 year</strong></p>
<p><strong>Top competencies required for this position:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Java with Spring framework</li>
<li>SQL skills</li>
<li>AWS services</li>
<li>Terraform Infrastructure as a Code</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Work on migration of complex, monolithic Java Spring applications from on-premises environments to AWS, ensuring minimal downtime and data integrity.</li>
<li>Design and implement scalable, cloud-native solutions using AWS services such as ECS, RDS, S3 etc.</li>
<li>Translate existing SQL-heavy data operations in AWS-managed databases (e.g., RDS, Aurora) while optimizing performance.</li>
<li>Develop and maintain Infrastructure as Code (IaC) using tools like Terraform for consistent, automated cloud provisioning.</li>
<li>Collaborate with cross-functional teams to refactor legacy components, integrate with Ops best practices, and ensure security, scalability, and operational excellence.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Chicago ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Illinois ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>                                                                                                                       
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ ASIC Development Engineer (32477) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 23, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[7AZQGYJS]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p data-start="118" data-end="191"><strong data-start="118" data-end="191">Position: Senior ASIC Design Engineer &ndash; Optical Communication Systems</strong></p>
<p data-start="193" data-end="621">Our client&rsquo;s team is expanding and seeking highly motivated, experienced professional engineers to help develop next-generation systems in a rapidly growing and competitive industry. This is an excellent opportunity to contribute to cutting-edge technologies in optical communication. Candidates must hold a degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, or possess equivalent professional experience.</p>
<p data-start="623" data-end="648"><strong data-start="623" data-end="648">Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li data-start="652" data-end="761">Develop state-of-the-art electronic devices and intellectual property (IP) for optical communication systems.</li>
<li data-start="764" data-end="827">Apply proven expertise in deep sub-micron silicon technologies.</li>
<li data-start="830" data-end="906">Collaborate effectively within a multi-site, international development team.</li>
<li data-start="909" data-end="967">Design ASIC devices for the processing of optical signals.</li>
</ul>
<p data-start="969" data-end="1008"><strong data-start="969" data-end="1008">Required Qualifications and Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li data-start="1012" data-end="1117">Master&rsquo;s degree or PhD in Electronic Engineering, Telecommunication Engineering, or a related discipline.</li>
<li data-start="1120" data-end="1199">A minimum of 8 years of demonstrated experience in deep sub-micron ASIC design.</li>
<li data-start="1202" data-end="1275">Proficiency in VHDL and/or Verilog for development and ASIC verification.</li>
<li data-start="1278" data-end="1376">Preferred experience in digital signal processing (DSP) and forward error correction (FEC) design.</li>
<li data-start="1379" data-end="1430">Experience with high-speed analog design is a plus.</li>
<li data-start="1433" data-end="1493">Strong analytical thinking and problem-solving capabilities.</li>
<li data-start="1496" data-end="1597">Excellent teamwork skills, with the ability to collaborate across international teams and time zones.</li>
<li data-start="1600" data-end="1661">Effective communication skills, including fluency in English.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Permanent ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Mountain View ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ California ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ ASIC Development Engineer (32476) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 22, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[4PKPPVVB]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p data-start="120" data-end="194"><strong data-start="120" data-end="194">Job Title: Senior ASIC Design Engineer &ndash; Optical Communication Systems</strong></p>
<p data-start="196" data-end="527">Our client&rsquo;s team is expanding and seeking highly motivated, experienced professional engineers to join in the development of next-generation systems within a fast-growing and competitive environment. Candidates must hold a degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, or possess equivalent experience.</p>
<p data-start="529" data-end="555"><strong data-start="529" data-end="555">Main Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li data-start="559" data-end="687">Design and development of state-of-the-art electronic devices and intellectual property (IP) for optical communication systems</li>
<li data-start="690" data-end="765">Demonstrated experience working with deep sub-micron silicon technologies</li>
<li data-start="768" data-end="833">Collaboration within multi-site international development teams</li>
<li data-start="836" data-end="890">Design of ASIC devices for optical signal processing</li>
</ul>
<p data-start="892" data-end="931"><strong data-start="892" data-end="931">Required Skills and Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li data-start="935" data-end="1043">Master&rsquo;s degree or Ph.D. in Electronic Engineering, Telecommunication Engineering, or a related discipline</li>
<li data-start="1046" data-end="1118">Minimum of 8 years of proven experience in deep sub-micron ASIC design</li>
<li data-start="1121" data-end="1184">Proficiency in VHDL/Verilog development and ASIC verification</li>
<li data-start="1187" data-end="1286">Preferred experience in digital signal processing (DSP) and forward error correction (FEC) design</li>
<li data-start="1289" data-end="1329">Experience in high-speed analog design</li>
<li data-start="1332" data-end="1387">Strong analytical thinking and problem-solving skills</li>
<li data-start="1390" data-end="1489">Effective teamwork and ability to collaborate with international teams across multiple time zones</li>
<li data-start="1492" data-end="1543">Excellent verbal and written communication skills</li>
<li data-start="1546" data-end="1570">Proficiency in English</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Ottawa ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ RAN Network (32467) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 19, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[ZL4395QF]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Customer Support Engine</p>
<p><strong>Customer Support Engineer &ndash; RAN (Radio Access Network)</strong></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong>&nbsp;Onsite in Chicago, IL</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong>&nbsp;No Corp-to-Corp engagements.</p>
<p><strong>Security Clearance:</strong>&nbsp;Must be able to obtain and maintain security clearance.</p>
<p><strong>Job Overview:</strong></p>
<p>We are seeking an experienced Customer Support Engineer specializing in RAN to work as an onsite Resident Engineer with our customer in Chicago. The ideal candidate will have recent, hands-on experience supporting RAN technologies and meeting the responsibilities outlined below.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Perform first-level troubleshooting and respond to anomalies in RAN network elements.</li>
<li>Escalate unresolved issues by creating detailed support tickets.</li>
<li>Support network activities including migrations, upgrades, and change implementations on behalf of the customer.</li>
<li>Prepare and review Methods of Procedure (MOPs) for planned activities, as outlined in the statement of work (SOW).</li>
<li>Participate in Operational Readiness Testing (ORT) and Acceptance Testing Procedures (ATP), as per the SOW.</li>
<li>Generate and deliver incident reports and KPI reports when required.</li>
<li>Provide technical support and troubleshooting to end-users and internal stakeholders.</li>
<li>Maintain accurate documentation of network configurations, changes, and system upgrades.</li>
<li>Lead trained contractors and BSS engineers during the installation and integration of telecommunications equipment.</li>
<li>Conduct trials, feature testing, and new product launches, as outlined in the SOW.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Hands-on experience with Operations and Maintenance (O&amp;M) for AirScale and FlexiZone (Indoor &amp; Outdoor) BTS site solutions.</li>
<li>Proficiency in BTS Element Management tools, including Web User Interface, BTS Site Manager, and BTS CLI.</li>
<li>Strong troubleshooting skills using tools such as EMIL Toolkit, DCAP, UTF, and 5G Tool Kit.</li>
<li>Experience working with OSS applications including Mantray, CM Operation Manager, CM Editor, Workflow Tool, Software Manager, and Monitor Application.</li>
<li>Familiarity with documentation and knowledge portals.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Chicago ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Illinois ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ SAP Technical Integration Manager (32440) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 12, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[E3D3Z71S]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Our Winnipeg, Manitoba client is looking for an experienced&nbsp;<strong>SAP Tech/Integration Manager</strong>&nbsp;to lead the design phase of an SAP integration project involving SAP and non-SAP systems. This is a&nbsp;<strong><u>HYBRID</u></strong>&nbsp;model with the&nbsp;<strong><u>Majority of the work model will be on site in Winnipeg</u></strong>. The focus will be on end-to-end integration design within a Utilities industry context. This is a highly collaborative role requiring both technical leadership and business acumen.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead technical workshops and contribute to the integration strategy.</li>
<li>Provide expertise in integration architecture and cross-functional design.</li>
<li>Define and document interface requirements (flow, mapping, transformation, error handling, etc.).</li>
<li>Align SAP S/4HANA system capabilities with business objectives.</li>
<li>Support creation of integration designs, functional specs, and connectivity documentation.</li>
<li>Collaborate across workstreams to manage integration points and business processes.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Skills &amp; Experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>10+ years of experience with SAP integration projects, preferably in the Utilities sector.</li>
<li>Strong understanding of integration practices in areas such as Finance, Customer Service, Procurement (Ariba), HR/SFSF, and Enterprise Assets (GIS, ESRI, EPRI).</li>
<li>Hands-on experience with SAP PI/PO, SAP BTP, API integrations, and Cloud Platform tools.</li>
<li>Proven track record managing technical design and interface development for SAP S/4HANA implementations.</li>
<li>Strong communication and stakeholder facilitation skills.</li>
<li>MUST BE BASED IN WINNIPEG, MB</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Winnipeg ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Manitoba ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ SAP Data Lead BODS - Manager/Senior Manager (32441) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 12, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[F0JH2SJD]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p>Our client, a global leader in the technology/software industry, is looking for a <strong>SAP Data Lead (BODS)</strong> at the <strong>Manager/Senior Manager</strong> level for a remote contract. The successful candidate will be responsible for leading data analysis efforts, ensuring data accuracy, and working with stakeholders across business and technical teams in an SAP environment.</p>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Lead data analysis and preparation efforts within SAP environments</li>
<li>Utilize SAP Data Services (BODS) for data extraction, transformation, and load activities</li>
<li>Implement and monitor data quality rules and controls</li>
<li>Analyze data to identify trends, inconsistencies, and improvement opportunities</li>
<li>Collaborate with SAP functional leads, data governance teams, business stakeholders, and other BODS developers</li>
<li>Interpret and work with SAP master and transactional data structures and physical table schemas</li>
<li>Provide leadership and mentorship to the developer team</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>20+ years of experience in data-related roles, including SAP Data Services</li>
<li>Strong hands-on experience with SAP BODS (ETL, DQ rules, data warehousing)</li>
<li>Expertise in SAP data models, including master and transactional data</li>
<li>Previous experience leading cross-functional data teams</li>
<li>Excellent stakeholder communication and leadership skills</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Waterloo ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ QC Laboratory Analyst (32376) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ May 2, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[K2YBKQC8]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>Myticas' direct client is seeking an IT Systems/Laboratory Analyst</strong>- Hypid at Worcester, MA (<strong>4 days onsite&nbsp;</strong>at Worcester, MA).</p>
<p><strong>Duration:</strong>&nbsp;6+ Months Contract (Possible further extension)</p>
<p><strong>Top Skills/Experience Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Familiarity and experience installing Acronis, Crowd strike( antivirus software), patchlab.</li>
<li>Strong communication skills</li>
<li>Strong excel macros and excel skills.</li>
<li>Medium proficiency in Power platforms</li>
<li>Decommissioning computer systems.</li>
<li>GMP experience</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Job Description Summary:</strong></p>
<p>Responsible for the provision of technical support for all IT/BTS (Business Technology Solutions) systems, activities, development, and administration of plant Quality Control (QC) and IT systems as well as similar scope on manufacturing operations.</p>
<p>Supports all hands-on projects that affect the lab and manufacturing IT infrastructure, systems, security, workstations, support, and IT standards.</p>
<p><strong>Job Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Work on client's IT QC systems and application projects.</li>
<li>Work on client's IT manufacturing systems and application projects.</li>
<li>Is responsible for the implementation and rollout of new IT systems.</li>
<li>Lead client' IT QC systems and application projects.</li>
<li>Lead client' IT manufacturing systems and application projects.</li>
<li>Ensure system documentation and computerized systems compliance with Data Integrity policies and regulatory requirements.</li>
<li>Collaborate with BTS IAI (Infrastructure Architecture Innovation) to maintain oversight over client's network infrastructure pertaining to the site.</li>
<li>Is responsible for ensuring the maximum availability of IT equipment and systems to support the business.</li>
<li>Participate in continuous improvement by identification and implementation of cost saving opportunities within the IT area.</li>
<li>Is the site subject matter expert (SME) for plant IT systems.</li>
<li>Continually building knowledge of the business while keeping current with new technologies.</li>
<li>Collaborate closely with other site functions on cross-functional projects and, responsible for delivering IT capabilities and support to site projects.</li>
<li>Liaise with IT Contractors/Consultants and ensure compliance with contractor management site policies.</li>
<li>Support of QC desktop/workstation and server applications.</li>
<li>Support of manufacturing desktop/workstation and server applications.</li>
<li>Training of employees on relevant applications.</li>
<li>Validation / Qualification of hardware and software as required by client's policies and SOPs.</li>
<li>Is responsible for data backup and administration / maintenance of the plant QC &amp; manufacturing systems.</li>
<li>Protect client's from cyber risk on QC equipment and site assets, adhering to cyber security procedures and practices of client's.</li>
<li>Is responsible for patching of the plant QC systems.</li>
<li>Is responsible for patching of the plant manufacturing IT systems.</li>
<li>Participation in cross functional teams and initiatives across the site.</li>
<li>Adheres to and supports all EHS standards, procedures, and policies.</li>
<li>Provide technical leadership on IT to functional areas and collaborates with key stakeholders.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Skills/Qualifications/Experience:</strong></p>
<p>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree: Degree level qualification in computer science or equivalent relevant discipline or respective proven expertise and experience</p>
<p><strong>Cognitive/Business Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Requires a high level of attention to detail and mental concentration to always ensure accuracy and total compliance with procedures.</li>
<li>Requires proven problem-solving skills and the ability to adapt to new requirements.</li>
<li>Must be results driven striving to meet all targets and metric standards as set by site/department and division leaders.</li>
<li>Requires innovative thinking, where new and untested solutions are proposed, demonstrated, and implemented on a regular basis.</li>
<li>Requires total commitment to quality and always maintaining a high standard of work.</li>
<li>Always demonstrates the highest levels of integrity and a strong work ethic.</li>
<li>Strong communication skills, both verbal and written, are required for the execution of this role.</li>
<li>Strong interpersonal skills are required.</li>
<li>Supports the principles of Perfect Performance.</li>
<li>Apply advanced technical knowledge and experience to the solution of a poad array of technical problems.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Job/Technical Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 years plus in IT QC System / Application Support (essential)</li>
<li>3 years plus of relevant IT experience (Essential)</li>
<li>ITIL (Desirable)</li>
<li>GAMP (Desirable)</li>
<li>Project Management must</li>
<li>Waters Empower (Desirable)</li>
<li>Familiarity with Acronis, CrowdStrike installs and maintenance as well as Lab instruments-Empower CE, SOloVPE, SHimatsu,Nexxus, BCS and others</li>
<li>Microsoft O365 PowerApps / PowerBi</li>
<li>Very strong knowledge on excel macros and powerapps</li>
<li>Familiarity with Sciex,Biotek,Waters,Plate freezers</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Worcester ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Massachusetts ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ United States ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      <![CDATA[ Java Technical Consultant - Software Engineer (32247) ]]>
    </title>
    <company>
      <![CDATA[ Myticas Consulting ]]>
    </company>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[ April 29, 2025 ]]>
    </date>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[POOR8PGL]]></referencenumber>
    <url><![CDATA[https://myticas.com/]]></url><description>
      <![CDATA[ 
<p><strong>RESPONSIBILITES</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Develop software solutions by studying information needs, conferring with users, studying systems flow, data usage, and work processes, investigating problem areas, and following the software development lifecycle.</li>
<li>Implement well-designed, testable, and efficient codes according to project requirements and adhere to coding standards, guidelines, quality procedures, and schedules.</li>
<li>Lead software projects from scoping requirements through actual launch and implementation.</li>
<li>Collaborate with team members on analysis, design reviews, and testing.</li>
<li>Document and demonstrate solutions by developing documentation, flowcharts, layouts, diagrams, charts, code comments, and clear code.</li>
<li>Perform thorough unit testing and support in resolving defects while ensuring proper documentation of all activities.</li>
<li>Complete peer-to-peer code reviews and improve operations by conducting systems analysis and recommending changes in policies and procedures.</li>
<li>Provide inputs and assist in the preparation of high-level designs.</li>
<li>Protect operations by keeping information confidential.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>What do I need to succeed?</strong></p>
<p><strong>MUST HAVE:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in computer science or software or systems engineering.</li>
<li>6+ years of working experience as a Software Engineer with a consistent track record of delivery, preferably in an agile environment.</li>
<li>Experience using Eclipse, Maven, and source control (SVN, Git).</li>
<li>Well-versed in JAVA, J2EE, Spring Boot, design patterns, Web Services, REST-based APIs, Apache Kafka, schema registry, Apache Nifi.</li>
<li>Must have client-facing experience.</li>
<li>Clear and concise verbal communication skills and the ability to communicate with all levels of an organization, both internally and externally.</li>
<li>Strong interpersonal skills with the ability to foster team collaboration.</li>
<li>Be proactive with a strong desire to learn.</li>
<li>Strong analytical thinking and problem-solving skills with the ability to create innovative solutions.</li>
<li>Ability to work across multiple project areas and manage competing responsibilities simultaneously.</li>
<li>Strong knowledge of and experience with object oriented and functional design patterns.</li>
<li>Knowledge of and experience with PostgreSQL database</li>
<li>Create coding and design guidelines to be used throughout our applications;</li>
<li>Develop and maintain Java applications in the development and test environments.</li>
<li>Strong knowledge of and experience with JSON packages and schemas.</li>
<li>Knowledge of and familiarity with Java build systems, i.e. Maven</li>
<li>Strong critical thinking, decision-making, problem-solving, and attention to detail skills.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>NICE TO HAVE:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Automation testing experience (JUnit).</li>
<li>Application development experience in a large enterprise IT environment.</li>
<li>Application development experience in an Agile environment using TDD and BDD.</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </description>
    <jobtype>
      <![CDATA[ Contract ]]>
    </jobtype>
    <city>
      <![CDATA[ Toronto ]]>
    </city>
    <state>
      <![CDATA[ Ontario ]]>
    </state>
    <country>
      <![CDATA[ Canada ]]>
    </country>
    <category>
      <![CDATA[  ]]>
    </category>
    <apply_email>
      <![CDATA[ apply@myticas.com ]]>
    </apply_email>
    <remotetype>
      <![CDATA[]]>
    </remotetype>
  </job>
</source>
